Stop, Yash. Stop.
Pranab-da's dog bit Mr Vajpayee.
Our Pranab-da? Pranab Mukherjee?
A dog bit him on his walk.
Oh no! Now that's 14 injections.
That's not written here.
He has no choice. What is it?
- There's eggplant on the pen.
- So?
I told you not to come
at lunchtime.
Eggplant! It's not poison, is it?
Strange fellow.
- Who eats eggplant every day?
- Well, I do.
Every day?
I like it.
Careful.
What's this?
- Well?
- An invitation.
- To what?
- The World Cup.
Really?
The dacoit Phoolan Devi
is surrendering.
- I hear she's beautiful.
- There's no photo.
Look! The launch of the Maruti car.
Kapil Dev, Mohinder Amarnath,
Madan Lal, Kirti Azad,
Sunil Valson.
Why are you taking their
bags with you, Mr Singh?
Because they're already in England,
playing County Cricket.
Congrats.
You mean they've replaced Gavaskar
with this guy as captain?
Hey!
- Can he do it?
- Sure, he can.
That also in England?
He can't even speak
English properly.
But he plays cricket well.
So what?
When are you back, Mr Singh?
When there are no more
matches for us to play.
The East Africans aren't playing.
So, who will you defeat?
The Cricket Board isn't even
hosting a farewell party.
Good luck!
Take care. See you.
We'll celebrate when we're back.
Celebrate what?
Good luck, Mr Singh.
All the best.
Well bowled, Kaps!
Mr Dev, your call to India
is connected, sir.
Hello, Romi.
Romi's out right now, Kuku.
Talk to me instead.
What will be happening here?
Half the kids are drinking milk.
The others are playing cricket.
You should play cricket all day
and drink gallons of milk.
A call from London?
And you didn't tell me?
Pinky, Happi, Guddo! Come,
a call from London.
And you...Meshi!
Call Kake too.
Come here!
Give me the phone.
Hello, Kuku!
Yes, Mama.
- Are you wearing your sweater?
- Yes, Mama. I will.
Son, win the Cup and come home.
Yes, Mama.
Tell me.
Hello.
The line's cut.
I didn't get a chance to talk.
Kaps, catch!
Impossible!
If Kapil catches it, I'll do
anything he wants me to.
- Sorry, sorry. That was tough.
- Jimmy said,
if you catch it, you can ask
for anything.
I'll ask him to teach me English
before the World Cup starts.
Asking for my life
would be easier!
That reminds me.
Did you talk to Lala-ji today?
- I'll do it now. Hold this.
- Give him my regards.
He isn't scared of the world's
fastest bowlers,
but trembles when he hears
Lala-ji's name.
Lala-ji, they're not playing
proper cricket.
60 overs. Start in the morning
finish in the evening.
Carry on like this and the game
will be reduced to 10 or 20 overs.
Sharma-ji, what nonsense!
- Mr Jimmy is on the line.
- He'll live a hundred years.
Hello, Jimmy, my son.
How are you?
I'm sending you two bottles
of pickle with Yash.
Mr Singh, why do you have
so many bottles of pickle?
Opening a store in London?
The food's so bland there.
Can't eat without pickles.
Well, sir, you'll have to pay
excess baggage.
Or leave some behind.
Give me a receipt.
Maan, we're vegetarians.
How will we eat there?
That's 5800-rupees.
But, sir, I don't have
that much on me.
Here.
Ask your office to pay
the money tomorrow.
Yes.
Mr Singh! Will you do me a favour?
- Can you get me an autograph?
- You can ask them now.
No, no.
I mean Viv Richards.
Please try.
Don't forget.
Thank you very much.
I'll get you Queen Elizabeth's
autograph too. You fool!
Sunil Gavaskar.
Syed Kirmani.
Yashpal Sharma.
Krishnamachari Srikkanth.
Dilip Vengsarkar.
Roger Binny.
Balwinder Singh Sandhu.
Sandeep Patil.
Ravi Shastri.
PR Man Singh.
Where's our team bus?
No, no. No bus here
for Indian team.
You mean on flight only?
When?
Rascal! You just got engaged.
Not for you.
The bus is here.
- Tell me more.
- Let's get on the bus.
- Did something happen?
- None of your business.
Tell me!
Patla told the airhostess
on our flight:
"Hi, I'm Sandeep Patil.
Sandy to you."
Then Yashpal says,
"Hi, I'm Yash to you."
The rascal added if India wins
the World Cup,
he'll eat this newspaper.
Ballu was next. And you know
what he said?
He says to her:
"Hi, I'm Balwinder Singh Sandhu."
"Balls to you!"
Listen, everyone.
Today for the vegetarians, there's
only bread, butter and salad.
Why look at me, Cheeka?
- We'll sort it out tomorrow.
- Listen, soldiers!
Welcome to London!
We must play four warm-up matches
before the tournament.
Let's show them what
we're made of.
This moment is frozen in time
A glorious dream is a few steps away
- What?
- South Indian.
What's this rubbish you're eating?
Five, ten, fifteen.
Today belongs to you.
Go outside.
Hello, Simran.
- Did you get there safely?
- Yes, I'm in London.
- Have you eaten?
- Yes, I have.
The airhostess served us lunch.
Very nice.
"Nice?" The airhostess?
No, the food was nice.
Cross the bumpy roads ahead
Good ball, Kaps.
What a shot! It's a boundary, bro.
Inswinger.
Easy, Cheeka.
It's only net practice.
When I hit, I hit hard.
I don't know how to play defence.
I know only hitting.
Go, go bowl.
Kapil, I'll end up hitting his head.
He doesn't know defence.
Mr Man Singh, how may I help you?
This pass says entry to all
stadiums except Lord's.
But India doesn't have any game
at Lord's.
But the Finals are at Lord's,
right?
So Mr Man Singh, if and when
India reaches the Final,
we shall happily issue you the pass.
OK.
Inswinger.
When you bowl an inswinger,
must you telegram the batsman?
Hide your grip.
Come on! Again.
That's good.
Where were you, brother?
- Learning a lesson.
- What lesson?
Just that we may have gained
our independence 35 years ago,
but we haven't yet won respect,
Captain.
Ballu.
A girl? In Ballu's room?
Yes! She must've just showered
because her hair was wet.
- And Ballu?
- Must have been in the shower?
Why weren't they bathing together?
I'll find out.
Do you plan to rub their backs
with soap?
No! It can't be Ballu.
It just can't be him.
He just got engaged to Simran.
There was a girl near the nets.
Maybe it was her.
Kaps...
Thank you, Kaps.
What is it?
Catch!
Another wicket down for India.
They're looking in trouble here.
Just 82 for 5.
Not a very good start to
their World Cup preparations.
The team is hopeless.
Don't lose face here.
We'll be disgraced.
At least win one match. Just one.
Kapil Dev!
Autograph, please.
I'm a fast bowler too.
- Do you drink milk too?
- Yes.
If you come to watch the match,
then cheer loudly.
But I can't come.
Because Papa says India never wins,
so why waste precious money
on tickets.
Kapil, in the run up
to the World Cup,
your team has lost
3 practice matches.
One against a minor county.
You talk...
You talk like fast bowler.
Can you talk slow like spin bowler?
My hand little tight in English.
What do you think your team's
chances are in the World Cup?
We here to win!
To win the World Cup?
What else we here for?
In the history of the World Cup,
the West Indies haven't lost
a match.
Not one!
Michael Holding.
He's known as "Whispering Death."
It's like a bullet,
if it hits you
you're dead.
That's Andy Roberts.
He's called the "Hitman".
He kills them one by one.
Kapil, tomorrow you're meeting the
Queen at Buckingham Palace.
What will you say to her?
I'll get her blessings, so
we will win the World Cup.
And that's Marshall.
The shortest, but the fastest.
And there's Big Bird.
Joel Garner.
He's 6ft 8".
His outstretched hand is 3ft,
then he jumps 2ft,
so his ball comes at you
from a height of 12 feet.
And at 150kms per hour.
Time to run for cover!
Shut up!
Is this cricket or a horror film?
Why scare everyone?
No, no. Sir, no!
Kapil was just being enthusiastic.
Our return is confirmed for June 20th,
before the semi-finals.
Talk later. I'm off to
Buckingham Palace.
There's a protocol meeting.
Once the Queen approaches
the players,
she will extend her hand out
to them.
They must hold the tip
of her fingers gently,
and make a small bow
from the neck.
Like this.
The team will then proceed to Lord's
for the traditional team photographs.
Once you've said, "Your Majesty,"
make sure you hold only the tips
of her fingers. Elegantly.
Don't grab hold of her hand.
Got it?
Now where do we find elegance?
You must have some!
Just look for it!
Maan, we're nervous and you think
it's funny?
A waste of time.
Are we here to play cricket,
or to act in a Shakespeare play?
Long live the Queen!
Guys, it's tradition.
The Queen will wish you luck.
- Yes.
- The Brit is talking!
Roger, when you meet the Queen,
tell her your grandfather
was Scottish. She'll be happy.
- Shut up, you bugger.
- You burger!
Hey, Cheeka. Watch it!
Don't wink at the Queen.
- Or you'll land up in jail.
- Shut up!
I'm serious.
I'm wearing a new wig for her.
Looking smart, Kiri.
Is this all right, Your Majesty?
Yes.
Just do whatever Kiri does.
Sunil Valson, heart of our team.
Best of luck.
Mohinder Amarnath, Vice-Captain he is.
- Your Majesty.
- Best of luck.
Thank you.
Sunil Gavaskar.
He don't need
no introduction.
I've seen you play before.
Your Majesty, an honour.
Wicket keeper, Syed Kirmani.
Your Majesty.
- Best of luck.
- Thank you.
Srikkanth, opening batsman.
He not know meaning of defence.
- Your Majesty.
- Best of luck.
Madan Lal, all-rounder.
- Thank you.
Imran.
- How are you, Kapil?
- All good.
How's practice?
Hello, sir. Myself Srikkanth.
I'm from the Indian cricket team.
Holding, sir.
Clive sir. Nice to meet you.
Sir, big fan!
- Best of luck.
- Thank you, sir. Thank you.
Gentlemen, line up, please.
- Maan, let's go.
- We'll stand in the usual order.
Time for the photograph.
Hey, giant! No one will see me.
Everybody, look into the lens.
Stand aside, Maan.
Can I say something, Captain?
You're the first man who said
we will win.
The journalists kept firing
questions at you
and you kept saying:
"We will win!"
A true freedom fighter!
Ever since I was a kid,
my mother told me:
"Win and come back home, son!"
No best of luck! Just win.
Bravo! Inspiration.
Inspire the whole team as well.
The hotel is quite far away.
We have a match tomorrow.
Let's have a meeting.
Why? Everyone knows what
they're supposed to do.
Tomorrow's the first World Cup match.
Captain, we should talk.
Maan, I don't know how
to give a speech.
Listen, everyone. Hey!
Team meeting!
There are seven senior players here.
What I can say?
Gentleman! The Captain.
Tomorrow, match very important.
Cheeka, you hit!
OK, brother.
Dilip, you strong.
Kirti, you focus.
Your problem there.
Sandy, hit them hard.
Yash, you're a lion.
Kiri, you'll be the wicket keeper.
That's what I do in every match, Kaps.
Enough?
Inspiration!
Like people says,
taste the success once,
tongue want more!
Captain.
Remember what your mother told you.
Just come home a winner!
Thank you.
I think team meeting is over.
I don't know what you say,
I don't know what he say
I want to dance and play
I want to play the game
of cricket
The historical field at Old Trafford.
Today is India's first match
in the World Cup.
They're up against the champions,
West Indies.
Both teams are ready to enter
the ground.
- - But rain is causing a delay.
- Oh no, it's raining there.
There's one thing we do know,
India have never won a single
game in the World Cup.
Unless you chose to remember that
game against East Africa
in 1975.
I would count that.
I was Man of the Match in that game.
- Oh, I had forgotten.
- Ah, now you know.
But the fact is, my dear friend,
the West Indies are here to win
this Cup for the third time in a row.
The rain gods have probably saved
the Indians from facing a crushing defeat.
So the covers are coming off
and play should begin soon.
I guess the Indians didn't pray enough.
It's stopped raining.
- Shut the idiot up!
- Let them speak.
The World Champions are stepping
onto the ground to a rousing reception
- by their legions of fans.
- Sunshine!
India is in Group B along
with two World Cup giants...
The 4th team, Zimbabwe, are playing
Australia today at Trent Bridge.
It's me or the West Indies.
Windy conditions and a moist wicket
will add sideways movement
to the lethal West Indies attack.
This will be no easy task
for the opening batsmen,
Sunil Gavaskar and
Krishnamachari Srikkanth.
Sunny, why is the wicket keeper
standing so far away?
Hey, man. Why you standing
so far from the wicket, man?
You'll soon find out, man.
You'll soon find out.
"Find out?"
Find out what?
- Good luck, Cheeka.
- Good luck, Sunny.
World Cup, 1983!
India's first match.
They're playing against the West Indies,
the strongest team in the world.
Make him smell the leather, Mikey.
Play!
Well bowled, Mikey.
Well bowled.
Too good for him.
Get it?
Too quick, Mikey.
He can't see
the ball.
This is the first time Srikkanth
is playing against the West Indies.
Make him smell the ball, Mikey.
Let's get him.
Too fast for him, Mikey.
What happened, man?
Too fast for you?
Now the ball is in Andy Roberts's hands.
Facing him is India's renowned
batsman, Sunil Gavaskar.
The Indian batsmen are being
severely restricted by the bowlers.
They really need to breakout now.
- Catch it!
- That's the first one, Mikey.
Catches the outside edge.
An easy caught behind.
Srikkanth made 14 runs
and is out!
- Catch it!
- Howzat?
Got him.
India is in big trouble now. Two
wickets down in quick succession.
I don't think the Indians can
quite see the ball, Farokh.
It's moving too fast for them.
Not a single boundary
for India till now.
Can you see the scoreboard?
Why do we bother?
Yashpal faces Garner's bowling.
Brilliant shot!
Yashpal hits a beautiful cover drive.
The ball crosses the boundary like a bullet.
Yashpal Sharma has hit
India's first boundary.
Another four! Great batting by
these two players.
That's his 'baadaam' shot.
His signature shot!
India have recovered from
their shaky start.
- Yash is hitting well.
- Yes.
What do you say now?
Sharma and Patil seem to be
seeing the ball pretty well.
Well, yes. I would have
to agree with that.
Gomy!
Yashpal is playing pace well.
Clive has now brought in a spinner.
Gomes is coming in to bowl.
Sharma hits him too!
He sweeps it to deep square leg.
Holding can't get there in time.
- That's it, guys.
- Good shot. Yash, son.
Patil hits a straight drive over
the bowler's head.
The ball crosses the boundary.
What a partnership between
Yashpal and Patil!
Patil is clean bowled by Gomes.
The Haryana hurricane,
Kapil Dev, walks in.
The score is 125/4.
Gomes coming into bowl.
Kapil hits it for a quick single.
Great shot by Yashpal! 4 runs.
- Catch it.
- Yeah.
Kapil Dev heads to the pavilion.
He's out with only 6 runs.
Oh no! Kapil is out for only six runs.
Oh, get it.
That's it.
50 runs up for Yashpal Sharma.
That's on the pads.
India now 214/6.
Come on!
Clean bowled! Ending a game
changing play by Yashpal.
A well-deserved standing ovation.
A great innings.
India now at 243/7.
That knock by Yashpal was truly
not expected, was it?
9 boundaries.
It's the highest score by
an Indian batsman in any World Cup.
Looks like the Indians want to
be taken seriously this time.
262 for 8.
That's a good score
put up by the Indian batsmen!
Wouldn't you say?
Well, yes, but that basically means
the West Indies middle order will
also get some batting practice today.
Kapil to Greenidge.
West Indies get off the mark.
That's a great shot.
And it's a boundary!
Sandhu to Greenidge.
Smashing cover drive for 4!
Yashpal throws the ball
from the covers. It's a direct hit.
And Haynes is out.
That's an important wicket for India.
And in walks probably the greatest
batsman in the world today, Richards.
Kapil to Viv.
Madan Lal stops it at short square leg
and it's just a single.
That's a brilliant square cut by Viv.
Richards is making this look too easy.
Rain, gentlemen.
Ballu, tell him you'll deal
with him tomorrow.
Drop it! Why make trouble?
Tell him.
He won't forget it when he faces
your bowling.
He'll be shit scared.
Scared? Madipaa, he's Viv Richards!
He whacks so hard.
Even the ball gets terrified.
- Scared? As if!
- So what if he's Viv Richards?
Remember what Kaps said?
Don't be scared. Just tell him.
Go on!
Hey, listen.
What do I say?
"I'll deal with you tomorrow."
See you tomorrow!
Yeah, man.
- You're mine.
- Careful what you ask for, man.
Now drop it!
Want to sing him
a lullaby?
Well, that's what you call luck.
Saved by the rain.
It looked like Viv Richards
was single-handedly
going to take that game away
from the Indians.
The game resumes tomorrow.
Let's see what happens.
The match is starting.
Second day of play.
Richards on strike
and Roger Binny to begin
India's bowling attack.
Let's see what Viv does today.
Binny running in on this overcast day.
Kirmani catches it and
Viv Richards is out for 17.
Richards is back in the pavilion.
Didn't I tell you, Ballu?
Hey, you!
Get back to work.
You had the day off yesterday!
Go on.
Madan Lal bowls out Bacchus.
What a brilliant delivery!
Binny to Dujon and he's caught
by Sandhu.
West Indies struggling at 107/5.
Shastri to Gomes.
Batsman are going for the second.
Sandhu gets the ball.
And that's a brilliant run out.
This is unbelievable.
The mighty West Indies are crumbling.
The champions are
in trouble at 157/9.
Big Bird Joel Garner is the last man in,
but 106 runs are still needed to win.
That's a big 6 over mid-wicket.
This is the same Andy Roberts who, in 1975,
together with Deryck Murray
added 64 runs for a 10th wicket
partnership.
They made their team win.
Looks like Andy Roberts
and Joel Garner
intend to perform the
same miracle today.
The West Indies need only
34 runs to win.
Kaps, get Shastri back.
They can't play slow spin.
Shastri has been called back.
That could be a big risk.
The game is at a crucial point.
The West Indies need 34 runs
off 36 balls.
India has done the unthinkable.
They've defeated the unbeatable.
The invincible West Indies!
I was away working for 12 years.
I returned with a ring.
India has won!
It's time to dance and sing.
Will Kaps get angry with us?
Tomorrow we're playing a match.
How will he find out?
He must've had his milk
and gone to sleep.
Let's go!
Tomorrow's a match day.
Fix your hair.
Where to, gang?
We've won the first World Cup match.
Why not celebrate?
- You coming?
- No, sir.
I'm captain in the day.
Patla is the night Captain.
They aren't as experienced
as you are on fast pitches.
Put your helmet on.
If I see someone yawning tomorrow,
they've had it.
Kirti, you trouble-maker!
Where are you going, Kaps?
The ball has stained my trousers.
It look bad.
- I'm taking it to the laundry.
- Has your family sent you money?
We get only £15 a day.
Laundry will cost you about £12.
Buy a new pair of trousers
instead.
- So?
- Wash them yourself.
I haven't even washed a hanky
in my life.
Nor have you wiped out the
West Indies team!
There's a first for everything.
Being young is a carefree time
We're ready to falter and fall
This no age anyway
To be all grown up
Crazy thoughts flood all our hearts
Let's cross all boundaries
This no age anyway
To be all grown up
Jimpa, I managed it in £1.
Cricket teaches you many things.
Why lose out on fun?
For fear of the others
So what if the world disapproves?
So be it
Let us go a little wild
Why be all serious now?
We'll follow our hearts
And do what it says
Let us go a little wild
Why be all serious now?
We'll follow our hearts
And do what it says
Let us go a little wild
Why be all serious now?
No authority scares us
What's there to fear?
And the man of the match, Madan Lal.
India wins rather comfortably,
with 5 wickets and 23 overs to spare.
With two back-to-back wins,
India now on top of Group B.
Let us go a little wild
Why be all serious now?
We'll follow our hearts
Cheeka!
Congrats.
Hey!
What's there to fear?
I've never seen so many people.
Man Singh, Kapil! Fantastic!
- Hello, Wankhede sir.
- You won two matches!
Mishra-ji, write a headline story
on the team.
Sure, sir.
They've won two matches.
Even if they had to return to
India tomorrow, it's OK.
No one's going anywhere.
You're booked to leave
on the 25th, right?
Yes.
What'll he do here till then?
Does Kapil want to watch the Finals?
He intends to play in the Finals.
I'm off.
"Play in the Finals!"
If we changed our tickets
from June 25th,
must we pay a cancellation fee?
Why would you care if we stayed
till the 25th?
Just tell me about
the cancellation charges.
How much? Really!
Then don't change the booking.
I was only asking to pass time.
And I can say this specially after
the fall of the first few wickets.
In the other match today at Leeds,
West Indies beat Australia by 101 runs.
An aggressive comeback after
their humiliating defeat to India.
Brother.
Free dinner?
Let's go.
Ma'am, this is Kapil - Kapsy.
Jimmy, our Vice-Captain.
This is Mr and Mrs Natrajan
from Madurai.
And their daughter, Kalyani.
- She cooks very well, they say.
- That's nice.
Shall we eat?
It's delicious.
The dosas are very good. Did you mix
the batter yourself?
No, we get it from India.
I've had five dosas already.
Please don't count.
This is also like your house only.
Kalyani enjoys cooking very much.
Really nice.
You've won two World Cup matches.
Now you should marry.
She says you've won two matches,
so you should settle down.
Cheeka is well settled.
He got married to a lovely girl
in March.
Didn't you tell them?
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Did you have to tell them the truth
like Raja Harishchandra?
A few more dosas would've been nice.
- You rascal! Shall I tell Vidya?
- Kapsy!
It's hard finding a vegetarian
South Indian family.
You can find Punjabis everywhere.
South Indian families are rare.
A wife fills the heart.
Food fills the belly.
You can't mix the two.
The end of my dosas.
He missed out on dessert,
that's why he's mad.
- Hello.
- How are you?
Simran...
Sat Sri Akal.
Say hello from me.
She says hello.
Hello-ji, sister-in-law.
We won't tell you about Julie.
Simran, I'll call you
from the lobby.
- These idiots are teasing me.
- Wait. Who's Julie?
There is no Julie.
He was just kidding.
Let me call you from the lobby.
OK?
Do you want my engagement
to be called off?
Now she won't get Julie
out of her mind.
Julie, I love you!
Julie speaking.
Lala-ji!
Who is Julie?
No, not Julie. I said July.
Lala-ji, all the boys were sitting here.
They want a short holiday
before going home.
So, we'll be back in July not June.
Everything's fine.
Do you want to talk to Jimmy?
He isn't picking up?
One minute.
Yes.
He was right here.
Jimmy!
He must be somewhere in the hotel lobby.
No, Lala-ji. No way.
He never goes out at night.
He's not here.
He's gone to sleep, Lala-ji.
Should I wake him up?
Hello. Papa.
What happened?
Go, look for Jimmy.
- Here he is.
- Jimpa, where were you?
Why?
- Lala-ji called.
- You should've said I was asleep.
- He told me to wake you up.
- Then?
Then I imitated your voice, but...
But what?
Lala-ji said:
"Kirti, I'm not just Jimmy's father
but your father too."
I hung up.
Must be Lala-ji.
I'm in trouble, thanks
to your free dosas.
I warned you.
Don't get trapped by free food.
- The dosas have cost you heavily.
- Yash, shut up.
What else did Lala-ji say?
- Just keep batting.
- He must've said something else.
Watching you is hurting my muscles.
Go easy!
Look at this photographer!
I'm the Man of the Match
and he's photographing you.
It's simple, brother.
Whoever pops the champagne cork
gets photographed.
They need action too.
Oh, I look handsome.
Captain, we've won two matches.
Sure we're not overconfident?
Kapil Dev.
Oh, fast bowler!
You won two matches.
I made a flag for your next match.
It's a beautiful.
Still undefeated, India arrives at
Trent Bridge to face Australia.
Sunil Gavaskar is apparently injured
and has been left out.
Can this cost them the match?
Kapil Dev strikes early.
Australia are 11/1.
What a shot by Chappell!
A smashing boundary.
Chappell displaying a tremendous
array of strokes.
That's been dropped.
Chappell given a life by Roger Binny.
This could be costly.
And how Chappell is punishing the
Indians for that missed opportunity.
Catch it.
The Captain clearly looks frustrated
at his players.
Too many missed opportunities.
Too many.
Well, I hate to say this, but the
Indians look like amateurs today.
Chappell has destroyed
the Indian bowling.
He hits a well deserved century.
And Australia are in a commanding
position at lunch.
Walking many nights towards
a dawn
This is not the dawn of our dreams
After some dismal
fielding from India,
Kapil Dev is taking the
bowling attack to Australia.
Great bowling, skipper.
Congratulations on the fifer.
What's wrong, Kaps?
The match isn't over yet.
You know he's pulled his
hamstring, but he's trying.
I expect more from Roger.
He better than that.
Kaps, the game is getting tough.
- We will not lose easily.
- We must win, Jimpa.
Walking many nights towards
a dawn
This is not the dawn of our dreams
The road ahead seems without end
Sorry, Jimpa.
Without Gavaskar, India's task of
chasing 321 is going to be a difficult one.
It shall not dampen our spirits
It shall rise again
This spirit of ours
Kapil is the only one with 5 wickets
and a 40 off 27 balls to his name.
The Captain did lead by example, but
India eventually loses by 162 runs.
A huge, huge crushing defeat!
Kapil, a true Captain's
innings today.
So what? We still lost
the match, Maan.
320 runs! We were hammered.
It looked like we hardly played.
If you accept defeat early
then how will you fight?
If anyone is injured,
Wally will take his place.
How is leg?
Better.
Sunny, it high time you get run.
Cheeka, you have to control anger.
All the time playing rash shot.
Not require.
What about the fielding?
Sunny Bhai!
Don't, Maan Bhai.
I don't understand why he's talking
to his team in English?
Do you know,
Kapil thinks in Punjabi
then translates it into English.
What he meant was - how long will
runs hide from you?
You're going to score,
come what may.
His English is all wrong
but his sentiment is right.
He's right.
I must score.
Not for my own sake,
but for the sake of the team.
Yes.
Kapil is the team's heart,
you are the team's balance.
They can't do without you.
He knows that too.
Anyway, I won't be able
to play tomorrow.
We need you tomorrow.
You're the only one the West
Indies bowlers are scared of.
My foot's still swollen.
- Yes, but...
- Sorry.
India is going to play the defeated
West Indies again.
Gavaskar has proven he's the greatest
threat to the West Indies so far.
Kapil Dev is making a major error
by dropping him now.
Skipper, my hamstring is feeling
much better now.
Let me bowl.
OK, Humphrey. You bowl today.
Let's be clear about this.
The West Indies want revenge.
You can see it in their eyes.
After their great upset in the
first match of the World Cup,
the West Indies want to prove that
they're the greatest team in the world.
The manner in which they demolished
the Australians in their second match
is enough to put a chill down
the spine of any team.
Greenidge caught at first slip
off Kapil Dev.
The West Indies are 17/1. Looks like the
Indians have come ready for battle.
Here comes the best batsman
in the world, Richards.
That should be a four.
No! Stopped by Binny.
Stopped a certain boundary there.
Looks like Richards has
chosen this match
for the team's march towards
another World Cup Final.
A masterclass by the two greats of
International cricket.
Clive Lloyd and Viv Richards.
That's a big one! I've not seen
a ball hit so far in a long time.
It lands straight on the roof
of the pavilion.
West Indies at a massive 282.
Sunny seemed fit when I saw him
walk in the nets.
Do you think he
really has been rested?
The best of players go through
a bad patch.
And I'm sure he'll be back.
I know him. He's a great player.
Yes, but this is the West Indies
that they're facing.
And who knows them better
than Sunny Gavaskar.
Come on, Andy.
Andy Roberts running in to bowl.
And that delivery almost took
Srikkanth's head off.
Srikkanth slashes
and he's caught behind.
India lose an early wicket.
Where you going, boss?
The pavilion's over there.
Mohinder Amarnath, the next man in.
And that's another one. A big one.
India have lost both their openers
in the first 10 overs.
Fiery Andy, Fiery!
That one hit Vengsarkar
right in the ribs.
This looks like a battlefield,
rather than a game of cricket.
India rebuilding quite well.
Indians thrilled by this 50-run
partnership between Jimmy and Dilip.
That was a fast one from
Malcolm Marshall.
Good stuff, Maco.
Lots of fire, buddy.
Don't worry about it, man.
Sunny knows about me.
You'll soon find out too.
Good shot, Dilip.
They say he's the new Gavaskar.
Give him some respect, Maco.
Dilip standing up to one of the fastest
most hostile overs seen in the World Cup.
Ball after ball after ball of
hostile short-paced bowling.
Dilip Vengsarkar simply could not
avoid that one.
He's wincing in pain on the ground.
Dilip was getting on top
of the West Indian bowling.
This is not the same Indian team
that landed in England,
and this is not the same West Indies
team they met a week ago.
A little bit faster, sir.
Marshall not letting up on his pace.
Pulled away for 4 by one of the
best players of pace.
With Jimmy Amarnath
still at the crease,
there's a chance of India
taking up the challenge.
Bowler!
And that brings up the fifty
for Amarnath.
The balls are coming like bullets, but
ever since Dilip Vengsarkar was hit,
Jimmy Amarnath is giving it back
to the West Indian pacers.
Gomes to Patil.
And he's gone, caught
and bowled by Larry Gomes.
India now 130/3.
- Shall we leave?
- Wait. Kapil Dev is coming on.
Kapil joins Jimmy on the field
at the crucial moment in the match.
- Kapil Dev!
All eyes are on the Captain.
The Captain is off
to a flying start.
India reaches 160
with four wickets down.
The Captain and Vice-Captain
put up a brave 50-run partnership.
A valiant innings
of 80 comes to an end.
Battered on the elbow, chest
and even on the face.
Amarnath stood and hooked bravely
at every opportunity for three hours.
Howzat, Umpire?
Roger Binny is out.
Catch it. Yeah!
And what a catch!
Absolutely brilliant.
Kirmani bowled by Marshall
for a duck.
No, no, no.
India all out in the 54th over, falling
short by a huge margin of 66 runs.
West Indies have had their revenge.
Their key batsmen
in hitting form and
their fearsome pace attack
being too much for the Indians.
Today it looked like
a bloody battlefield.
India in deep trouble now,
having lost 2 matches in a row.
Seven stitches.
The doctor said,
Dilip can't play in this World Cup.
So what if the heart is broken
It still beats and quickens
as before
Life runs through our veins
We shall keep our promises
The desire of every heart
Together we shall fulfill
Kapil Dev!
Keep the flag flying
Proudly flying in the wind
Let it fly on high
Proudly wave your country's flag
Keep the flag flying
Proudly flying in the wind
Let it fly on high
Proudly wave your country's flag
Keep the flag flying
Proudly flying in the wind
627, Kirmani, Dilip.
Patla, found your room?
Yeah!
Shall I ask the people in the lobby
to share the room with me?
Why are you making
a scene, Patla?
The wives are coming.
Please manage.
And our girlfriends?
Take them to the garden.
Treat them to ice cream.
Whisper sweet nothings!
Say good night then go back
to your room. OK?
Just listen, Maan.
If you play games at night,
you'll be useless on the field.
So sorry, Kapil.
You have a match tomorrow.
How long were you waiting?
- Three hours.
- Three hours!
Oh God, I'm so sorry.
Why was the flight so late?
You know how it is.
Everything is late in India.
I was reading an article about
a man who applied for a
phone line 18 years ago.
He still hasn't got it.
Just imagine, 18 years for
a phone line. Too much!
- What news back home?
- Everyone's thrilled.
You've won two matches.
And we lost two.
- Aren't you happy?
- Yes, I am.
Come on.
When I was sixteen,
I went to the CCI camp.
We bowled all day
and got two rotis to eat.
I asked them: "What's this?"
I went to complain to the camp head.
His name was Keki Tarapore.
"Sir, I'm a fast bowler,
two rotis aren't enough for me."
He laughed.
"Son, India doesn't have
fast bowlers.
- "Make do with what you get."
- "Sir, I'm not here to make do."
I kept fighting and finally
I was given four rotis.
Four years later when I had taken
100 wickets,
I went to the CCI and thanked
Mr Tarapore and said:
"Because of you, there are
fast bowlers in India now."
Rom, if people say:
"This Indian team is useless."
It makes no difference.
I'll give my answer on the pitch.
But when they say:
"Kapil, you've done enough."
It makes me furious.
If "enough" makes them happy,
then wait 18 years for a phone.
I'm not here to do "enough".
When people talk like that,
I want to smash their faces.
Hello!
Tomorrow's a big match.
It's a do and die.
- What's wrong?
- You mean "Do or die"?
Whatever!
Smash what you want there.
The BBC are not
showing this match.
Do you think that's reflection
of the fact
we're not going to see
anything exciting today, Farokh?
Well, it's a crucial match for India.
We find ourselves in a must win situation.
India must be still recovering
from the double thrashing
they received from the West Indies
and Australia.
If they win today by a huge margin,
they're still in the tournament.
If not, so long!
- I'm fifth down.
- Happy journey India!
Play well so I don't need to bat.
I'll shower now. I'll see you
at fielding.
- Must you make us late?
- The boys take time to come.
We don't need them.
We're not going to war.
We will miss the Indian batting.
Gavaskar at the crease. It's good
to see the Little Master back.
Rawson coming in to bowl.
And that hits his pads
and he is gone.
Gavaskar goes for a duck in
the first over of the match.
Catch!
And what a catch!
Srikkanth also goes for a duck.
Kaps!
Kaps, it's two down.
Caught behind. And would you
believe it, India is 6 for 3.
Kaps! Three down. Hurry up!
Sardar, let me shower.
The water's nice and hot today.
We're being hammered and Kaps
is happy about the hot water.
Kaps!
Curran to Patil.
There is an appeal.
And he's given him.
I cannot believe what's happening
here on this ground.
Kaps! We're four down!
I swear. Please, hurry.
Nonsense. Just shut up!
What do you mean "shut up?"
It's an important match.
Stop clowning.
Don't take a joke too far.
- What's the score?
- 9 runs.
Four wickets down.
Wickets are falling one by one.
Didn't I tell you?
The boy hasn't got it.
Captain change.
- Let the match be over.
- It's over.
Match is over. World Cup over.
Captain over.
Another wicket down,
we're not going.
No point.
We're waiting for the Captain
to enter.
India struggling at 9/4.
The Captain is rushing out.
It looks like he wasn't prepared
to come out so soon.
However, it's a moist wicket
and it's windy.
And there's immense sideways
movement on this green top.
Brother, what's going on?
Who knows! They're coming,
they're going.
The ball is swinging.
Play carefully.
Good morning, Sri.
What's wrong?
Another big wicket for Zimbabwe.
Yashpal departs for 9. The ball
is moving all over the place.
India now 17/5.
Let's go home.
Amateurs have been sent here
to play cricket. They've messed up.
It's hard to imagine how a side
that finds itself at 17/5
in 13 overs
can ever recover in a match
that will determine their chances
of continuing in this World Cup.
Wankhede sir.
17 for 5.
Roger, just stay there.
Don't give wicket.
OK, Skipper.
This is getting over soon.
- Let's keep the taxi waiting.
- Yes.
I'll just be back.
Keep the meter running.
OK.
Traicos to Binny.
That's a beautiful straight drive.
And that should be 4 runs.
Shot! Beats the fielder.
Four runs.
That's a beautiful shot
by Roger Binny.
Looks like India is finally
creeping back into this game.
Did you speak too soon, Farokh?
That's the sixth wicket
down for just 77.
Shastri mistimes a slower ball.
And is caught at mid-off.
That's the seventh
one gone for just 78.
This is truly a disaster
unfolding here.
Doesn't look like India
is getting past the 100 mark.
You're free to go to the hotel.
See you there.
We're not going anywhere.
We're staying.
Madipaa,
just hold on to your wicket.
I'll look after the score.
Don't worry, Kaps.
I'll stay put.
Contrasting emotions here.
Zimbabwe fans enjoying
a beautiful afternoon
while the Indians are miserable
with their team's performance.
Nice shot by Kapil.
Curran to Kapil.
Another boundary.
If we make 100 runs we'll save face.
What a hit that is from the Captain!
He's hit a sixer!
Looks like that hit has woken up
the Indian players
from their slumber
in the dressing room.
There's hope while
he's still out there.
And Madan Lal sweeps that for four.
Curran to Kapil
and another boundary.
Turn around.
Kapil hitting the ball all around
the park now.
At lunch Kapil and Madan Lal have
given some semblance of an innings.
36 overs down, Kapil is at 50.
But India are at 124/7 and
still in serious trouble.
If we make a 150-runs.
We'll go with respect.
We're not going anywhere, Ballu.
What happen, happen!
We still have 24 overs.
We fight till end.
Bring the sword out, Yash.
The sword?
Mongoose bat!
...couple of early wickets.
He's got the mongoose.
Kapil brings out the mongoose bat.
Better batting conditions post lunch,
encouraging him to counter-attack.
He puts that bat to good use.
Curran bowls again. Kapil hits a
second boundary of the over
and Curran looking
a little frustrated.
Kapil unleashing a furious assault
on the bowlers.
Good, Kapsi. Come on, Kapsi!
And Madan Lal's caught behind.
A 62 run partnership that
stabilized India comes to an end.
The Indian score still
precariously placed at 140/8.
Who moved?
- To pee.
- Don't move.
We'll get them before we're down.
They can't get rid of us.
Listen, everyone.
Till Kapil is batting,
no one moves.
- Pee...
- Statue-like.
You hit. I'm right here.
Try getting me out.
Just try it.
- Romi.
- No one move.
Kirmani off to a strong start.
That's a boundary.
I'm right here too, Kapsi.
And the onslaught continues.
That's mistimed and it's a six.
You're just a bloody slogger!
Seems to be an exchange of words
between Kapil and Kevin.
That's another big one.
It's a straight hit over the wicket.
Oh, bloody hell!
And that was a straight six.
Right into the commentator's box.
India now 164 for 8.
The Indian fans delighted
by Kapil's century.
Who would have believed, under
the circumstances?
A first for an Indian
in a limited overs match.
If we make 175 runs.
We'll manage it.
What did you say?
First it was 100 then 150
and now 175?
Is there no end to your demands?
Fix a target score and get them
to play accordingly.
- He's shooting off his mouth.
- OK, 200.
Bloody hell! That's my car.
Kapil has crossed 150.
An unbelievable knock.
I think the spectators
need helmets now.
No one move. I'll be back
in a minute.
I can't control it anymore.
It's your responsibility
if it goes wrong.
- Why?
- Agree?
- No.
- So, wait.
- Are you going to wet your pants?
- Just about. Get lost!
Gentlemen, what's the world record?
Good shot, Kapil! Good shot!
171 by Glenn Turner.
Ladies and gentlemen, we're about
to see a world record being broken.
You've been hitting sixers.
How come they're clapping
for a single?
Who knows!
Ask the Umpire.
What happen?
What happened?
You just broke the
bloody World Record!
Congratulations!
- Come on, Kapil!
- Congratulations!
You're a true freedom fighter.
He walked in when India were just
9 runs for 4 wickets.
He faced 138 balls, 16 boundaries
and 6 sixes.
He took India to 266 for 8,
and he himself finished with
an historic 175, not out.
Today we saw undoubtedly
one of the greatest knocks in the
history of this beautiful game.
Pain keeps telling your strong arms
If you stop now, you're in trouble
Pain keeps telling you
You can will defeat away
You're no ordinary man
You could never pass by unnoticed
There is no one like you
This field is all yours,
power is in your hands
Don't stop now
Don't bow down now
Don't let tiredness overcome you
Never give up, never give up
Don't cower down
Don't hide your strength
Don't let it falter
Never give up, never give up
What a shame the BBC
was on strike today.
The innings Kapil Dev played
today would have been a lesson
for generations to come.
Some events wipe out all
differences and unite hearts.
Today we witnessed such an
event at Tunbridge Wells.
Your country of origin did
not matter nor your age.
Because everyone who was there
witnessed history in the making.
Today a player brought victory
to his team single-handedly
and made many millions of Indians
proudly hold their heads up high.
£300.
- Yes, governor.
- It was worth it!
Kuku has broken a World Record!
That's why I say you should
drink milk. Yes!
You keep asking why, mister.
I didn't know we would play so well.
We can make it to the semis now.
Must they start playing badly?
If India loses face,
so will you, right?
Stop talking!
Tell me how much extra
for the flight?
How am I going to find
that much money?
You should know which way
your ball will swing.
Bravo, Ballu! You hid your
inswinger this time.
Come on. One more.
What was that? In or out?
I fought to have you and Ballu
on our team,
not for you to let the wind
and the pitch do it all.
When you your potential realise?
Say it softly.
He'll feel bad.
He's playing well.
He could play just as well
in his sleep, Maan.
We must make it to the semis.
Just playing so-so won't do.
You must outdo yourselves
in every match.
All of us must.
Come on.
- Aren't you ready?
- No.
- Kapil is just...
- I said: "No, Ballu."
- It's the High Commissioner's party.
- Not interested.
Why, Brit? Are you scared we'll
force you to sing the National Anthem?
Don't worry. I'll teach you
the words.
Just knowing the National Anthem
doesn't mean a thing
if it doesn't swell your
bloody chest every time it's sung!
No one should make fun of Roger
about the National Anthem.
- What's wrong?
- He's sulking.
- What did he say?
- Many things.
- Something about the National Anthem.
- But what did he say?
He said: "Bloody chest swelling."
I can't repeat his words with
as much feeling.
He moved me.
Congratulations.
What an achievement! Really!
Thank you so much.
Kapil, Romi, Man Singh,
meet David Frith.
A very senior journalist.
Congratulations, Kapil,
on the World Record.
It's a pity I couldn't watch it.
You should've. It was glorious.
Ah, yes.
But you see that day was also
the clash of the giants at Lord's.
West Indies vs Australia.
Now you wouldn't miss that
match for anything. Would you?
I would!
It's not every day you get to see
a World Record now, do you?
No, not at all.
I'm sure you're proud of him.
You've done a rather
splendid job, Kapil.
I'm sure you'll go back
a happy man now.
Hello, Mr. Frith.
We've read your article.
No, Kapil?
Myself Srikkanth.
And my beautiful wife, Vidhya.
Come here.
She's shy. We got married just before
the World Cup.
Congratulations, my dear.
You know, just after our marriage,
a phone call came.
We've been selected for
the 1983 World Cup they said.
I thought: "Very good."
So, we booked our tickets.
Bombay to New York.
A stopover in London.
With me in this plan...
Sandy was there.
Roger. Where is Roger?
Kirti, Kirmani, Shastri.
We were all going for
a holiday to the US.
We thought we'd play the World Cup
matches on the way.
Then we'd go on our honeymoon.
That was the plan.
Why are you embarrassed?
You were all there
in the plan, no?
Maan Bhai, you were
also there in the plan.
You must understand one thing.
We have never won any match
in any World Cup.
Before 1983, we beat only
one team - East Africa.
First of all, there is no country
called East Africa.
You all know that.
It's basically a bunch
of Gujaratis put together,
the Patels and their brothers.
They just formed a team.
And that's the only team we beat.
So now, in 1983, we come here
and our Captain says we'll beat
the West Indies.
We thought our Captain
had lost his mind.
Who is in the team?
Opening - Gordon Greenidge,
Desmond Haynes.
Number 3. Viv Richards,
Clive Lloyd.
And the 4 fast bowlers,
whose names none of us want
to remember for the rest of our lives.
And Dilip! He definitely
doesn't want to remember.
And our mad Captain
says we'll win this match.
I tell you the Captain has gone mad!
But Mr Frith,
he was serious.
And that day we defeated your
"giant" West Indies.
I don't think our mad Captain
is going to go back happy with just...
"a rather splendid job."
That he's done till now.
He'll be only happy when he's holding
the World Cup in his hands.
Nothing less will do!
Nothing less.
Like people say:
"Taste success once...
"tongue wants more!"
Kapsi! To our mad Captain.
- To the World Cup!
Racing to the front
leaving everyone behind
With our heads held high
We enter the field,
proud in our uniforms
Now that we are here,
we shall prove our talent
We shall show our strength
The strength of passion.
The fire of determination
The world will learn from us
We will win, we will win
India will win
A prayer in every heart
The belief of millions
We shall win, win we shall
India shall win
Fulfilling all our promises
India wins by a huge margin
of 118 runs.
Roger Binny has broken the back of the
Australians by taking 4 crucial wickets.
For my team.
India go to the semi-finals and
Roger Binny is the Man of the Match.
For my Captain.
Thank you.
Twenty wounded.
Four killed in Nawabpur.
Communal violence continues.
How will it end?
Madam!
We've reached the semi-finals
in the World Cup!
There's communal rioting in India
and you're talking about cricket?
Sports are above religious
differences.
Madam, what has cricket
to do with all this?
Did you know India
is in the semi-finals?
Yes, Madam.
- Does everyone know?
- Yes, Madam.
- Everyone knows. They're very happy.
- Why?
Madam, no one believed
it could happen.
Everyone hoped it would.
It's a different story
in the big cities,
- but in small towns like Nawabpur?
- Why not?
Don't they understand cricket?
Make this World Cup into a festival.
Get all India watching it on TV.
The World Cup games
must obsess all of India.
Will India win the semi-final?
Will India win the World Cup?
Make sure every home in Nawabpur
can watch the matches live.
Eight different countries have been
playing in the World Cup.
The Indian cricket team has made
history by making it to the semi-finals.
The match will take place
at Old Trafford in Manchester.
The semi-finals will be played between
India and England.
You can watch the match
on Doordarshan across the country.
Grandpa, did you hear?
The monkeys have broken the antenna.
We'll miss the match.
- We'll get it repaired tomorrow.
- Tomorrow?
There's rioting in the town,
and you want to watch a match?
No one goes out.
- Your grandfather?
- Yes, sir.
How did it happen?
Heart attack. Massive.
Morning walking and dead!
That's terrible.
Tomorrow is funeral.
- In Manchester.
- Manchester?
Yes, sir.
All right. Go on then.
You're a troublemaker.
Namaste, sister-in-law.
I was telling you about Julie...
Simran has broken off
the engagement.
What?
Her brother called.
He said my house is too small,
and I couldn't afford to keep
Simran happy on my salary.
He's right.
We don't earn half as much as
doctors or engineers.
Why would anyone want
their daughter to marry a cricketer?
Hey, Kapil...
Have you read this?
They say it's a fluke.
I don't know what the word means.
'Fluke' means it's pure luck
that we won.
Kapil, you must say
something about this.
How?
When I speak English at the
team meetings, you laugh.
You keep catching me out.
So, if I said anything to them,
it'd bounce off their heads.
No, Kapsi, it's not funny.
We won our way here.
We didn't get to the semi-finals
because of a quota.
What this article deserves
is what I'm doing.
You must make a statement, Captain.
Let's play cricket instead.
I feel like smashing their faces in.
Aren't you furious?
Madipaa.
Why are the West Indies
champions today?
In 1975 when Tony Greg
was England's Captain,
remember what he said about
the West Indies?
"We'll rub their faces in the mud.
"Make them grovel."
The West Indies didn't react.
They just went ahead and won
the World Cup twice.
The way we'll play will be
our answer.
"Where we come from."
"We are the England."
You know what happened the last time the
an Englishman said: "We'll make them grovel."
You created the West Indies
killing machine.
Well, I'll take my chances and
say the same again.
With people half the height,
a third of the pace
and a quarter of the ability.
And remember the history,
in limited overs cricket,
India has never beaten England
in England.
Maybe this time India
wants to rewrite history.
"Where we come from."
"We are the England."
Sandhu being punished
by the English batsman.
50 up. A promising start indeed
for England.
- Give Ballu a rest.
- What's wrong?
His engagement was
called off last night.
What?
Come! Come.
Binny to Tavaré. Azad tries to
stop it, but it's a boundary.
Has it come?
No.
Madan Lal gets hit
for a beautiful cover drive.
- Has it come?
- No.
And that brings up the 100
for England
in the 25th over for the loss
of just two wickets.
The Indians really need to try and
contain the English batsman now.
And now?
There's a change of bowler.
The signal is back.
Will Jimmy stop the English batsman?
Out!
Jimmy has played just the way
the Captain had hoped.
The wicket that India desperately needed.
Spectacular bowling!
Kirti Azad brought into the attack.
A sweep shot by Lamb.
That's a direct hit!
Very, very quick thinking and a fine
piece of cricket by Yashpal Sharma.
A very important wicket for India to get.
Jimmy to Gatting, and that's clean bowled.
A second wicket for Jimmy Amarnath.
Oh! That's got him.
That ball was kept really low
and Botham is gone for 6.
The ball hit the stump less than a foot high.
Poor Botham was left high and dry.
England in real trouble now.
160 for 6.
The jubilant Indian crowd has
invaded the pitch.
The situation for England
has become critical.
Amarnath and Azad are choking off
England's supply of runs.
Mind the pitch!
Jimmy, they're spoiling the pitch.
Kirti, the ball spins or is low.
How did you manage both?
Kaps, at release time
I held the ball like this
and I...
Kaps, sorry.
It's a trade secret.
I learnt it for the World Cup.
Well bowled, Kirti!
Kirti, tell me how you did it.
I couldn't admit to Kaps
that I didn't have a clue!
- What?
- What is it?
Bowled Botham out. I earned £50.
What more could I want!
Kapil Dev back into the attack.
And he's clean bowled.
Kapil to Allott.
He mistimes that and Patil
catches it at short third man.
Willis's leg stump goes over.
He goes for nought, and England
are dismissed for a score of 213.
Kapil gets his 3rd wicket
from the last ball of the 60th over.
Great recovery from India after a
solid start from the English batsmen.
The wicket was conducive
to Indian bowlers.
Round one had a similar wicket
that helped Kapil's team
defeat the West Indies.
What's the score?
England 213. All out.
England all out!
Patla, you go four down today.
I'll go after you.
What's wrong?
STD.
- What?
- I've got STD.
I warned you guys.
- Don't do it with everyone.
- Pass the soda.
Soda?
That doesn't cure STD.
It'll help me burp.
How can that fix STD?
It works for me.
Patla, "acidity!"
Give him a soda, he'll be okay.
That's what I told you.
What did you think?
I thought you had an STD.
That's what I said.
'Acidity.'
Hey, Dhadpadango!
Mind where you're going.
Fancy yourself an ace batsman.
- Calm down! Have a soda.
- All he does is smoke and hit.
Willis to Gavaskar.
Flicks it off his pads
for a boundary.
Srikkanth uses the pace of the bowler
to beat a third man for a boundary.
Four handsome runs by Sunil Gavaskar.
Belligerent blow by this
smashing stroke maker.
The Little Master is in form.
It's a solid start to the Indian
innings by Gavaskar and Srikkanth.
46 for no loss.
That's the wicket
England wanted badly.
No opposing team is comfortable as long
as Gavaskar is still at the crease.
Pulled away for a four.
Srikkanth on 19,
building his innings well.
Catch it!
Srikkanth is out.
Both openers gone in consecutive overs.
Cheeka is always so careless.
India at 50/2.
Marks now, coming in from
a different end.
Hit firmly to mid-on.
Going for a single.
Out comes the stump.
Did Sharma make it?
The Umpire, David Evans, is in a
perfect position to make that call.
Not out says the Umpire.
Sorry, STD.
Yash, we have a lot of overs left.
Don't take any risks.
OK.
I'll hit. Save your wicket.
- OK, Jimpa.
- Bravo! Be strong.
Amarnath comes down the pitch.
It's a six.
That's 100 for India.
That's more like it.
Good shot, Yash.
Careful. We both can't risk it.
OK, Jimpa.
No problem.
He's play that on side.
The fielder giving it chase.
Unsuccessfully.
Willis comes in for his second spell.
Yash.
That's a magnificent shot.
Yashpal has made room for himself
and put it on its way for a
magnificent game changing six.
Great shot! But why take risks?
Jimpa, you don't know.
He insulted me in the Madras match.
I won't spare him.
You'll take your Madras revenge
in Manchester?
Brother, it's the semi-finals.
Stay calm.
OK, big brother.
You say OK, OK. But you do
as you please.
Easy.
Yashpal has flicked it towards
deep square leg.
He takes a single
- and is trying for a second run.
- Why take the second run?
And he's out!
"Where we come from."
"We are the England."
You idiot!
Amarnath returns, making 46 runs.
A crucial wicket.
India at 142 for 3.
Yash, hang in there for 60 overs.
- I'll hit now.
- OK, Patla.
That's a four.
And that's an excellent 50
for Yashpal Sharma.
Another half century for Sharma
in this tournament.
Shall I hit? Or will you?
Tell you what, we'll hit together.
Not a bad idea!
Patil showcasing his big hits.
Sharma continues the onslaught
at the other end
to the delight of the Indian fans.
Patil is seriously punishing
the English bowlers.
Madipaa, let the match be over.
You guys always get the bottle first.
Today it's my turn.
Patil has hit it for a four.
The score is now 200.
Indian fans are delighted!
Patil's entrance has
changed the game again.
He has once again punished Willis,
just like he did last year.
Wasn't that Kulwant just there?
No, sir, no Kulwant.
It's in the air.
Allott is getting under it.
And it's...it's a marvellous catch.
Madipaa!
Yashpal Sharma walks back.
He's been the pillar of the Indian innings
India now 205 for 4 as the
Captain walks in.
Three runs needed for
India to reach the Finals.
Plays it into the covers.
That's one, they take another.
Oh no! There's been an invasion.
A premature invasion on the field.
Indian fans celebrating
a bit too early.
Willis waiting for the field
to be cleared.
This might just be the last ball
of the match.
Fellows move over.
Willis asking for a most
unorthodox field.
He has asked all his players
to move to the off side.
So that they can escape
if there is another invasion.
And that's it. It's off the edge
and it goes for a four.
India is through
to the Finals
of the 1983 World Cup.
India is now through to the Finals.
What a historic day for Indian cricket.
For my father.
Hey, you bloody Pakis!
Stop playing that stupid
drum and bugger off!
Shall we go?
Why should we?
We won the match
and we can't celebrate.
- Didn't you hear what he said?
- Play, Jassi.
- Bugger off!
Piss off!
Never mind!
Kapil will fix them in the Finals.
Yes, Papa.
Lala-ji?
What did he say?
He said: "My son,
today you have made me feel
ten years younger."
Don't tell anyone I'm crying.
There's a message from
forward post for you, sir.
Sir, the soldiers want to hear
the latest score of the Finals
- every ten minutes.
- How do I do that?
The moment the match starts,
the Pakistani Major Sadiq
will start firing.
Do they ever let us hear
the commentary?
They fire at us whenever
there's a big match on.
World Cup TV fund.
Sir, sir!
World Cup TV fund, sir.
You want a TV?
But we have a radio in the hostel.
A TV is a must, sir.
Radio or TV,
it's the same thing.
Sir, take my cycle.
Give me your car.
- Same thing, sir!
- Get lost.
Good news! If we win,
each player gets 25,000.
You crazy?
You'll give us 25,000?
The Cricket Board will.
I just heard it.
Ever seen 25,000?
It's probably for the whole team.
How much?
25,000, Roger! Just imagine.
Our Sunny, Gavaskar.
He used to play cricket here.
He's broken our windows
so many times.
But I always returned the ball
to him.
Children must be encouraged.
Oh God! There goes our window.
You fool. Do you think
you're Sunil Gavaskar?
- How many more tickets?
- At least four more.
I want four tickets too.
You're driving me crazy.
I don't have any tickets
for the Finals.
Don't talk about a ticket
ever again.
Now hang up!
What the hell do you want?
Do you have any hot water
in your bathroom?
- Is there any hot water?
- Yes.
Madi, you shower here.
I'll wait downstairs.
He wants to shower.
Yes, it'll be done.
I'll talk to him.
Thank you, bye.
Kapil, we need more tickets.
They've all arrived.
- I gave you the four tickets I had.
- I need some more.
- Hello?
- What "hello?" You "hello."
Want me to print them myself?
Come!
Hi, Romi.
Kaps, my boss is arriving tomorrow
from Nirlon. I need some passes.
- How many?
- Two or three.
OK, Sunny. You'll get them.
- See you.
- Bye.
- Let me concentrate on the match.
- At least get their rooms organised.
Tell you what.
They can sleep here.
I'll sleep in the bathroom.
I say before, we here to win.
One question at a time.
This was your dream.
It's every cricketer's dream.
Lord's.
India has never won a single match
in this stadium.
India has never made it
to the World Cup Finals either.
Are you scared?
Very.
Kapil Dev is all grown up.
He's India's cricket Captain.
He's broken a World Record
and even reached the Finals.
Behind this Kapil Dev
is a small kid, Kuku.
A kid who played because
he loved playing cricket.
Play for that boy today.
Sir, Pakistan's Major Sadiq
is on the hotline.
The hotline? Now what?
Yes, Major Sadiq?
Yes. Thank you.
He said we can enjoy the game.
There won't be any firing today.
Although the English cricket press
had given India no chance of ever
reaching even the semi-finals,
India rose to the occasion and
has surprised the cricketing world
by reaching the World Cup Finals
here at Lord's.
But of course the favorites
remain the mighty West Indies.
Sir, one ticket?
One ticket, sir. Give me one ticket,
my fair friend.
On this pitch whoever wins the toss
definitely has the upper hand.
The conditions are best for bowling.
I think so too, Johners.
Toss, please.
That's heads, that's tails.
Heads!
Heads it is.
West Indies wins the toss and
choose to bowl first.
Advantage West Indies
on this green top.
Come on, hurry up. Let's go!
They're here!
How's the pitch?
It's a green.
Openers, be cautious.
Specially you, Cheeka.
Don't throw away wicket.
OK, Kapsi.
Openers Sunil Gavaskar and Srikkanth
making their way to the pitch.
All of India is watching
these two players right now.
It's the first time the Indian team
has reached a World Cup Final.
The stadium is packed to the rafters.
The huge crowds have forced
the organisers to extend the stands.
Sachin, hurry up!
The match is starting.
Sunny Gavaskar will face the first ball.
Every Indian is hoping he builds
on the rhythm he found in the semi-finals.
Play.
Hitman Andy Roberts.. tries to play it,
but misses the ball.
A fiery first ball.
A good decision leaving that ball.
Aggressive bowling by Roberts.
A tense start for the Indians.
The opening batsmen have to
play with caution.
Garner to Gavaskar.
Almost catches the outside edge.
Come on! Over here!
The ball rises sharply and
hits Srikkanth on the gloves.
That was too good for him, Bird.
5th over and India has only 2 runs
on the board.
And that's Gavaskar's gone.
Beautifully bowled by Andy Roberts
and he's taken the first Indian wicket.
That's the one they wanted.
Gavaskar, the great Indian batsman
with the score at 2.
So that's first blood
for Clive Lloyd's team.
That brings one of the best players
of pace to the wicket.
Can he take the attack to the Windies?
Jimmy, we love you!
Amarnath pushes the ball
for a quick single.
West Indies keeping it very tight.
Good single.
Garner is unplayable out there
at the moment.
Well done, Bird. Well done!
What happened, man?
Too fast for you?
Cheeka, go easy!
Jimpa, I can't play slow
and don't know technique.
If I had technique,
I'd be Sunil Gavaskar.
I don't know how to play defence.
I only know how to hit.
Go ahead and hit.
- Shall I?
- Hit!
Damn if I do,
damn if I don't.
Now watch me hit.
Srikkanth slashes at another short
pitched delivery
and it flies over the keeper's head.
Looks like Srikkanth has decided
he's been respectable long enough.
What happened, man?
Too fast for you?
Bravo, Cheeka!
Don't know what the batsmen talked about,
but Srikkanth has changed his game.
Indian fans are just loving this.
Amarnath has pulled this towards
deep square leg.
Oh, what a beautiful shot!
That was meant to be
the quicker bouncer,
but Srikkanth was waiting for it
and sent it flying to the boundary.
And again. Beautiful!
This is clearly the shot
of the tournament.
Even the great Vivian Richards
is applauding that shot.
The Indians are loving this.
What a shot!
That's the third time he's smashed
this West Indian pace attack
away to the square leg boundary.
Oh, it's in the air. Logie misses it.
Luck is going India's way.
Almost got him that time.
In the air again.
From the meat of the bat.
Screams away towards the pavilion
for a four.
Quick inswinger from Marshall
hits straight on the pads. It's out!
The second big blow for India.
Short but enterprising innings
comes to an end.
38 runs including a 6 and 7 fours.
Magnificent shot by Amarnath.
Clean bowled. Beautiful ball!
Amarnath is out at 26.
India now 90 for 3
in the 30th over.
Half the match over and the
run rate at just 3 per over.
Gomes to Yashpal. In the air
and caught by the substitute Logie.
Something of a tragedy for India.
Losing two wickets in quick succession.
92 for 4 now.
India in trouble.
And here comes Kapil Dev,
the last remaining hope for India.
Kapil Dev!
Come on, Viv.
Richards to Kapil..
Hits strongly for 4.
Another smash hit from
the Haryana Hurricane!
Kapil knows India needs
to take charge right now.
That's 15 runs from just 8 balls.
For Kapil after Tunbridge Wells
anything is possible when he's around.
Kapil swings at another one
and it's gone high in the air
towards the long on boundary.
Catch it.
Looks like it's going to be a six.
That's a tragedy as far as
India is concerned.
Gomes has picked up the vital wicket
of the Indian Captain.
Roberts to Azad.
Catch it.
Kirti Azad is out without scoring.
India are now 6 down for 111
and in an awful lot of trouble.
Binny goes for two.
This is definitely a big
blow for India. Two quick wickets.
India now sinks deeper
at 130 for 7.
Patil goes down on his knees and
thumps it for 6 at square leg.
3 more runs for Patil.
Every run is vital for India.
Madan Lal has hit that
for a big six.
Catch it.
That's in the air
and that's got to be out.
And yes! Larry Gomes at mid-on
makes no mistake with that one.
Oh, that was a fast one from Marshall.
The West Indies are loving every moment.
Ballu!
That was a bit of their magical
pace they would say.
- India are now 161 for 9.
- Ballu.
Just one wicket left.
Is it all over for India now?
Ballu, no matter what's going on
in our lives
when we walk onto the pitch
in our uniforms
we have only one purpose.
To play for our country
with all our hearts.
Whatever might be happening
for us personally -
no one knows or cares.
But what we achieve
on this ground today
will be linked to our names forever.
This day will never return.
Hammer them.
Ballu, are you all right?
Are you OK?
You don't bowl bouncers
at number ten.
I won't have it.
Wins and losses should show
only on the scoreboard
not in our eyes.
Oh, well struck. Sandhu stands his ground
and hits Marshall towards mid on.
These two putting on
invaluable runs for India.
India now at 183 for 9.
Bowled him...it's all over.
That's the end.
Very gallant batting by the
last two Indian batsmen.
They put on 22 more runs
when it all seemed to be over.
Sandhu remains unbeaten on 11
and India are all out for
183 in just 54 overs.
Sit down. Come on, sit down!
In limited overs cricket, being bowled
out in less than the available overs
is a matter of great shame,
especially in a World Cup Final.
I hear whistling in my ear.
I was hit just below the ear.
It felt like all the slaps I got
at school had landed in one go.
No, it's the truth!
Here. Take this.
You'll be fine.
Well done, it's OK.
Get ready to bowl.
183 is the lowest score ever
in a World Cup Final.
Had it been England, we could've
called it a Final.
At least we would've had
an interesting match.
Come on. Come on, soldiers.
Let's fight!
Let them say they were batting
better than us.
Bowling and fielding better
than us. It's OK.
They just shouldn't say they were
trying harder than us.
I know we didn't get a high score.
But we did score.
And they have yet to score 183 runs.
We won't let that happen.
Come what may.
The game boils down to that.
Hey guys, this is your first
World Cup Final, so smile!
Come on, smile.
What we do here today
is that everybody fight.
Fight for our life
and we will do that.
Because like people says
Taste the success once...
Taste success once...
tongue wants more!
Here, catch! Make sure you catch
on the field too.
You don't give me an option only.
You laugh when I speak English.
183 is enough
if we fight for every run.
The West Indies fans dancing
to the calypso beat.
They'll be hoping it's a repeat
of the semi-finals against Pakistan
where they chased down 184
with 8 wickets to spare.
The first over by the Captain
is a maiden.
Looks like the Indians will fight
for every run.
Sandhu to Greenidge.
And that outswinger
almost finding the edge.
Ballu!
Play your inswinger.
And listen, hide it!
An extra man on the
off side for Sandhu.
And he's bowled him!
Would you believe it?
What a ball!
It looked like it would go out but
the ball cut back in quite sharply.
Sandhu has managed to fool a man
of Gordon Greenidge's experience.
An early breakthrough for India.
West Indies are 5 for 1.
And in comes Viv Richards.
And he's been in smashing form with three
man of the match award in four games.
He's arrived. Keep it tight, Sardar.
You'll get him out too. Come on.
You said something to him,
I was watching.
Kaps, what medicine did you
give Ballu?
Vitamin C.
- Keep at it, Sardar.
- Come on, Ballu.
Sandhu to Richards.
Pulled away powerfully. Four runs.
No problem. That's Richards.
Richards does make this look
awfully easy. Superbly timed.
Kapil to Richards.
And it's another boundary.
Pakistan made 184 in the semi-final.
That is one more run
than India's total today.
While Viv has made 80 runs
with 11 fours and one sixer.
Single-handedly winning the match
for his team.
Viv is going to kill you.
He's going to eat you up!
That's probably what he has in mind.
Beautiful drive! Madan Lal gets
the same treatment.
That's the third four.
The match is slipping away
from the Indians.
How has it happened?
What's this nonsense?
Let's go.
He hit Madan for three fours
in one over.
I can't bear to watch.
Kapil might want to change things
around after that last Madan Lal over.
Viv had 33 from just 27 balls.
Kapil, give me another over.
No, Madipaa. You'd better rest.
Kapil, I've set him.
Give me one more over.
No, he'll give you a hammering.
Kapil, he has it in for me.
He's batting like it's a match
of 30 overs.
He's overconfident. I'll take
advantage of that. Give me an over.
No, Madipaa. It's too risky.
He doesn't believe
I'm a bowler, Kaps.
Give me an over.
I want to show him.
Just one over, Kaps.
Ballu.
Madan Lal is given another over.
The Captain is taking a big risk.
Stop, Yash, stop!
Richards has hit that away to
within 15 yards of the boundary
and the Indian skipper has done
a tremendous job to run back there.
Marvellous running catch.
One of the finest ever taken.
This was the wicket India desperately
needed to stay in the game.
Richards departs for 33 runs.
Ladies, ladies.
Where are your passes?
We threw them away.
We thought we were losing but
now we want to go back inside.
Sorry, ladies. No entry without
a pass.
Madan Lal to Lloyd.
That doesn't look good.
The West Indies Captain is limping.
Can I have a runner, please?
Please. Please, we must go inside.
I'm Kapil Dev's wife.
Yes, sure, and I'm
the King of England!
Ladies, please step aside.
Madan Lal gets another one!
This is tremendous from India.
Absolutely fantastic.
Ladies, please.
Let's watch it on TV.
- Is it working?
- No!
- Now?
- Has it come now?
- Turn it properly.
What do you mean? No signal?
Someone, pick up the phone.
We're trying our best.
Our lives depend on this and
you've lost the signal.
No one disrupted the signal
on purpose.
When will it come back?
When the match is over?
Hello! Hey mister.
Hello!
His leg's hurting him.
Force him to come forward and play.
Binny comes back into the attack.
It's come.
Binny bowling to Lloyd.
And he's out! The West Indian Captain
is caught by the Indian Captain.
Big wicket!
Binny's 18th wicket, making him the
highest wicket taker of the tournament.
Mother!
He's gone. What a magnificent
catch by Kirmani.
At 76 for 6, the reigning world
champions are in total disarray.
Now dance. Now show us your dancing.
Kapil's going to kill you.
A low flat six from Dujon.
The Indians cannot
get complacent now.
Sardar, keep the ball tight.
It mustn't go for a boundary.
I've set the fielding. There, there
and there. Come on.
Where, where and where?
You think this is a joke?
Sardar, it's the Final.
Get serious.
Brother, whatever you say.
Crucial juncture in the game.
With that single,
West Indies brings up their 100.
Yashpal cannot stop that.
Ballu!
The required run rate is still
just over 3 runs per over.
Will Dujon save the game
for the West Indies?
The West Indies now need 65 runs
in 19 overs to win the World Cup.
Jimpa...
India needs a crucial wicket now.
Make Lala-ji 10 years younger today.
Kapil turns to his
most trusted teammate.
Jimmy to Dujon. And he's bowled!
Jimmy has proven his worth
time and time again.
Dujon is out. Amarnath has taken
a crucial wicket.
India is now back in the game
and it's wide open.
And that's another wicket
by Amarnath.
After a fabulous performance in the
semi-finals,
Amarnath is now turning
the tide in the Final.
Howzzat!
Kapil Dev gets another one!
India so close to
making history now.
What happened?
- What's the score?
- The score?
- 9 wickets down.
- Wow! 9 wickets down.
The West Indies now 9 wickets down.
Jimmy to Holding.
Howzat!
Out!
Steeped in your love,
O beloved country
Every trial is effortless
Together your admirers have
conquered the sky
Steeped in your love,
O beloved country
Every task is possible
Your admirers have won over
the world.
As long as there's life
in our breath
Devoted in our love for you,
O beloved country
India has won the World Cup!
Let our flag fly high!
Kapil!
Ladies and gentlemen,
India has won the cricket World Cup.
This shows that we can do it.
Brother.
One day, I'll play cricket
for India too.
Yes.
Name and glory,
O beloved country
Points to none other than you
Wherever I go, I long for you
Your name will shine for ever more
No one slept that night.
People were dancing everywhere, from
the streets into the hotel lobby.
I can't find the words to describe
that visual.
People were dancing and singing
and beating drums!
That kind of happiness was not
something we had experienced...
I definitely hadn't.
Champagne bottles were popped
every minute as people celebrated.
But I was just worried about who
was going to pay for all this.
It was the last day of the tour,
no one had any money left.
I still do not know to this day
who paid for everything.
We couldn't eat, we were so happy.
By the time we got hungry,
all the restaurants had closed.
The day we won the World Cup,
we slept on an empty stomach,
but with a full heart.
When we first got to England,
the famous cricket journalist,
David Frith
had written in an article
that if India won,
'he'd eat his words'.
Meaning he would chew up his words.
After we won on the 25th June,1983,
there were massive celebrations.
I only managed to get back
to my room at 4 am.
As soon as I sat down
I wrote a letter to David.
'Mr Frith, now that we've won,
you'll have to eat your words!'
A month later, on 23 July
David Frith went to Lord's.
He had a glass of wine in his hands,
and he chewed up the article
he had written!
Sitting with folded hands
achieves nothing
Go, show fate what it means
to have strength of purpose
If you are brave, my fellow country-
men God is on your side too
Go, show the world what it means
to believe in yourself
Keep the flag flying
Proudly flying in the wind
Let it fly on high
Proudly wave your country's flag
Keep the flag flying
Proudly flying in the wind
Proudly wave your country's flag