"Every rural home in
India has the same story."
"Farmers sell their land,"
"and do farming on their
own land for someone else."
"Or guard it."
"Or leave the village
and head for the city."
"This story is about
Dutta Pehelwan (wrestler),"
"and his son Rahul."
The bloody watchman's asleep!
Wake him up!
Coming, sir!
Watch out on the other side.
You're too close to the gate.
Stop. Stop. Stop.
The gate was swinging...
What have you done?
Beat him.
Rahul, that Shinder builder
is thrashing your father!
Come Ganya,
we'll have to teach him a lesson.
Wait, Rahul. I am coming.
181...
182...
Faster. You need to complete 200.
What are you doing, Shinde?
This is not the way.
Look at the Mercedes.
There's no way you
can pay for the damage.
Don't show off your wealth, Shinde.
Don't you forget,
this land once belonged to us...
which I bought in cash.
We all know at what price.
Leave it, Rahul. It was my fault.
Take him away.
Let's go.
Don't give me the stare,
cheapskate. Get lost.
What did you get
by selling the land?
Grand wedding for your daughter!
Cars, money,
jewellery for her in-laws!
So everyone can be awed
by the great 'Dutta wedding'.
Unfortunately, no one was.
But three months later
when she returned home,
everyone said Dutta
Pehelwan's lost his pride.
Spent more than he could afford
on his daughter's wedding.
Rahulya, you have a sharp tongue.
Put your energy to some good use,
so we can make ends meet.
Let the one who sold
the land earn a living.
Seriously?
And what about you?
You'll insult him and eat for free.
Rahul, finish your food!
Feed it to the dogs.
You lose your temper
on petty things.
I don't know anything
except for farming.
Quit school in class 8.
I quit school, you were dismissed.
For hitting on the
teacher's daughter.
I wasn't hitting on her.
I loved her.
- That's why he scr...
- Hey Rahulya, Ganya.
Uncle Uday!
What are you doing out here?
Arun you too.
Yeah, I brought him along too.
What are you doing?
Take the carrier home.
I got him in a college in Pune.
Why?
Because now I'm here for good.
I'm done with Mumbai.
What's up, uncle?
I got transferred to the
Market yard police station.
- Do you want to hear the entire story?
- See you later.
See you.
See you uncle, aunt.
What's wrong?
Why is everyone so depressed?
Shinde fired your
father from the job.
Why?
He getting vegetables,
from our field.
Our field, father? Ours?
Enough, Rahul. Stop it.
Why did he fire you if you were
getting vegetables from our field?
Shinde said he was stealing
and threw him out.
What now?
Tarde... he's found him another job,
in Pune's Market yard.
What job at the market yard?
Labour.
Good going, father.
Needs a lot of strength
but no courage.
And you're a wrestler.
- Stop I said.
- What happened?
Where are you going?
- Rahul.
Rahul, stop.
Shinde.
Rahul.
Rahul, stop.
Shinde.
What happened?
Why are you screaming?
You threw my father out of his job.
I don't entertain thieves
who steal at my place.
How much was he taking?
He's donated more vegetables
than you can count in a lifetime.
Get lost or I will
have you thrown out!
- Shinde...
- Rahul.
I am a son of a farmer,
and I swear on my mother.
One day I'll make you toil
on this field with a pair of bulls!
- Get lost.
- Like a plough.
Get lost.
- You don't ever listen to me, father.
- Come on.
Sit down quietly.
He'll have me thrown out.
He'll have us thrown out.
Sit down.
Sit down and keep calm.
Your temper will someday...
Rahul!
- Stop screaming, drama queen.
- Stop the truck.
Stop the truck.
Father dearest,
can he come with us too?
You always take things lightly.
Catch my bag.
- Sit here.
- Let's go.
He said and you tagged along.
Where are you going?
All thanks to Shinde Builder,
understand.
Leaving me alone.
"The world's a evil place."
"Filled with evil thoughts."
"Has run after,"
"dirty profession fast."
"Someone will come along,"
"in place of God."
"A girl's been raped
in a garage in Ganesh Nagar."
"Even the Police & local residents
are scared to help."
- "Why are you recording this?"
- "Wait."
- "We'll get in trouble."
- "We'll be viral."
- "Let's get out of here."
- "Okay, fine."
Come on.
Did anyone see anything?
No one saw anything.
Someone made a video, posted it too,
but no one saw anything.
What if it was your
daughter or sister instead?
Would you still be making
videos and posting them?
You should be ashamed!
Who are you scared of?
Who are you terrorized by?
Sir, I saw them.
Sir, it was the local MLA's son.
I saw it with my own eyes.
He's done it with another girl.
The girl's brother
made a Police complaint,
and they killed him.
They are all animals.
Where does he stay?
That building.
See who's at the door.
Why did you come inside, Sardar?
- So I can arrest you.
- Why?
Because of what you
did with that girl.
There's no witness or testimony.
Think you can still arrest me?
Not yet,
but there will be.
My belt alone can
teach you a lesson.
You were terrorized of him,
weren't you?
Will you testify now?
I will testify, sir.
I will testify.
- We'll testify!
- We'll testify! We'll testify!
Rahul.
What happened, Rahul?
Where were you looking?
This sack was lying in the middle.
It's not the sack,
it's the tea-seller.
I've been noticing for
the last couple of days,
you've had your eyes on her.
I've lost my heart to her.
She won't fall for you.
I'll impress her.
Leave it.
- Do you want to see?
- Yes.
What are you doing?
What?
One special tea.
Learn to say it first.
You teach me.
It's called 'special tea'.
Costs three rupees.
But you should stick
to regular one rupee tea.
That's what all labours here drink.
Then I will have the special one.
Because I'm special too.
Here are three rupees.
Here. Your tea.
How can you prove
this tea's special?
Everyone take's Manda's word for it.
Understood.
Then you taste it first
and then I'll be convinced.
Listen, you over smart freak,
look around you.
I'm the only female in this
man's world running this tea shop.
No one's dared to
even lay a finger on me.
And what do you think?
You can impress me
with your filmy one-liners.
Have your tea or get lost.
Smart alec.
Someday you'll offer this
freak this special tea,
after you've tasted it.
Let's go, Ganya.
Take your money.
Keep it.
As a credit for that special tea.
She's got a temper.
Where were you guys?
Having tea, father.
- Bring these sacks along.
- Okay.
Come, Rahul. Give me a hand.
What's he doing here?
Who?
From a pro wrestler
to ordinary labour.
Do you know him?
Know him?
He was the reigning
Maharashtra Kesari.
Absurd.
Honestly.
I gave him 5000
rupees with a trophy.
Careful.
Now he's sold everything
and reduced to dust.
Time to get paid!
So tired of working all day.
Let's collect salary.
Come on.
Pay up.
Come on, keep moving.
What is this?
What's the queue all about?
- It's the Corporator's share.
- Why?
No money no jobs.
But this is wrong.
We'll have to pay.
Here I come, my beloved bar...
Hey cheapskate, where do
you think you're going? Come here.
We've had enough of you wise guy.
Come here.
Don't touch my collar.
Stop blabbering and pay up.
Pay up.
- I said don't touch me.
- How dare you hit me?
Don't hit me.
- What are they doing?
- Why are you beating him? Leave him!
Leave my father alone!
Father, get up.
They are beating up a poor man
and everyone's watching.
Get lost.
Your father's had it coming.
Father, get up.
Ganya, let's go.
How dare you refuse us?
What are you doing?
Stop it, guys.
You've roughed him up enough.
Get lost, ass****
Don't abuse.
Or what? What will you do?
Don't touch me.
Take that you...
Rahul!
Stay back, father.
- Rahul.
- Ganya, take father away.
Let's go, let's go.
Wait a minute. They took my money.
Rahul.
Rahul, don't fight.
Rahul, listen.
Father.
"The world's a evil place."
"Filled with evil thoughts."
"Has run after,"
"dirty profession fast."
"Your last is written by his hand."
What are you looking at?
Sardars are not in Punjab alone.
Sardars are in every
corner of the world.
Even in Japan.
Where there are Sardars,
there's Gurdwara,
and a community kitchen.
No one ever starves.
You've only been
in the city for a week,
and already you got into trouble.
They were extorting
money from labours.
You should've paid too.
Sir, they were getting violent.
Then you should've taken a beating.
That place is filled with goons.
Why did you two have to be a hero?
We made a mistake, sir.
We'll never do it again.
Let us go.
You two are charged
with a half-murder case.
You two are almost there.
That Corporator Salvi
is a devious man.
Rahulya, Ganya,
what are you two doing inside?
Uday bro, you know these two?
Yes, these kids
are from my hometown.
I mean what have these two done?
Corporator Salvi has been extorting
money at the market yard for so long.
These two tried to be a hero.
Next week another labour
will refuse to pay him money.
They will stay in
lockup for two days.
Hoping they will get bail on Monday.
Otherwise, Salvi's men
are inside to take care of them.
Actually, they are good kids.
Sir, it's not their fault.
- They were just...
- Dutta.
Uday?
It's not their fault.
- Only to save me...
- Dutta, do you know them?
Yes, he's Rahul's father.
He's Maharastra Kesari (champion).
And that's his daughter.
Sorry sir,
but there's nothing we can do today.
If they get bail on Monday,
arrange for the bail money.
Money?
But I don't have...
Dutta uncle. Dutta uncle, I'm there.
Don't worry.
But brother Uday,
they haven't eaten food.
You're worried about
food at this time.
Anyway, come on.
I am there.
Come on, let's go.
Go on home. Look after your mother.
Did you like what you saw?
Thanks to you Maharastra Kesari was
standing helpless in front of me.
There's still time to change.
Otherwise, your father will be
dead on the inside before you die.
Hello.
Greetings, Nanya bhai.
Greetings, bhai.
What can we do?
Hey, Desai.
You're being released today,
Nanya bhai.
Right. They are all my brothers.
Take good care of them.
Okay guys, see you.
We'll meet on the outside.
It won't be much fun without you.
Do you want me to
rot in jail for your fun?
Come on, Nanya bhai.
Who are these two freshies?
These two roughed up Corporator
Salvi's boys in the market yard.
Them?
Yes.
They are in for a beating today.
Wise guy.
What's the matter, brother?
Think you're a loose cannon.
- Yeah.
- Watch.
Why are you hitting us?
What did you do at the market yard?
Look, man, I acted in a fit of rage.
It was a mistake.
I said it was a mistake
Mistake, huh?
What are you staring at?
Look down.
That's it.
Hey...stop!
Back. Stay back. Back.
Come on. Back.
What happened?
Nanya bhai, he roughed
up boss' men at the market yard.
And now you roughed them up.
Scores settled.
But he broke Makya's head.
- Why you...
- Wait a minute. Back. Sit down.
These things happen
in a fit of rage.
- Now leave. Come on.
- But...
I said leave you fool.
Get lost.
Back. Back.
What's your name?
Rahul.
Ganya.
You two will get the bail.
Stay out of trouble until then.
Keep calm. Now get going.
Who is he?
You fool,
Nanya bhai is the king of Pune.
- Hey...
- Hello, Nanya bhai.
What happened?
Who roughed you up?
Sit. Sit.
Salvi's boys roughed them
up at night in jail.
Salvi's boys are such cowards.
I broke one's jaw and
gave the other a black eye.
Nice.
Don't you have sugar?
But this is jaggery.
Have it.
You guys are a classic case.
Not to worry.
Work with me.
Tell your family
no need to work anymore.
Right?
Nanya bhai...
I want to teach that
Corporator a lesson.
- Who?
- Salvi. Salvi.
He broke Ganya's arm,
now I'll break his arm.
That Salvi has a history behind him.
He always carries
a dozen boys with him.
How will you rough him up?
But boss, he goes to Chaufala
alone every Saturday.
To watch the dance.
His boys stay out.
"My my my my..."
"Listen carefully."
Let our secret become public."
"Let me put our story on Insta."
"This spark will
make us trend."
"This spark will give
us 100 million likes."
"Not a minute of peace,"
"this is a reel of our love."
"No edit, no filter."
"Let it be a hit on the internet,
not on Twitter alone."
"I'll hashtag the entire world,
here comes the spark."
Corporator Salvi.
Yes.
"Why did you post this story?"
"The world will stalk you, dear."
"They will troll you for no reason."
"Your secret will be viral."
"here comes the spark."
"Come closer, sweetheart."
"Let me refill your
glass with my eyes."
"Let me swallow your darkness,"
"and give you the moon."
"Let me open all my secrets,"
"and tell you."
"Here comes the spark."
"Why did you post this story?"
"The world will stalk you, dear."
"They will troll you for no reason."
"Your secret will be viral."
"here comes the spark."
Let our secret become public."
"Let me put our story on Insta."
"This spark will
make us trend."
"This spark will give
us 100 million likes."
"Why did you hashtag your story?"
"Now your story
will become trending."
"You enchanted them with your eyes,"
"social-media is too powerful."
"here comes the spark."
Wow!
Look Ganya, squandering labour's
money on his hobbies.
Bloody rascal.
Why you?
Listen, if I ever see you
or your boys in the market yard,
then I will skin you alive
and make a shoe out of it.
You'll die like a dog.
What are you doing?
- Why you...
- Ganya, let's go.
Don't pick up this money.
Come on.
Rahul.
Sir, I didn't want to kill him.
But he came after me with a chopper.
And I only pushed him.
If I hadn't reacted
he would've killed me, sir.
Did you go there to
invite him to your wedding?
If we make a self-defence case...
Seems difficult.
There's a strong case against them.
They will face imprisonment.
MLA and Nanya together.
What are they doing here?
Hello, Rajveer.
- Hey, pull the chair.
- Yes sir.
What brings you here?
If you treat innocent
youngsters like this,
then as a public servant
I've to show up at your door.
They confessed that they
killed the Corporator.
If you torture them,
anyone will confess.
Turn on the TV.
Watch the latest breaking news.
The other day the
Corporator was drunk.
I told him to stay over.
But he didn't listen to me.
During the tussle, he rammed
into the glass and died.
I tried stopping
him from getting drunk,
but he assaulted me.
And then he fell down and died.
So it's clear
- that Corporator Salvi wasn't murdered.
- Switch it off.
It was an accident.
Bail papers.
Do you want to see it?
No.
Brother Uday, let them go.
- Touch the MLA's feet.
- Sir.
- It's okay.
You two did the right thing.
That Salvi was getting
to be a pain in the neck.
You put him down. Good.
But sir, how could his men lie?
We put a gun to his wife's head,
and he started
singing in our favour.
Simple.
Nanya, even I will put a gun
to your head like this?
And then I want to see how you sing.
Rajveer, calm down.
Do you want to get suspended again?
Doesn't matter.
Better change.
Come on.
- Soman, complete the procedure.
- Yes.
Come on, guys. Let's go, let's go.
Order some tea.
Nanavare, order some tea.
These things take time.
Only tea?
- Yes, tea.
- Bread-butter, toast?
No, only tea.
Is this Police Station
your father's house?
Water is fine?
Yes.
Offering water is a good deed.
I will see you.
My name is Advocate Soman.
I'm leaving now.
But I'll deal with you later.
Sir, did you get suspended?
Yes. This happened two years ago.
There was a drug
gang in the college,
who first got a girl
addicted to drugs.
And then raped her.
They threw acid on her face
and left her outside the college.
I couldn't bear it.
I took the law in my hand.
And didn't spare even
a single member of this gang.
The Human Rights people made
a fuss on this MLA's instructions.
And I was suspended for two years.
But crime will never end.
We never can.
Another goon took Gulshan's place,
and he got MLA's support.
He became Nanya bhai.
Now Rahul will take
Nanya bhai's place.
We cannot do anything
even if we want to.
Our hands are tied.
We can only supply raw materials.
To do these politicians' dirty jobs.
Careful, Dutta.
- Here.
- Father.
No more menial labour.
You took this burden off my back,
but what about the
burden on my chest?
What burden, father?
You killed a man.
Me? I was proven innocent, father.
Call it destiny, Rahul.
This is your chance to reform.
Look, we'll have half a square meal,
but make an honest living.
Father,
I'll have a full square meal.
Along with a sweet dish.
Criminals only end
up in the graveyard,
or be destroyed like this Satya.
Leave it, father.
Let's go to my new house along
with my mother and Seema.
You're not old enough to
shoulder our burden.
We have a long day ahead.
Have to make an honest living.
Okay, father. As you wish.
I don't want to eat.
Eat it!
Hey...why are you hitting the child?
She isn't eating.
Why aren't you eating?
Every day the same
old flour vegetable.
I am not going to et it.
We sell vegetables
from our fields here.
And feeds us
this flour vegetable.
Did you come here
to sell your vegetables?
Yes, sir.
That's my truck.
- How much did you sell it for?
- 8000
- Fertilizer, seeds, medicines?
- 1500
- And the truck's rental?
- 3500
- Toll, food?
- 1500
- How much?
- 6500
- How much is he left with?
- 1500
All this trouble for 1500?
What to do, sir?
Those agents don't
pay the right price.
Come with me.
Hello, sir.
Pay him.
I already did.
You got paid.
What else do you want?
8000 isn't enough, sir.
It's too less.
You guys are just...
Here, another 500.
This won't help, sir.
I want at least 12,000 for my truck.
Get lost with your truck.
Get out.
- Listen to me, sir.
- Take the money back.
- No, sir.
- If I ever see you in the market again,
I will break your legs.
No, sir. Listen to me.
Let's see who buys
your truck for 12,000.
I will buy it.
- Never seen him before.
- I'll buy his vegetables for 12,000.
Hey...I've been buying vegetables
in this market for 12 years.
I've seen people
like you come and go.
Next time you open your mouth,
I'll break your jaw and
shove it down your throat.
Hey...what are you doing?
Listen to me.
How much are you going to beat me?
I only roughed you up today.
If I see you in the market again,
I will break your
legs and shove it up the...
Everyone has two holes, up and...
Understood?
Get lost.
And listen,
now I will buy your vegetables.
And the rate is...
- Tell them.
- 12,000 rupees per truck!
- Long live...
- Rahul!
Tell Manda one special tea.
A truckload of vegetables
costs 32,000 at retail price.
Meaning 24,000 profit.
That's why I offered them 12.
Let's become partners.
Your brains and my money.
Boss, Daya and Pitya.
What are they doing here?
Who are Daya and Pitya?
Small-time crooks of Bund Garden.
They take on small-time jobs.
They are from Mulshi as well.
- Hello, Nanya bhai.
- Daya, Pitya, sit down.
Hey... Pitambar dada, Digambar dada.
What are you doing here?
You know them.
They were our boys.
They used to get cigarettes
and booze for us.
We used to hit them on
the head to get a job done.
Don't try that now
or they will screw you.
You must be joking, Nanya bhai.
I am not joking.
They murdered Corporator Salvi.
Really?
Nanya bhai, he always had guts.
He's that Dutta wrestler's son.
How is Dutta uncle?
Dutta wrestler is now
a labour at the market yard.
Nanya bhai, when I was in school...
Listen, fool, don't start
narrating his family story,
...tell me why you're here.
Oh yes.
There's a property of 50 acres.
Needs to be vacated.
It's a big job.
Not our cup of tea.
What do I get?
The client's offering 60 million.
We'll split it fifty-fifty.
- Done.
- What done?
It's the same property
we tried to vacate earlier.
It has 26 owners.
That is a native land...
We'll get screwed for good.
The Kamble family land...
- That property?
- Leave guys, not possible.
What if I try?
Even the best of the
best tried their hand.
What can you do?
Lawyer...
let me try there is nothing to lose.
Why is he telling me to get up?
I want to sit.
Sit down. Sit down.
He's telling me to get up.
Go ahead and try.
I'll try Nanya bhai, but fifty-fifty
doesn't sound right.
Now you want a share too?
Come on Nanya bhai,
will I ask you for a share?
I mean you keep
90% and they keep 10.
We brought this job.
Then do it yourself
and take the entire share.
He's got a point.
- Nanya...
- He's got a point.
- Okay, 30%
- 12.
- 20%
- 15.
18...
Hey fool, what is this a chop shop?
- Get lost?
- Okay fine, Nanya bhai.
15 is okay.
Hey lawyer,
keep every owner's document ready.
Cheers.
Put your thumb impression here.
I'm asking you politely,
We'll pay you more
money if you like,
but quietly put your
thumb impression here.
I won't put my thumb impression here
until the Master doesn't say so.
Ganya, who is their master?
The same guy who
threw you out of school.
I see...
Let your master come.
We'll settle some old scores.
Look, speak of the
devil and he's here.
Soman, you'll never learn, will you?
I get paid so my
job is to keep trying.
For the last time,
I'd rather die but
never sell my land.
- As you wish.
- If you're dead,
how would you know
this is your land or not?
Rahul.
What are you doing here?
I've taken up the
job to vacate your land.
Now come and sign the papers.
Leave my hand.
I saw your true colors at a
very young age, shameless.
That's why I threw
you out of school.
You did the right thing.
Because if I had continued studying,
I would've become a clerk.
Or maybe with my good luck,
an officer.
But you see, master,
even the biggest officer wet
their pants when they see me.
Let's sign the papers.
Master...
I am not scared of anyone.
Being a farmer's
son you stooped so low!
I won't sign!
Master, stop irritating me.
Or what?
What will you do?
Do you want to know your place?
Why the...
God!
Lawyer, what are you waiting for?
Take his thumb impression.
Even a dead man's
thumb is still a thumb.
Right away.
Ganya, take everyone's
thumb impression.
26 owners 26 stamp papers.
So he killed Maruti Kamble.
Yes, sir. He did.
He's Maruti Kamble's uncle.
And you're bothering
Rahul's parents for no reason.
He's the hero.
Tell sir.
I needed money.
And Maruti Kamble was being unfair.
So I shot him in a fit of rage.
Yes...I was telling him.
Okay, fine. That's enough.
Shooting him is one thing,
first, hold this gun.
What's the point?
He's admitting his
crime so arrest him.
You're such a rascal.
Some day I will strip you naked.
If we ever meet in court,
I will strip you naked
in the witness box.
Without taking a single cloth off.
I accept your challenge.
Tell me something,
how did you do it?
The old man was under a lot of debt.
We paid him.
Now he and his family will never
have to worry about money.
They are happy.
Yes...
He gave and I took.
And killed him.
- Isn't that right?
- It's okay, go on now.
- All done here.
- Fine.
Good boy.
Here's Rahul's anticipatory bail.
Now order some tea.
No, no, no...
There's already a shortage
of water in Vidarbha.
It's not right that you keep
wasting water on me.
Is it mineral water?
He was your teacher.
He taught you in school.
And you killed him.
I didn't kill him, mother.
His own uncle killed him.
It's all over the newspaper and TV.
See it for yourself.
Just like you didn't
kill the Corporator.
Go away, come on.
I said go.
You guys are being crazy.
Seema, please talk to them.
What will she say?
Ganya, take him away.
Then die here.
Seema, come with me.
Come on.
- Seema.
- Come on.
Get lost.
Don't ever come back here.
MLA sir, good morning.
Nanya, what brings you
here at this early hour?
I have to show up
when you don't do my job.
What job?
Salvi is dead.
And I suggested Dagdu Khapre's
name for the by-elections.
What happened?
Khapre has two murder
charges against him.
Listen Hambir, you never
had a clean record yourself.
But you're still the MLA.
The party president
isn't too happy with Khapre.
The other party is
ready to give him a ticket.
Then that same party will put...
...me against you in the
assembly elections.
Then you're done.
Don't get angry.
Fine, Khapre's seat is fixed.
I give you my word.
I knew you'll do the job.
See you.
- Did you unload the vehicle?
- I did.
Dutta, everyone looks happy.
Your son's made farmers life better.
He's also shed a
lot of blood for it.
Rahul, did you really
kill Maruti Kamble?
Look, Manda,
don't listen to my father.
Then why do people keep saying it?
I don't know.
It's also in the newspapers
that his uncle killed him.
My father is drunk all
the time, but he loves me.
Even I love you a lot.
Rahul, he'll take every
decision in my life.
And he will never let his
daughter marry a criminal.
What was he?
That's why he won't.
- Nanya bhai...
- Ganya...
Let it be.
- Where is Rahul?
- He's right here.
Rahul. Rahul. Nanya bhai's here.
You go.
Nanya bhai,
you showed up so suddenly.
- Nanya bhai...
- My angry young man!
Don't touch my feet.
Give me a hug.
Awesome.
You're my little brother.
What were you doing in the corner,
with that girl?
She's hot.
Really hot.
We're serious, Nanya bhai.
Are you done with her?
What are you saying, Nanya bhai?
It's not like that.
Let me know after you're done.
I like her.
We're brothers after all.
Together we can enjoy.
As I said Nanya bhai,
I love her.
We're serious.
I was only joking.
I got something for you.
Bring it.
Look. How is it?
It's awesome.
It's for you.
But there was no need for this,
Nanya bhai.
Need.
The deal on Maruti
Kamble's land is done.
26 agreements are lying in the car.
- Throw the key.
- Yes, boss. Here you go, boss.
Take this key.
Get in that car, and come
to my birthday tonight.
- On-time.
- Yes, brother.
Because until he doesn't arrive,
I won't cut the cake.
- Right, guys.
- Absolutely right.
Be there on time.
Come on.
Now he's your brother.
When your own family leaves you,
strangers become your kin.
- Go ahead.
- Rahulya, sit.
Sit here.
Sit here,
I'll tell you that rascal's story.
Sit. Sit.
When Shinde bought
your father's land,
at a dirt-cheap price.
Do you know how?
Because of this Nanya bhai.
This Nanya put a gun
to your sister's head,
and said put your thumb
impression on the paper.
Otherwise, first, he will
rape your sister and then kill her.
Your father had no choice.
He put his thumb impression.
And now this Nanya is your brother.
Now deal with the consequences
of your own choice.
Bloody useless...
That's all I have.
What are you doing?
Not my cigarette too.
"Make him understand"
Tell him.
What are you all looking at?
Is this a drama?
Get lost.
Hello.
Wait a minute.
Rahul. MLA Hambir.
Hello.
"There's only one
tiger in this area."
"Everyone's overwhelmed
when he arrives."
"Heaps of gold piled up,"
"let's dance my crazy."
"We'll break the speakers,"
"blast the firecrackers."
"Pour whiskey all night."
"We'll have a ball,
we'll have a blast."
"It's our brother's birthday."
"Market free, cigarette free,"
"ordered biryani with extra ghee."
"We're going to scream and shout."
"Market free, cigarette free,"
"ordered biryani with extra ghee."
"Chocolate cake's too big."
"The arrangement's just too great."
"Kolhapur, Sholapur, Satara."
"Wife will dance,
sister-in-law will dance."
"So will the old man."
"It's our brother's birthday."
"No one's gonna mess with us,"
"we've already made all setting."
"No on, Dagdu."
"No one's gonna mess with us,"
"we've already made all setting."
"We'll spread the carpet, "
"and make girls do the catwalk."
"We'll booze all night,"
"and puke in the morning."
"It's 12 o'clock."
"It's our brother's birthday."
"Happy happy birthday."
Hey lawyer, will you defend my case?
Of course.
Then hold this.
Come on.
Do you like getting
embarrassed every time?
I want to shoot you right now.
Mind your tongue, sir.
Stop hitting the weak.
Show me what you got.
Come on.
I respect this uniform, sir,
that's why I am quiet.
Whether you respect
this uniform or not,
but we sure do.
- Uday, look after this properly.
- Yes.
While I rough him up politely.
My father was Maharashtra Kesari.
Your father was Maharashtra Kesari.
I am Hind Kesari.
Do you know
I am Pune's new don?
You are Pune's new don,
but I was always the hero of India.
"The world's an evil place."
"Filled with evil thoughts."
"Has run after,"
"dirty profession fast."
"Your last is written by his hand."
There were more than
200 guests at that party.
No one saw anything.
But Rahul was charged
with Nanya's murder.
Rahul is a decent
and talented worker.
But the Police have
a personal enmity with him.
The Corporator died in an accident,
but Rahul was arrested.
Maruti Kamble was
murdered by his uncle.
But Rahul was accused of it again.
And now this.
But Police can't continue
this dictatorship for long.
Hey lawyer,
how long will this case last?
What case?
There's no witness.
The judge will throw
it out on the first day.
By the way,
Daya and Pitya want to meet.
Later.
- Where is Uday?
- Sir.
That way.
Hello, sir.
Sir.
Sit, Uday.
- Sir, do you know?
- Rahul got bail.
So you know.
Did you really believe
Rahul will rot in jail forever?
Until people like corrupt
MLA Hambir are out there,
these guys will get bail.
We got a gun but every
bullet is accounted for.
But these guys...
Nothing.
Meaning we'll do nothing.
We will.
We will use our minds.
Have you read the Mahabharata?
No, but I've seen it on TV.
Who was the hero of Mahabharata?
Arjun.
His aim was perfect.
But the brain was Lord Krishna.
He pitted brothers against
each other to end unrighteousness.
So to end crime,
why can't we pit these
criminals against each other.
Great.
What an idea?
How do you like my nature?
Nice. You're very calm.
Because I don't raise my voice,
I don't abuse,
I am not violent.
There is a lot of anger in me.
The day this Sardar loses it,
everyone will be scared stiff.
Rahul...
Daya, Pitya.
Not them again.
Make another one for me.
How are you, Rahul?
Great. What's wrong with me?
What brings you here?
Needed something.
The contract on Kamble.
We're here to collect our 15%
Look...Nanya's case turned
out to be too expensive.
Things are not good.
Even we're not in such
a good position, Rahul.
You know what, keep 600,000.
Let's settle the rest later.
What good is 600,000?
Our share is 9 million.
I told you to keep this 600,000.
Someone's coming to meet me.
Get going you two.
Leave. Are you waiting for dinner?
Rahul...
Sister-in-law.
Leave, guys.
Come on.
Rahul, I got to leave early today.
"I've nothing to lose
or gain except for you."
"Without you, I cannot live."
"Without you, I've nowhere to go."
"I am falling for you."
"Since you showered
your love on me."
"Yes, it's happening."
"It's happening."
"I am falling in love."
"Yes, I am falling in love."
"I am falling for you,"
"you're falling for me."
"I am falling in love."
"Yes, I am falling in love."
"The ambience seems scarlet,"
"stars scattered everywhere."
"Take me in your arms,"
"so we lose ourselves."
"I am wherever you are."
"I am the tune you're the music."
"I am falling for you."
"Since you showered
your love on me."
"Yes, it's happening."
"It's happening."
"I am falling in love."
"Yes, I am falling in love."
"I am falling for you,"
"you're falling for me."
"I am falling in love."
"Yes, I am falling in love."
I need a file urgently,
but can't remember which one.
Padwal, remember...
I've been looking for it
since morning, but can't remember.
- Sir, what about this one?
- No, no, can't be in this one.
Then...
Sir, he's annoyed now.
Brother Uday,
I've been waiting for half an hour.
Give me the register
so I can sign it.
Are you some Minister
to get VIP treatment?
Put your feet down.
Put your feet down
or else I will break it.
Bloody cheap goon.
Several Police officers survive
because of this cheap goon.
You survive on our leftovers.
And is this your honest living
which you're squandering away?
You earn by snatching
lands from poor farmers.
Coward.
When this coward becomes
the MLA tomorrow,
then a minister.
Will you salute him then?
Will you survive till then?
We've a list of monsters like you,
who ended up in the
grave before swearing-in.
Sir, I am different.
I will survive.
And someday also become
the CM of Maharashtra.
Nothing lasts forever in this world,
except for plastic.
Then think of me as plastic.
And I promise you,
someday you'll be saluting me,
and even fall at my feet.
I am a Sardar.
I only bow before the Lord.
When I get a chance
I will shoot you.
Uday, take this illiterate's
thumb impression.
If I lose my mind, I will
put his brains on this register.
Maharashtra's CM.
Daya, it's been too long.
Patwardhan will be here soon.
Your watch is really cool,
brother Pitya.
- Like it?
- Yes.
Here.
- No, no, I was just...
- Keep it.
Hey...who are you guys?
- What is this charade?
- Here he comes?
- How did you two get inside?
- Through the gate.
Coming inside our
own farm is no crime.
Your farm?
Can't you read?
Read that.
This property belongs
to Vijay Patwardhan.
Trespassers will be prosecuted.
Sorry, sorry.
Now get out.
Get out.
Where do you think you're going?
What are you doing?
Quiet.
Give me that.
What are you doing?
Now read this.
My father's land.
Do whatever you want.
Pitya and Daya.
You don't know who got me this land.
Who?
Rahul.
Brother, brother, listen.
Please let me go inside.
- Bhaskar, throw him out.
- Please listen.
Get out.
I just want to talk.
- Just let me talk to him once.
- What's going on there?
He's been waiting
here since morning.
He's insisting on meeting you.
Let me go inside.
Let him in.
Come on.
What's your name?
Siddharth.
Do you want money?
Job. With you.
What does your father do?
He died two years ago.
Three months later my
mother committed suicide.
Since I had no job I stole.
I was in the remand
home for two years.
Someone said Rahulya
dada is a good man.
So I came to you.
Keep this money. Keep it.
And don't hesitate
to ask if you want more.
Understood.
Someone take him home.
- Go on, son.
- Brother.
- Brother, I've no one.
- Listen.
Let me stay with you.
Boss...
Don't be scared. Jump.
I am right here.
No, father. I am scared.
Where are you going?
Use your hands and feet.
Bravo, my son.
Bravo.
I told you I am always with you.
Boss is calling.
Yes, boss.
Bandya,
where did you leave that boy?
Nowhere, boss.
He's still sitting outside the gate.
Bring him inside.
Okay, boss.
Boss.
Come on.
You go.
Sit.
Not there, sit here.
Here?
Yes.
You want to stay with me.
I won't leave you
until you're alive.
I'll do everything you say.
You'll attend school from tomorrow.
I'll get you the best education.
I'll never let you miss your father.
I know how it feels
not having a father.
Not the feet.
Not the feet. Not the feet.
Sit here.
You're my best friend now.
Go on.
Rahul.
What?
Remember Patwardhan whom
we got a place in Mulshi.
What about him?
Daya and Pitya seized his place,
and shot him in the leg.
We must soon take care of
these fools Daya and Pitya.
And what time do we have
to go to the IT Park tomorrow?
10 o'clock.
But what's in the IT Park.
Golden egg laying gooses.
What?
You bought the farmer's
land at dirt cheap price,
and built this IT Park.
Now those poor farmers are either
working as labour in the market yard,
become drunkards,
or committing suicide.
And you scoundrels
are making millions.
You'll have to pay a share.
We make an honest living here.
Do you think we'll easily
pay up if you threaten us like this?
Of course, you will.
And if I say no,
then you'll beg me
to take your honest money.
Otherwise, everyone will
get a bullet in the head.
Taking my opinion and
going against it. Sit. Sit.
Sir, please. Please, sir.
Sit.
Sit, sit.
Your villagers have
started a new shop.
Meaning.
IT Park, extortion...
20 million every month.
That much.
That was Agarwal on the line.
He's scared.
I said make an NC.
No.
So.
Brother Uday,
have you seen a cockfight?
Several times in my village.
We'll make your
two cocks fight here.
It's going to be a lot of fun.
- Padwal.
- Sir.
Call Pitya.
Tell him that his share
of the IT Park money,
is going to Rahul now.
Sir.
Pitya.
Father, how are you?
How is mother?
Who is he?
Are you angry?
I don't know.
What kind of an answer is that?
I read the newspaper every day.
They write nonsense.
Don't read them.
Ganya, come here.
What is it, Satya bhai?
Give me a hand.
That Rahul is so rich,
why does he still
come here to drink tea?
He's your future son-in-law.
Scoundrel, that's my daughter.
I would rather throw
her in front of a train,
then let her marry him.
Rahul, Satya bhai is refusing
to let you marry Manda.
I'm not scared of him.
- Even I was a gangster at a time.
- Why that...
But I wasn't a coward like him.
Listen you,
drunkard, I am not asking you.
If you don't agree then
I will take her forcefully.
I see...
Rahulya, when I get a headache,
there's a shop nearby
where I buy aspirins.
Two for rupee 1.
But I check it twice
for its expiry date.
She's my daughter.
Who is she?
My daughter.
How many times will I
check the guy she will marry?
I won't let any
guy marry my daughter.
And you're done forever, man.
Your expiry date is long gone.
- Telling me about my expiry date.
- Yes. You can drop dead any time...
- Rahul!
- What are you doing?
Leave him, Rahul.
Whose expiry date has arrived?
Yours.
I am not scared of you.
Wait, Manda.
You think you won't
let her marry me.
Your daughter's slept with me.
Will you still stop me?
Try stopping me.
Satya. Satya.
Shameless! I won't marry
you even if he says yes.
What are you saying, Manda?
And you're trying to
assert your right on me.
What do you want to tell everyone?
Listen, everyone!
Yes...
Yes, I slept with him!
But I still won't marry him.
Manda.
He can forcefully take others lands.
But he cannot take Manda.
- Manda, I love...
- I hate you!
If you'll try to forcefully take me,
you'll only drag my dead body.
- Manda, listen...
- Get lost.
I said get lost.
Take him away!
Give me the flask!
Yes.
Rahul, Barkya went to the
IT Park to collect the money.
Daya and Pitya shot
him and took the money.
Barkya is dead.
Soon it will be your turn, Rahul.
Check properly.
- Uday,
- Yes sir.
this is better than a cockfight.
These criminals
will kill each other,
end of crime.
What will we do?
We'll only count the heads.
- Padwal.
- Sir.
- Note down these names.
- Yes, sir.
Saurav Salvi.
Vikas Sanap.
Nilesh Jadhav.
Raees Khan.
Rahulya, Daya and Pitya
killed two more of your guys.
"The world's an evil place
filled with evil thoughts."
"Running after evil money,
shame on them."
"Someone arrives as God
and controls your life."
"It's so difficult here,
I talk to my own pain."
"Kill him, kill him, I'll kill him.
"I will bloody kill him."
Daya, Rahulya killed
two of your boys.
Did you finish the job?
Yes, sir.
Tea?
- No, sir.
- We've to leave.
"My heart burns and I carry
my passion in my arms."
"I fight against death
in the path of death."
"I live under fear and yet I dare."
"My breath's filled with poison
and compromise with my dreams."
"I won't endure any longer,
no more fear in my eyes."
"What else can I say?
You strangle millions."
"Kill him,
kill him, I will kill him."
Sameer Dhonde.
Agarwal sir, is the money ready?
How many more of
you will we have to pay?
Who else dared to ask you for money?
Us.
You're Rahul's sister.
Yes, sir.
What are you doing here?
We're in dire straits sir.
I wash clothes and plates here.
The sister of Pune's new don,
and working as a maid.
I am proud of you and your father.
If you ever need anything
then don't hesitate.
Sir...
Rahul.
When those drops cool down,
they fall on earth as raindrops.
Understood?
Haha...
Thank God I am not too educated.
Why?
I would've lost my mind.
Not you, the teacher
would've lost his mind.
It's not that difficult, brother.
I'll teach you.
- Yes.
- Please don't teach me anything.
Rahulya, we know where Daya is.
Why the...
Where are you going, brother?
Continue studying.
I've to teach someone a lesson.
"Brother-in-law was sleeping
on the roof."
"I mistook him for you."
"Forgive me Ranaji,"
"I made a mistake."
Run. Run.
He's escaped.
Nanavare sir.
What are you doing here?
Pitya's boys went to Makwana Jewellers,
for extortion.
He was with them.
What am I hearing?
Why did you go with those goons?
I didn't know why they were going there.
They are my friends.
I went because they did.
Friends.
Where did you get this expensive phone?
Brother Pitya gifted me.
Brother Pitya gifted you!
Do you have the money to buy this?
Mother was sick and you
took her to a government hospital.
Brother Pitya gave me money
and I took her to a private hospital.
How dare you take money from gangsters?
How dare you?
Trying to show your father his place?
What are you doing?
What are you doing, Uday?
If mother found out she
would've committed suicide.
Do you know what he did?
I heard everything.
Sit son, give him some water.
- Padwal.
- Sir.
Call Pitya.
Right, sir.
Tell him orders are out for his encounter.
Okay, sir.
Constable Padwal speaking.
Orders are out for your encounter.
Within 24 hours your game's up.
What did he say?
Stop. Stop. Stop.
Sir...
Pitya is here. Pitya is here.
What Pitya?
Please save me, sir. Please save me.
What brings you here?
Padwal called saying there's
an order for my encounter.
That guy Patwardhan whom you shot,
turned out to be the
Home Minister's relative.
I made a mistake, sir.
I'll pay whatever is required.
I beg you, sir. Save me.
This is not my case, it's Uday's.
Uday.
Uday...
We're from the same village.
Please save me.
- I'll do whatever you want.
- See...
Please. Please.
- He's your hero?
- Save me, Uday.
Kick him.
No, sir.
If you don't kick him then
your father will shoot him.
No.
Not here,
Uday, outside the Police station.
What are you saying, brother?
Don't do it.
I beg you.
Kick him. His life is in your kick.
Kick me, Arun.
What are you waiting for?
Kick me. Kick me. Kick me.
His life depends on it, Arun.
Kick him hard.
What are you waiting for?
You listen to me, don't you?
Kick me hard.
Kick me. Kick me. Kick me.
He saved your life.
Thank you, sir.
As I said this is not my case,
it's Uday's case
Thank you, Uday...
Sorry... thank you...
Sorry, sir.
You got slapped seven times
by a Policeman.
But you didn't budge.
He's your hero.
One slap and he peed in his pants.
Sorry, father.
I made a mistake.
I won't do it again.
Here's your phone.
Sorry, father.
Forgive me.
Uday, continue this at home.
We've a job to do.
- Boss...
- Who is it?
Pakya.
Pick it up and put it on speaker.
Yes, Pakya.
Boss, I came to pick
up Siddhu from school.
But Siddhu isn't in school.
What do you mean?
I mean I looked everywhere
but he isn't here.
Find him, Pakya!
I will kill you if you don't find him!
- Pitya.
- Sir.
What are you doing here?
- Craving for some sweets.
- Sweets?
No, sir.
Don't waste your time.
Rahulya has grown too big.
Go after Rahulya.
Sir, that boy is very close to Rahulya.
If I get my hands on him,
Rahulya will come crawling.
That's the difference between
Rahul and you two fools.
Even criminals have a code.
They don't touch family and children.
Get lost.
Let's go.
I couldn't find, Siddhu.
What happened, Rahul?
Ganya, I told you to
keep two boys with Siddhu.
Didn't I tell you?
But I told Pakya...
If anything happens to him,
Ganya, I will kill you.
But.
Siddhu's here.
Where were you? Where were you?
It's your birthday, I went to get a cake.
Oh yes, Rahul, we completely forgot.
Next time if you go without telling me,
I will kill you.
Sorry.
Go get ready, let's cut the cake together.
Okay.
Come on.
- You must be hungry.
- Yes.
Come.
Oh wow, what brings you here today?
Why? Scared?
Me?
Why would I be scared?
Don't let anything happen to this child.
Sir, I will set the world on
fire if anyone lays a finger on him.
What is your relationship with him?
Him?
He's my life.
He's got no parents,
even I don't have any parents.
Who is that person who works
as a labour in the market yard?
And the woman who cleans dishes in homes,
who is she?
Rahul, you're treating these farmers,
just like Nanya treated your father.
You've already destroyed your life,
now you will destroy his life too.
Don't worry, sir.
I won't let him become a gangster like me.
I will make him the
godfather of gangsters.
A Policeman like you.
And do you know what I will become?
You know.
CM.
You've lost your mind.
You really think you're plastic.
You're plastic. The filth of this city.
I've no regrets.
Needless to say, I am going to rule.
And one more thing,
today this labour owns 300 acres.
How much?
300 acres?
But who is ploughing these 300 acres?
Your father? Your mother? Or your sister
Even I was born in Maharashtra.
And even I am the son of a farmer.
Even my father's land
was snatched from him.
But I didn't become a gangster like you.
I became their godfather.
A cop.
To eradicate goons like you.
Six months ago I bought only
one-acre land with my hard-earned money.
My father works in
the field every morning.
He's very happy.
What about you?
300 acres you claim?
Tomorrow you'll have 600 acres,
and later even 6000.
But in the end, you'll only need 6x3.
How much?
6x3.
Maharashtra's future CM.
Who is it?
Me.
Rahulya brother.
I had to come, Shinde.
You should've called me instead.
I told you to buy Jadhav's
land for 20 million,
but you didn't listen.
What...can I do, Rahulya brother?
The market's in a bad condition.
- Sit. Sit.
- Yes...
The market isn't bad,
your intention is bad.
I'll send him five million.
Five for him and 10 for me.
This is not the way,
we have given 25 first.
- Hello, sir.
- Hello.
- Happy birthday.
- It's okay.
- Leave it.
- Happy birthday.
Happy birthday, sir.
Rajveer, how are you?
All good, sir.
How is Law and Order in Pune?
Who would know better than you?
But everything will be fine in the future.
Because today's lawbreakers,
will become protectors of the law.
What do you mean?
Today's Robin Hood,
Tomorrow's MLA.
Maybe the future CM.
How much?
10 million.
40 more when we see Rahul's dead body.
You'll see it soon.
And I'll pay an extra 20.
Constable Padwal speaking
from Market Yard Police Station.
Yes.
Shinde's offered 70 million
to Pitya for killing you.
I see...
Is the news confirmed?
Yes, it's confirmed.
What did he say?
Cool as a cucumber.
But sir, now Shinde's life is in danger.
Hear him. Shinde's life is in danger.
He's no saint either.
This story began with Shinde,
and Rahul is its last link.
- Come on.
- What...
- What are you doing?
- Come on.
Rahulya brother, you're mistaken.
You offered money to Pitya for killing me.
No...
I know everything.
It was a mistake.
Please forgive me. Only once.
I made a promise to you. Remember.
- It was a mistake.
- Today I will fulfil it.
Rahulya bhai.
Ganya, take him away.
- No, Rahulya bhai.
- Come on.
Come on.
Please forgive me.
Please...I won't make
this mistake again.
Please forgive me. Only once.
I won't do it again.
Please forgive me.
Remember Shinde,
you said you'll tie me to the horses,
and I said I'll tie to you a bull.
In a pair.
I bought them especially for you.
Tie him up.
No Rahulya brother. I'll return your land.
Rahulya bhai.
You took my father's land.
You made him guard his own land,
humiliated him.
You're the reason my father,
mother, sister are not with me.
I lost everything because of you.
I will take this land back for my father.
Remember Shinde,
I shed blood on this land.
One day I will take it back.
Ganya, take his thumb impression.
Look Shinde. I took your land.
I took it.
I took it. I took it. I took it.
- Rahul, what are you doing?
- Leave him.
- Rahul...
- Leave me, Ganya.
Stay back or else I will kill you too.
Rahulya, he's dead.
Father! I got our land back!
Father!
I got my land back!
I got it!
I promised you, father.
Dutta...
Rahulya.
Did you misdial my number?
Father, I've some good news.
I got our land back from Shinde.
Look Rahulya,
that land belonged to my father.
I sold that land for
cheap to protect my children.
I'll never set foot on it again.
Listen to me, father.
Father.
Here comes, Rahulya.
Exactly.
Talk to him directly, Maurya uncle.
- All because of him.
- Yes.
Yeah.
You scored quiet high.
Come, sit.
Maurya uncle, all good?
How can it be good?
You want to snatch my means of living.
What are you saying?
Ganya, what did you tell him?
I told him to sell his land.
But he isn't listening.
- Rahul. Leave it, let's talk business.
- Seriously.
Look Maurya uncle,
I'm losing 50 million
because of two-acre land.
He's Mittal.
He wants to start a factory there.
Name your price.
You'll do it.
You're smart.
What the...
Rahul. Rahul.
What's all the drama?
What's so funny, huh?
Now laugh.
Rahul, what are you doing?
Can't laugh now?
Sorry, we know it's our fault.
You see my son scored good
marks in his class 12 exams,
and I didn't have to give
any donation for engineering as well.
What else can make a father happy, son?
But sorry...
- Give him a sweet...come on.
- Give him.
Sorry.
Please.
So Laugh.
Ganya, we won't take Maurya uncle's land.
We want this land.
I'll get you another piece of land.
Rahul, there's water behind his land.
I said I'll get you another land,
near the water.
- Where are you going?
- Something's come up.
I'll come along.
I am not a child, understand.
You don't have to follow me everywhere!
No one will come after me!
Brother Dutta...Rahul.
Father, I need to talk to you.
Speak.
Father, nothing seems good without you.
Not one bit without you guys.
You left willingly.
What will, father?
I told you to come and live with me.
Your house will reek of
dead bodies that you killed.
After killing the Corporator
you had a chance to reform.
But you were high on money, power.
Father, will you come
back if I quit everything?
No.
Surrender to the Police.
When you return after
serving time in jail,
we'll happily accept you in our house.
You know that's not possible, father.
I promise I will quit everything.
I am entering politics, father.
A party is offering me
a ticket and I will win too.
I want to see you and mother
smile like you two used to.
Come live with me.
I am lonely, father.
Very lonely.
Please smile for me, father.
Our situation didn't
take away our smiles, Rahul.
Your actions did.
The day you cleanse your sins,
I will smile.
Can I eat now?
I've a long day ahead of me.
Here comes Rahulya the don.
Rahul.
On me. I won't charge you for it.
I've some good news for you.
Come here.
Next week I am getting married.
With him.
And six months later
is my child's naming ceremony.
Do drop by if you have time.
He can't come.
His expiry date has expired.
Rahulya brother.
Manda, you're looking
awesome in this sari.
I will come if I am still alive
Glory to Lord Ganesha.
- Let's go to immersion duty.
- Yes, sir. Ready, sir.
Why is this bad luck calling
on such an auspicious day?
You see Rajveer, I called because
I've decided to do the Police's job today.
Please do it.
You just watch the fun.
We will.
We'll eradicate Rahul
and Ganya's entire gang.
Please do.
Don't stop us.
We won't.
Only enjoy.
We'll enjoy it.
Sir, we won't do anything?
They think they are doing it.
But Paaji's calling the shots.
That's true.
Come.
Please, sir.
Do you know where my journey began?
Market yard.
And you know,
this is where I lost my heart.
Tea shop?
Not the tea shop?
The owner.
Isn't she beautiful?
Manda.
I came to return your glasses.
I kept them with me as your memory.
But without you,
there is no memory.
Brother,
there's no one there.
She got married.
Come with me.
Where?
Don't ask questions.
Just come along.
(Sanskrit Chant)
"Glory to Lord Ganesha."
"You're my illusion,
you're my religion."
"My existence doesn't matter,"
"you're the eternal one."
"All sins are pardoned today,"
"your benevolence is divine."
"You're the one true Lord."
"You're Lord, you're destiny."
"You're the benefactor
of this world."
"You're a storm, you're the wind,"
"you're the waves,
you're the shore."
"You're the giver of happiness,
destroyer of sorrows."
"Without you,
I don't know what to do."
"You're my Lord Ganesha."
"Glory to Lord Ganesha."
"Whenever the world
refused to hold my hand,"
"I came to your threshold Lord."
"Not just my peace and serenity,"
"you mean everything to me, Lord."
(Sanskrit Chant)
"You're my sole support."
"You're the giver of happiness,
destroyer of sorrows."
"Without you,
I don't know what to do."
"You're my Lord Ganesha."
"You're my illusion,
you're my religion."
"My existence doesn't matter,"
"you're the eternal one."
"All sins are pardoned today,"
"your benevolence is divine."
"You're the one true Lord."
What are you doing?
Whose house is this?
Rahul.
What are you doing here?
Is this my child?
No.
It's mine.
Good.
Manda,
everything I touched turned to dust.
First my mother, then my father,
now you left me too.
Please forgive me, Manda.
Forgive me.
I made a big mistake.
Brother, shall we go?
We've to attend the immersion.
Call Ganya.
(Sanskrit Chant)
Yeah, Rahulya.
Ganya, I'm not coming.
Fine, go home.
I'll see you there.
- Who was it?
- Rahul.
He isn't coming.
He's going home.
Okay.
Rahul isn't coming here.
- He's at home.
- Why that...
Go and kill him in his house.
Come on.
"You're the giver of happiness,
destroyer of sorrows."
"Without you,
I don't know what to do."
"You're the giver of happiness,
destroyer of sorrows."
"Without you,
I don't know what to do."
"You're my Lord Ganesha."
(Sanskrit Chant)
"You reside in my heart,"
"I utter your name
with every breath."
"I am just a drop
in the ocean of life,"
"you dwell in me."
He's done.
I told you.
When this Sardar loses it,
everyone will be scared stiff.
Today, this Sardar has lost it.
(Sanskrit Chant)
See Rajveer,
we cleared the filth in the city.
Not completely.
What do you mean?
(Sanskrit Chant)
"Morya..."
"Ganpati. Ganpati. Ganpati.
Bappa Morya."
"Morya..."
Why you...
(Sanskrit Chant)
Shall we?
Not today, sir.
Just give me a day.
First I will perform
Ganya's cremation.
Finish Pitya and Daya,
and then you can even hang me.
If I hadn't arrived on time,
you wouldn't be alive for this crap.
It's my luck that I'm alive.
Go on, try your luck.
Wait.
Where are you going?
Going to get some tea.
Do you want some?
One for me too.
Two cups of tea.
Yes...
We're here.
Come on, they have arrived.
Come on, let's go.
Not now.
Catch him. Catch him.
Come on, let's go.
We won't spare him today.
Hey!
Hello.
- Siddhu.
- Yes, brother.
I'm in trouble.
Listen, tell the boys outside
the house to come to the marketyard.
Okay.
Okay, brother.
Look at the Mercedes.
You can't pay for the damages
even if you sell yourself.
Shinde, don't show off your money.
Don't forget this
land once belonged to me.
I paid money for it.
We all know for what price.
Stop it, Rahul.
I said it was my mistake.
You had a chance to reform.
We'll have half a meal,
but make an honest living.
I'll have a full square meal,
and with a sweet dish.
Your daughter slept with me.
Listen, everyone.
He can forcefully
snatch people's land,
but not Manda.
I've a list of monsters like you,
who ended in their grave
before they could swear in.
- Shoot him!
- Now he's your brother.
When your own family deserts you,
strangers become your kin.
First, he will rape your
sister and then kill her.
Out of the way everyone.
Rahul.
Look there.
Move.
Yes.
Sir, Dutta Patil speaking
from the market yard.
People are firing bullets here.
Do something, sir.
Or Rahulya will die.
Coming.
"The world is dirty."
"with bad intentions."
"Someone will come."
"instead of god."
"My last is written by his hand."
He's not over there.
He's hiding somewhere here.
Find the rascal.
Look here.
Well Daya Pitya, game over.
Sit over there.
What for?
We've a recording of Ganya's murder.
That rascal Rahulya
is hiding somewhere here.
We'll first kill
him and then come back.
What will the Police do until then?
Play marbles?
You can do anything you want.
Let's go.
"The world is dirty."
"with bad intentions."
"Will kick hard,"
"on the dirty."
"Someone will come."
"instead of god."
"My last is written by his hand."
Come on, get up.
Get this dirt out of here.
Come on.
And what about you?
Sir, I want to surrender myself.
Right decision.
Brother.
What are you doing here, Siddhu?
There's no need for it now.
There is.
Why?
After mother died I swore
I'll kill you publicly.
My name's Siddharth.
Siddharth Maruti Kamble.
Remember something.
You did the right thing.
- That's more like it.
- The mutt's dead.
Hey cops, take us along now.
We'll be out tomorrow.
And we'll rule over
Maharashtra when we come out.
Maharashtra isn't your property.
Rahul.
Father,
I didn't listen to you.
Forgive me.
Sir, I am different.
I'll survive.
Nothing lasts in this world,
except for plastic.
(Sanskrit Chant)
Smile my father.
Smile for my father.
The day your sins are cleansed,
I will smile again.
(Sanskrit Chant)
But in the end,
you'll need only 6x3.
(Sanskrit Chant)