"1947."
"In the massacre during
the partition..."
Anybody alive!
"Indians...
learn from us how to kill."
"Where thousands of families
were destroyed,"
"several families got
a new lease on life."
"One such family was
Tara Singh and Sakina."
Muslim!
You say she's a Muslim!
There. Now she will be a Sikh!
"All this wasn't as easy as it looked."
"Life was filled with happiness,"
"when one day..."
Our motherland, our people,
our country, is Pakistan.
"Facing several difficulties,"
"along his wife,
the mother of his child..."
You will not be given a visa.
Iqbal sir.
You think Tara can't go to Pakistan
without a single seal!
No power or border can stop me
from uniting my son with his mother!
Long live India!
"After teaching his father-in-law
Ashraf Ali a lesson in humanity,"
"Tara Singh brought Sakina
back to India."
"The swings are out again,"
"and the fruits have ripened."
"Life is short,"
"For India,
it was a matter of celebration."
"But in Pakistan..."
"politics had taken a different turn."
Hang Ashraf Ali!
Ashraf Ali's a traitor!
"How could Major Hamid Iqbal
take all this lying down?"
"Forty soldiers of his battalion
were dead."
"Because of a Hindu."
"Indians....whom."
"Indian...
whom he detested completely."
"Before the independence,"
Hamid Iqbal was a captain
in the British Indian Army."
"And yet,
during the gory partition,"
"he couldn't save his family
from Indians."
*Praying.*
"As a result,"
"hatred coursed through his veins."
"For Hindus and Indians."
"He had only one purpose in life."
"Gazwa-E-Hind"
(Invade and Conquer India)."
Mercy.
Sir, mercy.
Mercy has no value
in the eyes of religion.
My father and my mother begged
for mercy.
My siblings.
Your people killed all of them.
In Delhi.
That was your country.
You killed my men.
This is my country.
Now I will kill.
This is my country too.
For four generations--
Is this your country?
Fine.
Prove this is your country.
Captain.
Get it.
Gita.
Or Quran.
Sir, you all know about
the Tara Singh and Sakina case.
Tara Singh killed 40 soldiers
and fled to India.
And he was aided
by Sakina's father Ashraf Ali.
We are receiving backlashes
from everywhere, sir.
Please, have a look.
The politicians aren't taking any action,
nor is the army.
I want Ashraf Ali
to be sentenced to death.
"Even after getting
Ashraf Ali sentenced to death
He wasn not satisfied."
"He had another desire suppressed
in his heart."
"The desire to sentence the killer
of his men to death."
"But this was an impossible task."
"Because Tara Singh
was far beyond his reach,
some where in India."
"To be floored on someone's smile."
"To share someone's bane."
"To spread love..."
"Life is all about that."
Imtihaan, wake up.
Yes, brother.
Yeah...
I was awake, brother.
"Curse you."
"What have you done?"
"I was sleeping, brother."
"But when I heard your voice,"
"I got up all of a sudden..."
"And this happened."
Exactly like his uncle Darmiyaan.
Brother, do we unload the goods
for the refugees or not?
Yes, unload it.
Get to work.
Right away, brother.
Sir, this General Hamid Iqbal
has lost his mind.
He's totally obsessed
with 'Ghazwa-E-Hind', sir.
His mortars have destroyed
our 'Kaali Mandir' Base completely.
War is inevitable, sir.
We'll infiltrate all the way
to Lahore and shoot him.
Once I spot him,
I am going to kill the bloody Idiot.
Roger, sir. Yes, sir.
Oh! Tara Singh ji.
Jai Hind, sir.
Come, please.
How are you, Tara Singh Ji?
I am great.
What about your family?
Your son?
Is he studying?
Children these days don't study.
They only watch films.
They have to watch
the first-day first show.
- Please, have a seat.
- But I've kept my son in check.
In check?
He's in my control.
What have you thought?
What do you want him to be?
Sir, I want him
to be an officer like you.
God willing.
Sir, why did you call me here?
I wanted to know
if your union can arrange 50 trucks.
Why not?
Just give the orders.
No, not yet.
There are chances of war,
Tara Singh Ji.
I want a backup ready.
We are prepared, sir.
Whenever you say the word.
I know.
Thank you.
Okay, sir. Jai Hind.
Tara Singh Ji.
Your in-laws have sent something
for you.
My in-laws?
Usually, it's only arms and explosives.
This time they have sent some gifts.
Madam ji.
Look what's arrived for you
from Sargodha.
Madam ji.
Tangerines from Sargodha!
Colonel sir sent these for you.
The colonel...
Are you hurt?
Here, eat.
What happened now?
With time,
your care for me keeps increasing.
Another thing that keeps increasing,
madam ji.
What is that?
My love for you.
Then sing for me again.
It's been so long.
"Fly away O bird,
with a candy in your beak."
"Convey my message,
and I'll be obliged."
"The swings are out again,"
"and the fruits have ripened."
"Life is short, nights are too long."
"Come home O traveller,"
"without you I am incomplete."
"Thus arrived the weather
of romantic songs."
"Eyes lie in wait looking
for beloveds that have separated."
"Your memories keep me awake all night."
"All my songs are my heart's desires."
"Come home O traveller,"
"without you I am incomplete."
Bro, I've shined the car like a star.
Are we going or...
We're not going.
At least let me finish my song.
But, bro, we've to go.
Go where?
At Pishorilal's.
To make a delivery.
- Huh?
- Yes.
You go.
How can I go?
Is Jeetey at home?
He's at college.
What's so funny?
I was thinking whether...
I should tell you or not?
Say it.
But if I tell you,
Jeetey will beat me up.
Now I will beat you.
I prefer Jeetey.
Lately, he has been hanging
out at Sharda Bhavan.
With Ved Keemti Lal drama company.
Ved Keemti Lal is here?
Yes.
"I searched the entire universe."
"I never could find anyone like you..."
Wonderful!
Outstanding!
"I searched the entire universe."
Mahiwaal...enter!
"Handsome creation of God..."
"Honest and truthful."
My Soni, I am here.
- Enter, my boy.
- Mahi.
Come with me.
Let my Soni go, you bloody wretch.
- Mahi.
- Come with me now.
- She is mine.
- Hey...
I said she is mine.
She is my life.
Stop. Stop. Stop.
What are you doing, Jeetey?
Why are you speaking
in Dilip Kumar style, son?
Your dialogue should be heard
all the way to the last row.
This is a play.
Bring some pitch in your voice.
Pitch. Like Prithvi Raj Kapoor.
Right. Prithvi Raj Kapoor.
Here you go.
You wretch, let my Soni go.
Or else I will behead
you with my sword.
Mahi.
Don't touch her
or I will behead you right here.
Mahi.
Stop. Stop. Stop.
What are you doing, Jeetey?
What are you doing?
Mahiwaal was a lover.
He shouldn't be holding a sword.
But a flower.
- Yes.
- Flower.
He shouldn't be cursing.
He should be singing.
Song.
Song. Okay, song.
Listen to me.
I want you to sing a song,
that leaves people in awe.
I will leave you in shock and awe.
Like two lovebirds free,
Lovers are meant to be.
As your bird flees,
My bird is left to plea.
Like two lovebirds free,
Like two lovebirds--
Father.
Get down.
"He's in college," you said.
You didn't go to college?
And this?
What are you dressed as?
Mahwaal. Mahwaal.
He's busy being a lovebird!
keep telling everyone,
my son will be a successful man.
He will become an officer.
But look at him...
He'd be lucky if he could
become a truck driver.
He's been missing college for 10 days.
What?
Don't pretend you don't know.
Where are your books?
Where else but in my room?
Such attitude.
He hasn't even read his books.
Tara ji is right, son.
You need to study.
I don't want to study.
- You are going to study...
- Tara.
See...you are spoiling him.
Over here. Come over here.
Let go of her hand.
Keep him locked
in the room all day.
No food for him.
- I will fix him.
- But...
I will fix him.
Close!
Come on.
Come here.
Uncle's friend Keshav lives
in Chandigarh.
I'll speak to him
and get him into a hostel.
Hostel, Tara ji?
So far away.
Why not?
Even you studied at a hostel.
And look what you became -
a madam ji.
Even he will become an officer.
I am not going to Chandigarh.
- I'll see how you won't go.
- Oh! Tara ji.
What--
What are you guys looking at?
Scram!
See...that's the company he keeps.
This company is what spoiled him.
I will break your legs
if you don't study.
Stop. Stop it, both of you.
Look, don't feed him until
he doesn't study.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Okay, Tara ji.
What are you looking at?
I am hungry.
What took you so long to get the food?
I am starving.
Yes, of course.
You are extra hungry today.
Naughty boy.
You are the mother of a strong,
budding young man.
I feel hungry after every two hours.
Come on, feed me.
Shut up and eat.
I have to come up
with several excuses for you.
It's a sin.
Feeding a hungry person is not a sin.
It's a good deed.
Your enemies will starve.
Hamid Iqbal?
Jeetey. Get this out of your mind.
Why?
He hung my grandpa,
and granny died from grief.
And I cannot even talk about it?
You think I am a kid.
Jeetey, stop thinking about all this.
I want to know,
why haven't you attended college
for 10 days.
Nor tuitions.
Don't you care about
your father's feelings?
And what about my feelings?
I told you weeks ago,
Bittu and Pradyuman's fathers
bought a motorcycle for them.
Every day they--
Motorcycle. Motorcycle. Motorcycle.
Quickly. Wipe your mouth.
The chances of a war are growing.
We have to go dig, trenches.
to escape the bombings.
Like we did in '65 war.
One thing confuses me.
People over there want peace,
even we want peace.
But these politicians make things worse.
Come on. Eat.
- Am I right?
- Absolutely.
Eat your food.
Did you feed Jeetey?
You said no food for him.
Even if I did,
you didn't have to starve him.
What kind of a mother are you?
Keep seated.
I will feed him.
You have a meeting, don't you?
My son is studying.
Sit down.
Son.
Eat some food.
I am studying.
Don't disturb me.
Son, I made a mistake.
Please eat it.
I don't want to eat it.
Let it be. I'll feed him.
I'll see how he doesn't eat.
Trying to act smart with me.
Telling me he doesn't want to eat.
You dropped some food
on the book too.
Son...
you don't know how happy I am today.
Sometimes I get worried.
Do you want me
to keep studying like this?
Why not?
Then I am going to stay with you.
Yes. You are not going anywhere.
Then get me a motorcycle.
Son...ask for something else.
No motorcycle.
It's prone to accidents.
No. No motorcycle.
All my friends have a motorcycle.
I am only asking for a motorcycle.
Get him one.
Okay.
But I have a condition.
You have to secure first rank.
- First rank?
- Hmm.
- Me?
- Yes
Only one out of forty
boys gets first rank.
Just say it if you don't want
to buy it for me.
You can be that one among forty.
What is this?
Dharmendra.
Jeetey!
Stop. Stop right there.
Is this what you call studying?
Father, I...
What father?
You are going to Chandigarh.
You will study there
and become an officer.
I won't go to Chandigarh.
I will go to Mumbai
and become an actor.
Tara.
My knees are aching from sitting
there for such a long time.
I don't want to stay here.
What happened?
Why are you hitting my son?
Come here, Jeetey.
- Jeetey? Where are you going, son?
- What happened?
Had your uncle been still alive,
you wouldn't dare to do this.
Aunty, he doesn't study.
He's only obsessed with films.
Even you used to see films.
Don't you?
And you used to sing all day
"Let the heart burn."
You had your share of fun
when you were young.
This is his time to have fun,
so let him.
Let him watch films.
Look at what happened to me.
I became a truck driver.
I don't want him
to become a truck driver--
No. I am taking him
to Chandigarh tomorrow itself.
He will stay at the hostel
and become an officer.
Brother. It's his birthday today.
We returned three days earlier
from our pilgrimage,
only to celebrate his birthday.
And you say he leaves
for Chandigarh tomorrow.
- Right.
- Leave it, grandma.
He only remembers that
I am useless, good-for-nothing.
He keeps humiliating me.
- Slapping me in front of my friends.
- Tara!
Keeps telling me to study all the time.
Heard that?
Am I saying anything wrong, son?
I don't want to celebrate my birthday.
- Son. Jeetey.
- Where are you going?
Jeetey.
Your father is not wrong, son.
Are you happy now?
Want to go for a ride?
"I set out...on my vehicle."
"On the roads and streets..."
"I came to a turn,"
"where I lost my heart."
"God knows when I passed Amritsar,"
"and when I arrived in Lahore."
"I lost my heart."
"I came to a turn,"
"where I lost my heart."
"I met my companion at that turn."
"This Jat lost his heart."
"I fell asleep under
the cool shade of her tresses."
"When I woke up, I ran."
"Breaking all barricades and signals."
"I lost my heart."
"I came to a turn,"
"where I lost my heart."
"She blushed and flinched."
"The moment she woke up from her sleep,"
"I told her, listen to me, dear."
"She got scared and ran behind."
"She thought,"
"a thief had creeped,
"or sneaked into her house."
"I lost my heart."
"I came to a turn,"
"where I lost my heart."
Want to go to Bombay?
Become a hero?
First go to Chandigarh
and finish your studies.
I am missing our son.
It's been only a month,
but feels like years.
I was thinking about that too.
Whenever I would go
to the hostel to study,
mom and dad must've felt very lonely.
Right?
Mom once told me...
When I separated
from my parents during the partition,
father would stay up all night crying.
Honestly...life seems incomplete
without children.
Isn't it?
Then let's go to Chandigarh.
Hello.
Yes.
Yes, he's here.
Brother, it's the captain on the line.
The colonel wants to speak to you.
The enemy's action is well intended.
They want to take over Ram Tekdi, sir.
Sir, this feature will serve
him a bloody firm base.
Sir, they have destroyed
all our vehicles.
Sir, we can't get the ammunition there.
We need reinforcements.
Major, control yourself.
Sir, it's difficult to control.
My boys are dying without ammunition.
- I wish we have the obstacle system was like DCB.
- Colonel GS has called up.
Air support tonight is not possible.
Can I speak to Bhargav?
Thank you.
Bhargav, I am sending CHTs.
CHTs?
That's the only option I had, my boy.
Keep fighting.
Don't give up.
Reinforcements are coming
from the DMA.
But tonight...
The platoon's honour is in your hands.
- Got it?
- Got it, sir.
Come on, buck up!
Sir, the CHTs have arrived.
Oh, fantastic.
Load the ammunition.
Who is in charge of them?
What is your name?
Tara Singh, sir.
The firing from enemy mortars
and rifles shows no signs of ceasing.
You can hear them, right?
You have to dodge the shelling,
and deliver the ammunition
to our soldiers.
You won't get scared, will you?
Sir, maybe you don't know
who Tara Singh is.
You should ask the enemy
See you, sir.
Load the ammunition!
Go.
Here, take them quickly.
Move, move, move.
Hurry.
Here, catch.
Kuljeet, we got the ammunition.
Load your guns.
Load your guns now.
Nara-e-takbir!
Allah-o-Akbar!
Baldev!
Alpha One for Charlie
heavy vehicle advancing towards us.
Sir, our plan has failed.
We cannot take over Ram Tekdi now.
The infidels have received ammunition.
Tara Singh?
With the grace of Allah,
I finally found you.
I looked all over for you.
Now everyone will be looking for you.
Let the enemy think they are winning,
and let them come forward.
You keep falling back.
Retreat.
- Brigadier Salim.
- Sir.
Let's play some war games.
Glory to India!
Har Har Mahadev!
Jai Bhavani!
Fire.
- Please be a little patient.
- Mom.
- Why aren't you give us any information?
Mom, father?
My Tara Singh is okay.
Tara is on the hill.
Helping people.
He will be fine.
Please be a little patient.
I can understand your emotion.
Please allow us.
We want to go take
a look ourselves on the hills.
I can't allow you
to anywhere, ma'am.
Who told you this incident occurred
on the hill?
It occurred on the other side
of the hill.
Do you have any idea
how dangerous and volatile it is?
Can't you hear the shelling?
Do you know how many men,
how many lives are at stake here?
My own officer Major Bhargav
is right now--
Colonel.
I need to speak to the Div.
Headquarters right away.
The matter will go up to the UNO.
Five of our men and three CHT drivers
have been captured by the enemy.
According to intelligence information,
Indian Army's Major Bhargav,
Capt. Tiwari,
Subedaar Prakash,
two other army soldiers,
driver Pooran Singh,
Ranjeet, Tara Singh...
These seven people are
in Pakistan's captivity.
But the Pakistani army
has denied these claims,
and accused the Indian army
of infiltration.
The Pakistani government is also denying
any prisoner of war.
The government even goes on to say,
they are either missing in action
or died in the encounter.
Again and again
the same bloody question.
Madam, we are in a war-like situation.
Don't you get it?
And I am already in war.
Please, calm down.
You must understand
her situation as well.
She deserves to know the truth.
Whether he's actually
in their captivity or...
We understand, sir.
I am telling you this again.
Don't worry, we're doing our job.
But nobody is above the country.
We know the enemy here.
We all do, don't we?
We're constantly in touch with the UNO.
The circumstances are such,
that we need to be prepared
for all kinds of eventualities here.
We need to be prepared
for all kinds of eventualities.
Mom.
Allah...nothing can happen to my Tara.
Pull yourself together, mom.
- Tara will come back.
- Mom, pull yourself together.
"O beloved, don't sever
this bond and leave me."
"I forsake the world,
but don't leave me."
"That can never happen,"
"don't be afraid if it does."
"I will come running back on your call."
"Come home O traveller,"
"without youI am incomplete."
"without you I am incomplete."
"Come home O beloved traveller."
"I will be grateful to God."
Mohammad Gul Khan.
Next to Baba Chote Shah's shrine.
Lahore, Pakistan.
"He alone is brave,"
"who fights for the one in need."
"He may get cut into pieces,"
"But he will never leave
the battlefield."
"He alone is brave,"
"If you want to play the game of love,"
"Then step onto my path with
your head on the palm."
"If you want to play the game of love,"
"Then step onto my path
with your head on the palm."
"When you place your feet on this path,"
"Give Me your head,
and do not listen to what others say."
"When you place your feet on this path,"
"Give Me your head,
and do not listen to what others say."
"He may get cut into pieces,"
"But he will never leave
the battlefield."
Keep your belongings,
your passport and visa in your hand.
Indian spies are infiltrating
us using forged documents.
Is anyone of those bastards here?
Everybody, get off the bus now.
Here. You may go.
Thank you, sir.
Next.
224853.
Forward line of all troupes--
- Wahid Khan.
- Yes, sir.
- From Lucknow, are you?
- Yes.
I see.
I've heard you people
are treated unfairly.
That's not true, sir.
Except for a few handful incidents,
it's very peaceful out there.
Peaceful, is it?
Come with me.
Go on.
Next.
Come, mister. Come here.
- He says it's very peaceful there.
- What is wrong?
What is the matter, sir?
I am a Muslim.
Every Muslim who thinks
he's lucky to be living in India,
deserves this.
Malik.
Come on.
You say it's peaceful.
And you call yourself a Muslim.
And you praise the infidels.
True Muslim.
Go.
Passport.
Passport!
Ashfaq.
Yes...yes, sir.
Isn't that your name?
Yes, sir.
And I am a Pakistani.
I live in Multan.
I had gone to Aligarh at my uncle's place.
For my aunt's wedding.
Amazing. Amazing.
By the way,
what do those infidels say
about Pakistan.
You better not ask, sir.
What do they say?
Promise me you won't get mad at me.
What do they say?!
The Indian army says that Pakistani army
is a bunch of cowards.
They don't have any respect for you.
They say we defeated them in '48,
again in '65.
If we go to war again,
we'll defeat them again.
And build a new Bangladesh.
Enough!
Have you heard about
Major General Hamid Iqbal?
Yes.
Yes, sir.
We had a small encounter at Ram Tekdi.
He blew them up.
If we go to war again,
we'll break them into pieces.
We'll soak their lands red,
and their flag in green.
If we go to war, sir.
Then you will experience
my blood boil too.
I will bathe the enemy
in their own blood.
So be it.
So be it!
The youngsters of Pakistan are amazing.
Bravo.
Goodbye, sir.
Who was that boy that just left here?
And who are you?
Major Anwar Ali, ISI.
Give me a copy of his passport, quick.
You got to be kidding me, son.
The ISI can sniff anyone out like a dog.
They will investigate you.
Get your entire details out.
And if they learn...
that you are Tara Singh's son
then you're as good as dead.
So take my advice, son,
eat something and go back to India.
Without my father?
Whenever I see tears
in my mother's eyes,
I want to set the world on fire.
I fear nothing.
I'll deal with whatever comes my way.
You got to be kidding me, son.
Have these Lahori Chole-Bhature first.
You won't stop licking your fingers.
Here.
Tell me about my father.
Any news?
Son, since I received your letter,
I've been busy gathering information
about your father.
The first thing I did,
was send your uncouth aunt home
with her idiot sons.
And then General Rani...
General Rani is a popular courtesan.
- From General--
- Tell me about my father.
I am telling you about your father.
Tell me.
General Rani is the one true queen.
So I made friends with her cook,
treated him to English liquor,
and got him to spill all the secrets.
Understood?
So I found out...
Some Indian soldiers and truck drivers
were captured from the Pathankot border.
They have been locked away.
Hidden.
Secret.
One thing is clear, son.
My friend is alive.
"And the other news is,"
"They are all being held
in Kot Lakhpat jail."
"Mom...do you know,
I met granduncle."
"With his help,"
I got hold of the map of
Kot Lakhpat jail."
"And found out that father
and the other POWs,"
"are being kept
in a high secretive cell,
let alone no ordinary inmate,"
"even human rights and the red cross
aren't allowed here."
"Getting there is impossible."
"But I will."
"I will bring my father back."
"Don't worry."
"As grandma always says,"
"when all doors are closed,
God opens new doors."
O' Jeetey, my baby.
"My eyes seek you..."
Farid.
We were supposed to meet here
after the prayer meeting.
Sultan bhai is here from Muslimpura.
Greetings, Mr. Khan.
Greetings, Ranger.
He's brought some consignment
from the cross border.
I am just tallying the goods.
Tell Muskaan to take care of this job.
Muskaan hasn't returned from college--
Father. Father...it was a great day today.
Muskaan is back.
Come here, my child.
Father. Father. Father...
- You know my friend Rihana.
- Yes.
Her brother Murtuza went
to Bombay, India.
So this time I asked him,
to get me a photograph
and autograph of Rajesh Khanna.
See. Dear, Muskaan.
Father, please let me meet
Rajesh Khanna once.
I'll do anything you say.
But meeting Rajesh Khanna
in these conditions is impossible.
Uncle, you know
I can do anything for my father.
Listen to me.
Listen to me first.
Abdul Ali and Gullu
has brought a new cook.
Go and meet him.
I am going over
to General Rani's place.
That Gullu must have brought
some idiot again, father.
I am not doing it.
We have no other option, dear.
Eid is around the corner.
Orders are pouring in.
And we are short of cooks.
- Okay, fine...fine.
- Okay then. We'll get going.
Was Major Anwar from the ISI here?
Yeah, so?
He's got pictures
of some Indian spy again.
Did you take a look at their faces?
We all look the same.
Whether it's on this side or that side.
Before the partition,
we used to live together peacefully.
But only God can save us now.
And yes. Stick it over there.
And check the new cook thoroughly.
- Fine.
- Let's go, mister.
Rehman. Get the knife.
What if it's your picture?
Anwar Ali has seen you.
I think it's my picture.
Then let's get out of here, Jeetey.
But where will we go?
Kurbaan Khan has already seen me.
You said if I get this job,
it will be easier for me
to get to my father.
So I must get this job.
But how, Jeetey? How?
Hey...
Excuse me.
Can I give you a hand?
This is Ashfaq.
My nephew.
- He is a really good cook.
- Yes, he is.
Once you taste his biryani,
then you'll never stop licking
your fingers.
I see...
so I need to test this Indian hero.
Indian hero?
Judging by your style,
you look just like Rajesh Khanna.
Even you look nothing short of Mumtaz.
Uh-huh?
- Listen.
- yes.
He's come all the way from Multan.
Especially for this job.
If he gets the job,
it will be a big load off our chest.
And what about him?
Test me.
Come on.
By the way, I want to dedicate
a few lines to your beauty.
Go ahead.
Your beauty rivals Taj's grand fame,
You are so enchanting,
I wonder what's your name.
They call me God's grace,
flowers' golden hour,
- Oh.
- They call me God's grace,
flowers' golden hour,
They call me Muskaan,
my beauty empowers.
By the way, you seem
a fan of Hindi films.
Not more than you.
What do you think of Saira Banu?
Honestly speaking...
not more beautiful than you.
You have a way with words.
From your attitude, gait and speech,
you don't look like a cook.
- What?
- See...got you.
You didn't tell me your real purpose.
Do you want to know the truth?
I don't expect it,
but please do.
What's keeping you?
Coming.
You didn't tell me yet.
I want to go to jail.
What?
After getting beaten up by you.
So that my name's
on the list of your lovers.
Allah.
By the way, jokes apart.
The truth is I am an actor,
and I came here looking
for a job to act.
Actor? You?
Exactly. Like Rajesh Khanna, Devanand.
I want this job to make ends meet,
on the side.
Understood?
I know the initial steps
to make a biryani.
You can teach me the rest.
I need to make the ends meet, you see.
Please.
Do you act like you make biryani?
Seriously?
Do you have an earthen pot?
There, in the storeroom.
Shall I get it for you?
I can get it myself.
Mister, couldn't find the pot yet?
Coming. Just looking for the pot.
Coming.
Do I get the job?
This is Hotel Kamyaab.
Getting a job here isn't easy.
You keep singing
and I'll keep thinking.
"The passion, the mischief,"
"Finesses and exquisiteness,"
"You are beautiful..."
"From head to toe."
"My heart sways...it sways."
"Like an angel...
an angel it sees you."
"My heart sways...it sways."
"My heart can't stop swaying."
"Your attitude is unique."
"My heart's a fan of yours."
"Your tresses are as black
as the cloud."
"Like the cool shade under the sun."
"Your eyes shower me with grace,"
"I feel blessed."
"How can I forget...your blessings."
"You are beautiful..."
"From head to toe."
"My heart sways...it sways."
"Like an angel...
an angel it sees you."
"My heart sways...it sways."
"My heart can't stop swaying."
"Every word seems like wishes,"
"you finally included me in them."
"Finally I've achieved
a part of your heart."
"Your heart is just like you."
"It's making me happy."
"Wherever you go,
you spread light."
"You are beautiful..."
"From head to toe."
"My heart sways...it sways."
"Like an angel...
an angel it sees you."
"My heart sways...it sways."
"My heart can't stop swaying."
"God doesn't create faces like
this anymore."
"From which you can't take
your eyes off."
"One that brings peace
to your heart."
"You are beautiful..."
"From head to toe."
Mom, everything is fine now.
I got the job.
I am very close to father.
Just wait till Eid.
All our happiness will return.
Farid.
Did you make preparations
for Kot Lakhpat Jail?
Yes, father.
You, Muskaan, Fauzia, Akram along
with seven other people.
Did you include him?
No, father. He's been included
on General Rani's team.
Son, he's been requesting me
for three days,
to be included on this team.
Oh yes.
He said he was writing
some story on jails.
Take him along.
This way the poor boy can
complete his research.
So...?
Father, I am coming.
Allah...look at your tears.
Thank you.
Thanks to you, I can complete my story.
And...my story?
Eidi (gift).
Eidi (gift)?
I need to get ready Kot Lakhpat--
I have decided.
This year for Eidi,
I will ask father for this new cook.
Indian Prime Minister Mrs. Indira Gandhi
and the President of Pakistan are...
Yes, father.
Hurry up, child.
Get those 12 pots loaded.
But Asfaq was supposed to do that.
We always had our doubts about him.
He's been missing since last night.
Okay, father.
I'll take care of it.
Yes, hurry up.
Such weird kids.
"We were in love,"
"We were meant to be together,"
"So many things were left untold,"
Tomorrow at Eid,
she will talk to her father
about marrying me.
What?
What are you saying?
I made a big mistake.
I should have never chosen this path.
I have no right to play
with anyone's life.
For my personal gains.
She is innocent.
I must find another way...
"So many things were left untold,"
"The saga...of our love."
It's a good thing you are here.
Maybe I could have never
told you this personally.
My name isn't Asfaq.
It's Jeetey.
Charanjeet Singh.
I was on one of those posters.
I came from India
on a fake passport and visa,
to find my father.
To get him out of here.
He's locked away in Kot Lakhpat jail,
without any reason or crime.
"Meant to be together,"
You could do your duty as a Pakistani.
Don't worry about me.
I am Tara Singh's son.
Under every circumstance,
I will do my duty as a son.
"That was a moment to rejoice."
"And this is a moment of sorrow."
Muskaan.
"A life wasted away,"
My name isn't Asfaq.
It's Jeetey.
Charanjeet Singh.
You could do your duty as a Pakistani.
"A life meant to be spent together,"
"Meant to be spent together,"
Just once...
Swear on me and say
you are not an Indian spy.
And you just came here looking
for your father.
I swear I'll cross 100 seas,
to unite you with your father.
Do you see anything but the truth
in my eyes?
"Whatever your decision might be."
"Just let me know."
"Whatever is in my destiny."
"Unite me with that person."
"Unite me. Unite me."
"Unite me."
"Every time I open my eyes,"
"after prayers,"
"show me the face,"
"of my loved one."
"Unite me."
"Let's be destroyed once again."
"Let's fall in love with you."
"Let's get shattered again."
"The promise my heart made to you,"
"is known only by me or my God."
"I want to keep walking
in your direction, beloved."
"Let's fall in love with you."
"It was with God's will,
"that I gave my heart to you."
"Now I live every day of my life,"
"only for you."
"It was with God's will,
"that I gave my heart to you."
"Now I live every day of my life,"
"only for you."
"I am not one of those people,
who part ways..."
"midway somewhere."
"Let's fall in love with you."
"Let's get shattered again."
My son has come
to watch the Indian prisoners.
He thinks they are very dangerous.
Let him get over his fear.
- Jailer.
- Yes, sir.
Bring those prisoners out.
Today is Eid.
They deserve some festivities.
My wish comes
to my lips as supplication of mine...
O God!
May like the candle be the life of mine!
My wish comes to my lips
as supplication of mine...
Please, brother.
I'll take this to the General.
Hey, where are you going?
The general said the prisoners
deserve some sweets--
Mister. Mister.
They are our workers.
- Happy Eid.
I am Muskaan.
Kurbaan Khan's daughter.
- Subedaar.
- Sir.
Go grab the sweets.
Give me the sweets.
Give me the sweets!
Father...
What happened?
My father...
He isn't with them.
He isn't.
You bloody Indians don't deserve
any compassion.
Put them all back in the cell.
Take them away.
Long Live India!
They are just six.
Where's the seventh one?
Their boss...that Sardar,
the truck driver.
He made trouble could of days ago.
We've put him in solitary confinement.
Do you have kerosene?
Yes.
When you get your chance...
Where is this Asfaq?
Father, it's Eid.
So he's staying with his uncle.
I am so tired and sleepy,
that I can't keep my eyes open.
Time to open your eyes, Khan sir.
Father?
Uncle, you...?
Where is my father?
Father was never caught, son.
Then where is he?
Brother?
Tara Ji!
Thank God.
The currents took me back to my country.
The locals saved my life
and took me to a hospital.
I had no papers or documents.
And I was in a coma.
So how could anyone inform
you about me?
Jeetey...
Jeetey?
What happened to Jeetey?
Pakistan...
Pakistan?
Why Pakistan?
To look for you.
And you let him go.
- I tried...
- You let my son go!
- I tried to stop him.
- You let him go to Pakistan!
Tara.
Don't get angry.
What were you doing, aunty?
- We tried to stop him.
- How could he go over there?
He left without telling us.
He left a letter.
What letter...
We tried to stop him.
Read this letter.
How could he go to Pakistan?
Mom, you say I shouldn't go
to Pakistan.
Then what should I do?
Take part in plays,
watch films, study in Chandigarh?
What do I do when my father is missing?
Shouldn't I go looking for him?
Tara Singh's son.
I am going.
I will bring father back.
Without him, there is no you,
no me and no family.
Aunty...
He...
My son is there...
I want my Jeetey back, Tara Ji.
Tara... I want my Jeetey.
I want my Jeetey back.
He is definitely
in some kind of trouble.
He hasn't written
to me for a long time.
And...and that Hamid Iqbal...
Jeetey
Calm down.
Don't worry.
I will bring Jeetey back.
I will bring our Jeetey back.
No one can lay a finger on him.
I will bring Jeetey back.
"O Master of the two worlds,"
"Hear my prayers."
"Hear my wishes."
"My prayers for the apple of my eye."
"Wherever he is,
always protect him."
"Every moment,
keep him in Your sights."
"Keep him in Your sights."
"Just keep him in Your sights."
"Don't let the scorching sun harm him."
"Don't let the rains make him ill."
"Keep him covered with
Your own hands."
"Keep him away from harm's way,"
"bless him with Your grace."
"Keep him in Your sights."
"Just keep him in Your sights."
Crush India!
The next Friday prayers
will take place in Delhi!
Crush India!
The next Friday prayers
will take place in Delhi!
Crush India!
The next Friday prayers
will take place in Delhi!
Crush India!
The next Friday prayers
will take place in Delhi!
Crush India!
The next Friday prayers
will take place in Delhi!
Crush India!
The next Friday prayers
will take place in Delhi!
Crush India!
The next Friday prayers
will take place in Delhi!
Crush India!
The next Friday prayers
will take place in Delhi!
Crush India!
The next Friday prayers
will take place in Delhi!
Crush India!
The next Friday prayers
will take place in Delhi!
Crush India!
If your wishes exceed your capacity,
then you don't need enemies
to destroy you.
Get lost.
The next Friday prayers
will take place in Delhi!
Crush India!
The next Friday prayers
will take place in Delhi!
Crush India!
The next Friday prayers
will take place in Delhi!
It was my bad luck that
I went to see my parents.
If I hadn't,
then your father wouldn't have taken
in a Hindu boy.
He's worried about other's families,
but not his own family.
We don't have anything to eat.
Now look at your father's condition.
He's running from pillar to post.
He's on the run.
The police are chasing after him.
We have nothing left to eat.
No food.
Are we going
to survive on these chillies?
Your father is so stupid.
Trying to save others family.
What about his own family?
- Keep this.
- You children are growing up too.
Mom, Tara Singh gave us money.
Money. Show me?
Let me see. Great.
But, mom, this is Indian money.
Indian.
Useless son of a useless father.
What Indian?
Do you know?
Listen to me carefully.
There is only one thing good
about India.
Their money is worth double our money.
Great.
Go check there must
be more lying around there.
Go check.
Tara Singh,
you did one good thing before you left.
Gave us some money.
Wished you had given more.
It's been so long since
I saw any money.
The story remained untold...
I found out from my shop,
some stranger was looking for me.
I knew it must be
you looking for Jeetey.
Where is Jeetey?
I will tell you.
Cover your face before someone
recognises you.
Come on.
Tell me my friend, where did
my beloved where you spent the evening?
everywhere.
Gullu.
Gullu, look who is here.
Gullu! It's Tara, Gullu.
Tara. You are here, my buddy.
You are here.
You are here, my friend.
Save me, my friend.
I lost my family, my home.
The police beat me to a pulp.
Look. Look at me.
Gullu, you will get better.
But, where is Jeetey?
Your son Jeetey is a brave boy.
There is no telling
how much he loves you.
He faced several hurdles,
took up several job,
even cooked Biryani for customers,
and finally made it
to jail looking for you.
- Honestly.
- Jeetey?
He entered the quagmire for you,
but he couldn't get out of it.
With the help of General Rani's cook,
a cop told me--
That night, when he entered the solitary
confinement cell to find you.
You...
This wretch helped you get in,
didn't she?
How dare you hit me
in my own home?
Your father must be yearning
for you just like this.
Yes, he isn't dead yet.
Tara Singh is alive.
He will surely come to save you.
It's time to offer our prayers, sir.
Hamid Iqbal.
A son, whose father is still alive,
has nothing to worry about.
You're going to pray, aren't you?
Then better pray to Allah
my father doesn't land up here.
Because if he does,
and he sees me in this condition,
then he will tear you into
so many pieces...
That all of Pakistan
will not be able to count.
I will kill Hamid Iqbal!
Where is he?
Tara...your temper is justified.
But this is not the time
to lose control, Tara.
We have to save Jeetey.
Look at this poster.
Take a look at it.
In the name of Allah,
the Most Gracious and The Most Merciful one.
You have all not gathered here willingly.
In fact, you've been brought here
by Allah's will.
Couple of years ago,
what was initiated by a Hindu criminal,
today Allah wants to put an end to it.
Nara-e-takbir!
Allah-o-Akbar!
Kill him. Kill him.
Don't be fooled
by this boy's innocent face.
This boy is an Indian spy.
Not only did he use a fake passport
and visa to enter our country,
he has even humiliated Islam
by posing as a fake Muslim.
To fulfil his espionage intentions,
just like his father,
he misled an innocent girl
of Pakistan,
made her fall in love with her,
and tarnished her honour.
Jeetey is innocent.
He didn't lay a finger on me.
He has committed no crime.
Jeetey is not a spy.
Forgive him. Forgive him.
Muskaan is right, sir.
- Mukhtair!
- Uncle--
Mukhtair!
You are lucky.
Allah himself has bestowed you,
with the opportunity
to raise the flag of Ghazwa-e-Hind.
General sir, please forgive Jeetey.
Forgive him.
Sign this.
General...
Sign it, woman.
Otherwise...
Muskaan, my child,
is this your statement?
Every word written here is true,
isn't it?
This infidel Indian has tarnished
your honour.
Tell them.
Tell everyone...
that he tarnish your honour.
Is this your signature?
And did anyone force you to sign this?
Are these your signatures?
Yes.
Could there be a sin bigger than this,
in Islam's view?
Our scholars have stated
one day...
Ghazwa-e-Hind will become a reality.
So be it.
Every Hindu will convert to Muslim.
These Hindus want to mislead
our innocent daughters.
Tarnish their honour.
Convert them.
Allah-o-Akbar!
Jeetey!
Be patient.
This infidel will be punished.
Tie him to the mouth of the cannon.
And let the world
watch justice of Sheriyat.
Great. You call this justice.
My mother has narrated Koran
to me more times then you have read it.
She has explained it to me.
And the Koran says the dying person
is asked for his final wish.
After the heinous crime
you committed,
you've lost your right
to a final wish, boy.
But the Pakistani law is merciful.
Tell me...
What is your last wish?
Son would like to meet his father.
Tara Singh.
You arrived at the right occasion.
Son being murdered
in front of his father.
What a sight!
You killed 40 of my men.
Finally, I will be at peace.
General.
Let me son go.
He is innocent.
Your grudge is with me.
I am right here.
I've a grudge with every Indian.
You are done torturing
my Muslim brothers in India.
Now...we will get them freedom.
Freedom from whom?
India belongs to Muslims.
India belongs
to Christians, Sikhs, Hindus.
It belongs to every Indian.
Together they fought
for our independence.
They made several sacrifices.
I see...then what about East Pakistan,
where you misled Bengali Pakistanis,
and formed the Mukti Bahini Army?
What about that?
We did not form any army.
They are victims of your torture.
Your soldiers killed
three million Bengali Muslims.
They tortured their woman.
No! It's a lie.
Then what about
the 10 million refugees in India?
It was staged by your people
to show to the world.
Stop lying, General.
Stop these political games.
Stop playing God to Muslims.
If the people are given a chance,
to resettle in India.
Then half of Pakistan will be empty.
Your politics will make you a pauper.
You will be begging on the streets,
and no one will give you any alms.
Enough of this rubbish.
Tie father and son
to the cannon's mouth.
Let's see what he uproots today!
Catch him.
Hamid!
Tara Singh.
In order to deliver the devout,
Attack.
And to eradicate the heretical,
As well as to reestablish
the essence of dharma,
I Myself appear millennium
after millennium.
Jeetey.
Father.
Jeetey! Jeetey! Jeetey!
Jeetey is over here.
Tara Singh, where are you?
Jeetey is over here, with me.
Tara Singh, you coward,
show yourself!
Let my son go, please.
Please, please.
Hamid!
Hamid, save my son, please.
Drop the guns.
Please. Shoaib.
Shoaib...Shoaib.
Save Shoaib, please.
My baby... my baby.
Shoaib...
Shattered to bits, aren't you?
And my father didn't even lay
a finger on you.
Shoaib!
- Shoaib, my child!
- Shoaib, my baby!
Hands don't lie
Unflinching shock closing in
You and I feverishly tipping high
Toes trotting jazz got us
Hamid, you'remaking history.
Rewritten it, rather.
Amazing comments
are being said for you.
General sir. Wait up.
Amazing.
Hold this.
One thing about Tara Singh...
He seems like a glorious man.
Catch him for my sake.
You just start anywhere, Rani.
That's why I am a fan of you.
And that stupid made a fool of you.
And he himself became a hero.
You bloody idiot.
He just caught your son,
and you started shitting
in your pants.
Look at this newspaper.
- Hello, Mr. Khan.
- Hello.
Look at this newspaper.
Come here, take a look,
at this cartoon in Indian newspapers.
Read it out, Noor.
It says,
"He's the son-in-law of Pakistan."
"Welcome him, anoint him."
"Otherwise, this time
he will take Lahore in dowry."
Bloody shit.
You are very naughty, Noor.
- Come here.
- Rani.
You embarrassed us
in front of the enemy.
I told you there is no need
for drama now.
This is not the right time.
We'll do it after the war.
Tara won't go anywhere,
until we have his son behind bars.
You bloody tried to convince me...
You convinced me...
that the morale of my boys will go up.
Maulanas are doing let them do it.
You have 72 hours.
Only until Friday.
If he crosses the Pakistan border,
then your fate will be just like
Ashraf Ali's.
Understand?
Sadar sir.
I've endured a lot of humiliation
during the partition.
And every time I've emerged stronger.
I will do so this time as well.
Thank you very much, sir.
Sir, we've sealed the Lahore border.
The father and son duo
can never get out of Lahore.
I breathed a sigh of relief
when I read the newspaper.
Are you okay, Tara ji?
Don't worry, Madam ji.
We are both absolutely fine.
Jeetey. Where is Jeetey?
Here, talk to your son.
- Hello, mom?
- Jeetey.
Mom...
how are you?
It's been so long since
I heard your voice.
Don't cry, mom.
Don't cry.
You made your son emotional.
Stop crying.
And tell the colonel,
that Valli bhai helped us a great deal.
He also told us a way
to get out of here.
We'll take part
in the procession tomorrow,
and cross the border.
Not possible.
It's not possible
to cross the border, my friend.
Looking at the current situation,
the government has cancelled
the procession.
Police and the army
have surrounded us from all sides.
There is no way out of here.
There is a way.
Surrender.
Catch him.
Catch them. Go.
Let's go, Jeetey!
Wait here, son.
Weapons cannot shred the soul,
Nor can fire burn it,
Water cannot wet it,
Nor can the win dry it.
Father, give me your hand.
Fire!
Jeetey.
This is Radio Pakistan.
In breaking news,
Pakistani forces have severely injured,
Tara Singh and his son Jeetey
and separated them from each other.
They are looking everywhere
for these two.
More lives...
It's also been announced,
if anyone helps them,
then they will be deemed a traitor,
and punished severely.
General Hamid Iqbal has made big claims,
saying soon father
and son will be in his custody.
and punish them brutally,
which will make India shiver.
Sir. Yes, sir.
We heard a rumour about Tara Singh.
Someone spotted him
in the Punjab University area, sir.
Yes, sir.
Sir, where else can they go
but straight to hell?
Punjab University.
Do you want to meet your father?
Police. Police...
Shut up.
There is still time
for the 72-hour deadline.
We have already
got the location of his son.
And, as for Tara Singh--
Hey...
Where is my son?
Muslimpura.
All stations.
Get all the Maulanas' men activated.
Over and out.
- Where is that non believer?
- That way!
Let's go.
Come on.
Come out.
I've closed all the doors.
Eat some food.
You must be hungry.
Why this favour?
I am an Indian.
- And I--
- Who came from India to look for his father.
Newspapers have found their
"breaking news",
and people have found
their daily dose of drama.
Come on.
Don't think too much.
Okay...do one thing.
When you go back to India,
then help a helpless Pakistani.
You'll be surprised at
how peaceful you will feel.
Come on, eat it.
Hmm.
My father must be hungry too.
I'll take these.
- I will eat with him.
- But...
- I'll leave.
- Take more...
Listen, son.
No...it's better I leave
in this darkness.
I don't want anything bad
to happen to my aunt.
Aunt?
This is my mom's home.
Pakistan.
Where else would I have an aunt?
The police treated
Tara's son unfairly.
They beat him to an inch of his life.
Jeetey.
But the son's emotion
for his father is amazing.
Gives you a strange courage.
He escaped from police custody.
To find his father.
He's lost so much blood,
whether anyone finds him or not,
scavengers will definitely find him.
Poor guy will become food
for scavengers.
Jeetey.
God. Protect Jeetey from harm.
Protect him.
Please, God.
God. Protect Jeetey from harm.
"Come home O traveller,"
"without you I am incomplete."
"Our love story is filled
with so much bane."
"Like the seven seas dwell
in our eyes."
"When my heart and I..."
"When my heart
and I talk about you."
"The rains pour
in before the monsoon arrives."
"Come home O traveller,"
"without you I am incomplete."
"Take me home O traveller,"
"Come home O traveller,"
"without you I am incomplete."
This is Sultan bhai.
From Muslimpura.
He is a park ranger.
He helped us find you.
Don't worry.
We'll get you across before dawn.
There is a bridge close
to the border.
Smugglers have built
a tunnel under it.
That's how they smuggle goods
in and out.
Kurban Khan.
You helped my son.
And your entire family had
to pay the price.
And yet, you are...
That's not true, Tara Singh.
Helping you cross is
a good deed for us.
That is why Ranger sir
is helping you too.
There is no danger.
After we help you,
we'll leave for Balochistan.
Tara...
I have a request.
Return my daughter's happiness to her.
Your daughter is like my daughter.
Thank you.
She will be alright.
Father...
Father, please don't send me away.
This is where
I was born and raised.
How do I leave you
and start afresh?
I cannot hold my tears back,
I just cannot.
My child...please, don't cry.
The infidels escaped.
There is a bridge close
to the border.
Tara Singh.
Returning to your motherland?
Take this gift along.
Brother!
Farid!
What do you say, Tara Singh?
I've not one, not two,
but several gifts for you.
Your Indian soldiers
and your son's in-laws too.
Tara Singh,
which gift should I send next?
Stop.
Father.
What's the plan now, Tara Singh?
What now, huh?
How will you escape now?
We don't even have my son here
for you to threaten.
How are you going
to take out my soldiers now, huh?
You took them down before, remember?
And what about you?
"A father's always got his son's back."
You spat on my face, didn't you?
I dare you to try it again.
Go on, do it,
now that your father's here too.
Go on!
Jeetey!
We desire 'Gazwa-E-Hind',
and you desire to convert
our daughters instead?
You want to step on my land,
my Pakistan,
and start chanting "Long Live India"?
You did that, didn't you?
Long Live India!
Subedaar, turn on the camera.
Now you're going to chant,
"India be damned."
Say it, Tara Singh -
India be damned.
Say it.
SAY IT!
My India was worth praising,
is worth praising,
and is always going be worth praising!
Hey!
I'll say it.
I will say it.
But how will it matter if I say it?
Even if I say those words,
it won't diminish the worthiness of
my country.
Our tricolor flies high in the sky
and will keep on doing so.
Even if every Pakistani here says
"India be damned,"
their voices won't reach the border.
But if every Indian says,
"Long Live India,"
the sound of it will tear all
of you apart.
Long Live India!
"O' my Motherland, I bow to thee!"
- "O' my Motherland, I bow to thee!"
- Tara Singh!
"O' my Motherland, I bow to thee!"
Hold up. Nobody shoot.
He's got the General.
Catch him alive.
Go.
Jeetey!
"He is complete, he is summit,
he is pot of fire"
"He can cause uproar,
he is the punishment for justice"
"In the flow of emotions,
he is like a summit of a mountain"
- Hurry up, Tara Singh.
- Jeetey!
"The one who destroys the evil,
he is with the truth"
Come on, come on.
No!
Surround them!
They shouldn't escape!
Load! Ready, set, fire!
Fire!
Load! Move forward, you buggers!
Get up and move!
Go, open fire!
'H' 'E' Turret lock!
- Sir!
- Delta One, move right!
Sir, the turret is locked.
Push the turret manually
towards the target.
Move! Move!
- Hit! - Move forward!
- Yes, sir!
More tanks!
Major, look there!
Move forward!
Yes, sir!
Crush them!
Block them on both sides!
Charge!
Move!
God help me!
Jeetey!
Father!
Bloody infidels!
Get down!
Where will escape now, huh?
Get down.
Tara Singh!
Glory to India!
What is this nonsense, Colonel?
Look at my ranks.
I'm the General of the Pakistan army.
Don't you know the Geneva Convention,
damn it?
I'm in India.
I'm a POW.
Prisoner of war.
Arrest me.
Did you follow the Geneva Convention
at Ram Tekdi?
Did you?
Look at my men.
Look at their condition.
You're lucky we didn't start a war yet,
or we would've met not here,
but in Lahore.
And there, General,
your neck would've been
in Colonel Rawant's hands.
But as of today,
the war hasn't even started yet.
There is no war diary,
no arrest memo.
In fact, officially,
we aren't even here.
So you're playing games?
Now I am going to look the other way,
and you and Tara Singh
can settle your scores.
No, Tara Singh.
I have a family.
I have a little kid.
Please, please.
And what about the families you killed,
including the kids?
You guys killed my family
too during the partition!
Countless families lost loved
ones during the partition.
It was a tragic incident
that we've already put behind us.
But you're exploiting that incident.
You are using it as an excuse,
along with your religion,
to behead people.
She's the Quran-e-Sharif.
And he's the Bhagavad-Gita.
Now pick one.
What's the difference between the two?
The world was formed from one light.
Wasn't that what Baba Nanak
also preached?
If you had followed
Baba Nanak's teachings,
you would have embraced
people instead of beheading them.
Tell me, you want to live or die?
Quran?
Or Gita?
Gita.
Couldn't you have embraced both of them?
What kind of person are you?
If you had followed
the path set by your Lord,
you would not have spoken
about 'Gazwa-E-Hind'.
You would have instead spoken
about loving India.
And this world would
be like heaven then.
Tara Singh!
Fire!
I'm so proud of you, Tara Singh Ji.
You wanted your son
to be a soldier like me, right?
I think he's ready to join the army.
What do you say?
Yes, sir.
"The swings are out again,"
"and the fruits have ripened."
"Life is short, nights are too long."
"Come home O traveller,"
"without you I am incomplete."
"Life is short, nights are too long."
"Come home O traveller,"
"without you I am incomplete."
- "Come home O traveller,"
"Come home O traveller,"
"without you I am incomplete."