[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
5TH AUGUST 2019
LAHORE, PAKISTAN
What are you looking at?
It's cancer.
Not some pretty girl's Instagram page.
How long have I got?
- [DOCTOR] Three years.
- [INTENSE MUSIC]
Maybe.
[NEWS REPORTER] The Indian government
has made the shocking decision today
to revoke Kashmir's special status.
The Indian Parliament has unilaterally
announced Article 370 is abrogated.
Pakistan's Foreign Affairs Office has
condemned this unilateral action and said
that Pakistan will weigh up all
options and give a befitting response.
[DOCTOR] Article 370 canceled!
How can India do that?
- This is wrong, sir.
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER ON TV]
This is not wrong.
It's a declaration of war.
You said three years, right?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
It's long enough.
Time for diplomacy has passed, sir.
If we wait for the UN resolution,
then India will take control
of our Azad Kashmir next.
A man of God cannot challenge them.
It's time to befriend the Devil.
- [MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
- [CELL PHONE BEEPS]
[JIM'S THEME PLAYS]
[MAN 1] Jim.
[IN ENGLISH] General Qadir for you.
[JIM] General Qadir, all in order?
Don't want order,
I want chaos.
[JIM] What do you want?
To bring India to its knees.
[JIM] You sure?
Once that bullet is fired,
it won't go back into the gun.
You need to be sure.
Can you do it?
[JIM] It'll take time, but it can be done.
[CELL PHONE BEEPS]
3 YEARS LATER
SOMEWHERE IN AFRICA
- [INDISTINCT CLAMORING]
- [GUNS COCKING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[GUN COCKING]
A radar can't detect it,
no signal can stop it.
It fears nothing,
nor can it be reasoned with.
Once it's launched,
it's like a djinn from Hell.
Countdown to Judgment Day starts.
[IN ENGLISH] Good.
[IN HINDI] Jim will let you know
where to deliver it.
Why? Doesn't he trust you?
Jim?
[CHUCKLES DEVIOUSLY]
If God asked him to name
anything he wanted,
he'd say, "Are You playing a trick on me?"
Hmm.
Jim keeps his cards close to his chest.
[IN ENGLISH] Boss, is this man Raafe?
[IN ENGLISH] Why?
One man come.
He asked for Raafe.
We say don't know Raafe.
He say Raafe come to see Fayyad.
- [DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- Where is he?
VIP area, getting special treatment.
- [MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
- [MEN GRUNTING]
- [GRUNTING]
- [CHAIN CLANKING]
[PUFFING]
[GRUNTS]
[IN ARABIC] Who are you?
Hey, Hindi.
[IN ARABIC] Speak up!
Talk in Hindi!
No fun swearing at you in Arabic.
You'll take five seconds to be surprised.
Five seconds to wonder
where you've heard this voice.
And five more seconds
to get over your disbelief.
[SNIGGERS]
Then you'll ask...
[IN HINDI] "Pathaan? You?"
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Still alive.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Where is she?
How did you survive?
[CLICKS TONGUE] Answer my question first.
Where is Rubai?
[SNICKERS]
Oof!
Mr. Pathaan has a broken heart.
Love and perfume cannot be concealed.
She's far from your reach.
- Now you'll be going far away too.
- Ouch.
Any last message?
I have a gift for her.
- [CHAIR BOLTS CLATTER]
- [MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Your dancing bells are undone, Raafe.
So dance!
- [GRUNTS]
- [GUNSHOT FIRES]
[DYNAMIC MUSIC]
[MAN 1] Kill him!
What are you waiting for?
[IN ENGLISH]
♪ When all the world is burning ♪
♪ And fearing all the time ♪
♪ Crying every breath out loud for help
But there's no one around ♪
♪ Looking in the gloomy face of bleak
And darkness everywhere ♪
♪ Losing all hope and faith
But there's no one to dare ♪
♪ Rises an arrow to burn the evil
And set the order right ♪
♪ He strikes a blow, he fights alone
Shining so bright ♪
♪ He's the knight ♪
- [GUN COCKING]
- [ROCK MUSIC PLAYS]
[MAN 2] Kill him!
[EXPLOSION]
[THUD]
[THUNDEROUS EXPLOSION]
[GRUNTS]
- [THRILLING MUSIC]
- [GUNSHOTS]
[MULTIPLE GUNSHOTS]
There's a storm coming, Raafe.
Fasten your seat belt.
[ENGINE STARTING]
- [THRILLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [ROTOR WHIRRING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[MULTIPLE GUNSHOTS]
Close the door!
[SCREAMING]
[IN ENGLISH] Sorry, Raafe.
[RAAFE SCREAMING]
[GUNFIRE]
[THUNDEROUS EXPLOSION]
- [MULTIPLE FIRING]
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
YASH RAJ FILMS
PRESENTS
PATHAAN
NEW DELHI, INDIA
J.O.C.R. HEADQUARTERS
[SIREN WAILING]
- [PAPERS RUSTLE]
- [CELL PHONE BUZZES]
I'm on my way, Barun.
If you go on about the cake,
how can I finish my work?
Light the candles.
Start singing "Happy Birthday",
and I'll be home
before the candles go out.
[WOMAN 1] Ma'am, I've got
all the information.
- [FAINT CHATTER]
- [DEVICE BEEPS]
[WOMAN 2] Yeah. Check again.
I need all the information now.
Run it past the Finance Ministry.
- Uh, ma'am?
- Yes?
[IN ENGLISH] We have a red flag.
[IN HINDI] Our scanner
has just identified someone.
- [IN ENGLISH] Who is it?
- [DEVICE BEEPING AND BUZZING]
Rubai?
[IN HINDI] Where?
Paris.
A security camera at
Palais Royal metro station.
When?
15 minutes ago, max.
[IN ENGLISH] Get a team on it right away.
[IN HINDI] Keep eyes on her.
Do not intercept.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[IN ENGLISH] Get a plane.
Use the blue channel. We need
permission for immediate takeoff.
[IN ENGLISH] Yes, ma'am.
[IN HINDI] And yes, tell Barun...
[IN HINDI] To keep a slice of cake
for you in the fridge.
How much longer?
Uh, five hours, max.
Uh... ma'am?
Hmm?
Ma'am, are we going after Pathaan?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
What do you know about Pathaan?
Not much, ma'am.
Whenever he's mentioned,
everyone gets uncomfortable.
They change the subject.
Ma'am... is he on our side?
He was once.
Not just on our side,
he was our center-forward.
Opening batsman, opening bowler...
wicketkeeper and four slip fielder too.
You know, if it weren't for Pathaan...
we would not be doing what we do.
Nor would the JOCR Department exist.
Two years ago,
during a Myanmar mission,
Pathaan got badly injured.
He lay in a hospital for weeks.
It was touch and go.
Everyone believed
the Pathaan chapter was closed.
We didn't realize that...
he was writing a whole new book.
INDIAN MILITARY HOSPITAL, NEW DELHI
2 YEARS EARLIER
[INVIGORATING MUSIC]
I heard you got badly hurt.
Ma'am...
yes.
I have a metal plate in my foot,
a titanium disc in my neck,
and bio-absorbable screws in my shoulder.
[LAUGHS]
But you look very well.
It's tough. My body goes
beep, beep, beep at airport security.
They keep detecting metal. [CHUCKLES]
Looks like retirement doesn't suit you.
- [MELLOW MUSIC]
- Why?
Retirement can be peaceful, Pathaan.
There are so many ways
to spend one's time.
Tomorrow we could be a MasterChef
and Indian Idol the next day.
[IN ENGLISH] You need to
get a hobby, Pathaan.
[IN ENGLISH] Found it.
Kintsugi.
[IN HINDI] Is that Punjabi?
[PATHAAN CHUCKLES]
[IN HINDI] Japanese.
And I know you know what it means.
I know.
If precious pottery breaks,
the Japanese put the broken pieces
together with molten gold.
The object looks stronger
and more beautiful.
It's even considered more valuable.
Ma'am, look at this file.
These are the broken pieces
of our organization.
- [MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
- They're soldiers like me.
Forced to retire
because of injury or trauma.
But they're not done yet.
They're still full of guts and passion.
They're ready to fight and die for India.
So what do you want?
To form a new unit?
[IN ENGLISH] Yes, ma'am.
Do you realize how many people
will need convincing?
There will be so much red tape,
your hands will get glued together.
[IN ENGLISH] Try it.
[IN HINDI] You think
I've just been growing my hair out?
[IN ENGLISH] I've tried it.
And better, I've done it.
J.O.C.R.
JOCR?
Joint Operations and Covert Research,
ma'am.
[IN HINDI] Giving me a new job?
[IN HINDI] No, ma'am.
Just returning my boss her chair.
You were looking for a new hobby.
[IN ENGLISH] Try Kintsugi, please.
[IN HINDI] These broken soldiers
need new meaning in their lives.
They're ready for a mission.
You are the molten gold
who can put them together.
Stronger than before...
and more dangerous.
- [EXHILARATING MUSIC]
- [LIGHTS CRACKLE]
That was the birth of Team JOCR.
Every important mission for India
that no one else could carry out,
or take the responsibility for...
that was our playground.
[IN ENGLISH] We had no rules to stop us.
[IN HINDI] So obviously
anyone who loved rules...
had a problem with us.
Like our Colonel Luthra.
Wow!
Beautiful!
Very beautiful!
This space was reserved for a recreational
club for us and other departments.
A gym, sauna, pool tables, etc.
Sauna? Pool tables?
[IN ENGLISH] Excuse me, sir,
you can't be serious.
- [IN HINDI] These people are my officers.
- [IN ENGLISH] They're not officers!
[IN HINDI] You've made JOCR
with some broken jokers!
They're just broken eggshells.
- [IN ENGLISH] How dare you!
- [PLAYFUL MUSIC]
[PATHAAN CHUCKLES]
[IN ENGLISH] Good invention, guys.
- Rishi, well done!
- Thank you, sir.
- [IN HINDI] Did you think I actually...
- No, ma'am.
[IN ENGLISH] Oh, come on, Pathaan!
I was just playing along.
[IN HINDI] Would I talk
to a superior like that?
No, never.
[IN ENGLISH] Don't be a child.
[IN HINDI] I admit
Rishi's invention is very real.
[IN ENGLISH] But, Pathaan,
you can't mess with me.
- [IN ENGLISH] Is this a bad time?
- [PATHAAN] No, sir.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh!
[IN HINDI] He looks a little pale.
[IN ENGLISH] And he has those bags
under his eyes, which you guys missed.
[IN HINDI] Have you seen
Luthra's double chin?
It hangs down to his belly.
And Luthra's paunch?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC ENDS]
Sir!
Very good!
Very serious department!
[IN HINDI] Now I can make recommendations
to the Defense Secretary.
I told you that you're broken eggshells.
That's all.
[IN HINDI] Paunch, ma'am!
Sir. Sir.
Sir, now that you're here,
wait two minutes, please.
I must show you something.
[RISHI] Aeroflot 394C, 144 casualties.
Daesh claimed it was their doing.
Norwegian ship, Asgard.
Pirates destroyed it in the Gulf of Aden.
[IN ENGLISH] Biggest ecological
disaster of the decade.
Courtesy Boko Haram.
Chemical attack on the Japanese...
The Japanese outfit Aleph
claimed responsibility.
You think I have no intel on all this?
No, sir.
It wasn't Aleph...
or Boko Haram or Daesh.
At least, they weren't directly involved.
They outsourced these attacks
to a private terrorist group.
They work on contract,
not for ideological reasons.
[SNIGGERS] Really?
Terrorists are corporations now?
[SCOFFS]
Let's say a group like this exists,
so what?
They're Interpol's problem, not India's.
[IN ENGLISH] Actually, sir, now it is.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[IN HINDI] Because their next episode
is an India special.
[IN ENGLISH] And this is a big one.
[IN HINDI] In Dubai.
Sir, through the darknet,
we found out that
Outfit X is planning
something big in Dubai.
At the Asian Scientific Conference,
two Indian scientists
will represent India and our...
At the conference, our President...
is giving the keynote address.
[IN ENGLISH] They're after the President.
[IN ENGLISH] We think so, sir.
I'll make sure the security is tripled.
[IN HINDI] They won't
get near the President.
Thank you, sir.
- Thank you.
- [IN HINDI] Another request, sir.
If you don't mind...
these...
eggshells will come with me to Dubai.
[IN ENGLISH] Trust me, Luthra.
[IN HINDI] You look after
the President's security,
we'll handle Outfit X.
DUBAI, UAE
[LUTHRA] We took no chances, Pathaan.
Frankly speaking, your intel is paranoia.
I changed the President's
travel itinerary at the last minute.
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- [IN ENGLISH] No sign of explosives.
[IN HINDI] There are no spots
for a sniper to hide.
Absolutely nothing suspicious.
[IN ENGLISH] Intel was real, sir.
[IN HINDI] But now there's radio silence.
They've either become more careful or...
Sir, you said you changed
the President's travel route.
What was it before?
He was to travel with
the two scientists and the press.
[IN ENGLISH] Showing support for science.
[IN HINDI] Now he's taking
another route. With full security.
What about our scientists?
Will they travel with the President?
No. Multiple vehicles
make security tricky.
I want our NSG commandos
to focus on the President.
So the two scientists who had NSG cover,
no longer have it.
[IN ENGLISH] Damn it!
[IN HINDI] They tricked us
into changing the travel itinerary.
Their target is not the President, sir.
- [CAR ENGINE REVS]
- [TRILLING MUSIC]
I was hoping to take a selfie
with the President,
and impress the missus!
You still want to impress her,
after thirty years?
Science is easy, Farooqui.
Love is hard.
[TRILLING MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
PATRIOT
[JIM'S THEME PLAYS]
- [BRAKE SCREECHES]
- [LOUD EXPLOSION]
[IN ENGLISH] Sir, we've been attacked!
You were right, Pathaan.
They've attacked the scientists' convoy.
Shweta, lock me to the scientists' phone.
- [SHWETA] On it, sir.
- [IN ENGLISH] Now!
[FAROOQUI] Wait. Don't shoot!
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Dr. Sahani, Dr. Farooqui.
Take my advice.
Be more scared than you are.
[IN ENGLISH] You're pretty screwed.
He's got the scientists
in a gray Hummer, Pathaan.
[IN HINDI] Sir, I've sent you
the Hummer's location.
- [BRAKE SCREECHES]
- [VEHICLES HONKING]
[THRILLING MUSIC]
There's the Hummer, sir!
[CAR SCREECHES]
[LOUD EXPLOSION]
[VEHICLES HONKING]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[MELODIC WHISTLING]
[JIM'S THEME PLAYS]
Pathaan, I've been waiting
for a long time to meet you.
I heard a lot about you
when I was in RAW.
They call me Jim.
Jim?
You probably heard I was dead.
So?
Well, I am actually dead for India.
Here's the proof.
Bravery award.
[IN ENGLISH] I died a bloody hero.
[GRUNTS]
How come, Jim?
- [IN ENGLISH] I heard you...
- Were the best?
[IN HINDI] You heard right. I still am.
She broke my heart.
She'll break yours too.
You know her.
The difference is
I considered myself her lover,
and you think you're her son.
Mother India!
[TENSE MUSIC]
You're lucky.
You'll die believing your patriotism
meant something.
I'm sure they'll throw a medal
for bravery on your grave.
They'll call you a martyr.
[IN ENGLISH] But cost to the country?
Zero.
[IN HINDI] If life was different,
perhaps we'd be friends.
What a pity!
We have to play the cards we're dealt.
And in this round,
I hold all the aces.
[JIM'S THEME PLAYS]
Raza! Rishi!
Guys... [GRUNTS]
- Rishi...
- [GRUNTS]
- [GROANS]
- [SEAT BELT CLICKING]
- [RAZA] My seat belt.
- [RISHI] I'm stuck!
- Pathaan, I'm stuck!
- I can't unfasten my seat belt!
- [HUFFS] Rishi!
- [GROANS]
[RISHI GROANS]
[PATHAAN] Yeah! Come on.
[YELPS]
- [RISHI GROANS]
- [PATHAAN MURMURS INDISTINCTLY]
- [RISHI] I can't! My legs are stuck!
- [PATHAAN] Come on!
[RISHI] My leg is stuck, sir.
- Rishi.
- [RISHI GROANS]
- My leg!
- Don't worry, Rishi.
- [RISHI] My leg! I can't...
- [RAZA] Pathaan!
[IN HINDI] Sir, my leg is stuck.
- We must go, Pathaan!
- Wait!
- Raza! Wait!
- The car is about to explode!
- Raza, take him away!
- There's nothing you can do.
- [RAZA] Pathaan, we must go.
- [RISHI] Go, sir.
- [RAZA] There's nothing we can do!
- [IN ENGLISH] Sir, it's been an honor.
[RAZA] We must go, Pathaan!
[GRUNTS] Pathaan!
- [SHOUTS] Jai Hind!
- [THUNDEROUS EXPLOSION]
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
[DYNAMIC MUSIC]
[GRUNTS, SCREAMS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [RIVETING MUSIC]
[IN ENGLISH] Block the road.
[VEHICLE CRASHES]
[VEHICLES HONKING]
[GROANS]
[BOTH SCREAM]
[ACTION-PACKED MUSIC]
[GROANS]
[JIM] These choppers
won't fly through the tunnel,
they'll crash into the building.
Well, Pathaan? What next?
Their lives hang by this rope.
Only you can untie the knot.
[IN ENGLISH]
So, what's it gonna be, buddy?
[IN HINDI] Sacrifice? Or common sense?
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
Say hello to Mother India!
Tell her I'm coming soon.
I have a score to settle.
Jim. [SCOFFS]
Can't trust dead men
to stay dead. [SMACKS LIPS]
Was Jim working for RAW?
- Jim and Kabir.
- [MELANCHOLIC MUSIC]
Our best agents.
They were quite similar.
[IN ENGLISH]
Calculative, precise, methodical.
[IN HINDI] Not like our Mr. Pathaan.
He first listens to his heart,
then to his superiors.
[IN ENGLISH] So, what went wrong?
[IN ENGLISH] A job.
[IN HINDI] Remember the ONGC drilling
team the Somalian pirates kidnapped?
- [TENSE MUSIC]
- Hmm.
[IN ENGLISH] Jim went in solo.
[IN HINDI] He managed to save
six hostages, totally unharmed.
The pirates swore to take revenge.
They finally tracked Jim down.
They asked for a ransom of ten crore
rupees in exchange for Jim and his wife.
But we don't negotiate with terrorists.
[SCREECHING WITH PAIN]
[IN ENGLISH]
You love your country too much.
But your country...
no love you.
[JIM'S WIFE YELPS]
[GUN COCKING]
[SCREAMS] No!
No!
[WHIMPERING]
[MUFFLED VOICE] No! No!
[SCREAMS] No!
No.
[CRIES]
[JIM SCREAMS] No!
No! Please leave her!
No!
- [DOLEFUL MUSIC]
- [SOBS]
- [MULTIPLE GUNSHOTS]
- [SCREAMS] No!
No!
[LUTHRA] We never found Jim's body.
So we assumed he was dead.
Jim was given a medal,
the bravery award.
One of his uncles received it.
Couldn't you have paid the ransom for
an agent like him and his family?
[SMACKS LIPS]
Your department does not
lack funds, sir.
Our funds can't be wasted
on personal matters, Pathaan.
[SCOFFS]
Such honesty, sir!
What if it was a minister's family?
Only the weak go down
on their knees, Pathaan.
Not soldiers.
Now this soldier will have us
on our knees.
Colonel...
I have looked into his eyes.
He's beyond right and wrong,
good and bad.
Your decision has convinced him
that his actions are justified.
And now...
he will not stop.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[IN ENGLISH]
Shweta, check for leads on the darknet.
- Raktbeej.
- [IN HINDI] What's that?
The word keeps popping up.
- Raktbeej. Sounds like a code word.
- For a man? Or an object?
Mm-hmm.
Have the dead in Dubai been identified?
Yes, sir.
All ex-soldiers or secret agents.
They recently received money transfers.
From one account?
Yes. From a Pakistani doctor.
Rubina Mohsin.
She lives in London.
Her account was inactive for months.
Then these transfers were made.
Who knows if she was even aware.
The bank would've alerted her
about the transfers.
We've hacked her emails.
She hasn't logged in for a month.
Her phone is off too.
But two hours ago,
she checked in online.
She's taking a flight.
Where to?
If it was another agent,
she'd be off to Iraq or Syria.
As it's you...
it's Spain.
Mm-hmm.
I'm desperate for a vacation.
[IN SPANISH] ♪ Tonight... ♪
♪ Life is complete ♪
♪ In this instant... ♪
♪ Life is rich ♪
♪ Tonight... ♪
♪ Life is complete ♪
♪ In this instant... ♪
♪ Life is rich ♪
[IN HINDI] ♪ My heart has been robbed ♪
♪ By my lovers ♪
♪ How they torment me ♪
♪ These crazy thoughts of mine ♪
♪ The moment I feel a wave of modesty ♪
♪ I throw it to the wind ♪
♪ The world has not seen ♪
♪ My true colors ♪
♪ My heart has been robbed ♪
♪ By my lovers ♪
♪ How they torment me ♪
♪ These crazy thoughts of mine ♪
♪ The moment I feel a wave of modesty ♪
♪ I throw it to the wind ♪
♪ The world has not seen ♪
♪ My true colors ♪
Shweta, I'm sending you info
on Dr. Rubina Mohsin. Check it.
♪ I'm like a breath of fresh air ♪
♪ My style, my habits, all new ♪
♪ I never follow the right path ♪
♪ The path of wrong is so inviting ♪
[IN SPANISH] ♪ Tonight... ♪
♪ Life is complete ♪
♪ In this instant... ♪
♪ Life is rich ♪
[IN HINDI] ♪ When I feel
A wave of modesty ♪
♪ I throw it to the wind ♪
♪ The world has not seen ♪
♪ My true colors ♪
♪ My heart has been robbed ♪
♪ By my lovers ♪
♪ How they torment me ♪
♪ These crazy thoughts of mine ♪
[IN SPANISH] ♪ Tonight... ♪
♪ Life is complete ♪
[IN HINDI] ♪ By my lovers ♪
[IN SPANISH] ♪ Life is complete ♪
[IN HINDI] ♪ My heart has been robbed ♪
♪ By my lovers ♪
[IN SPANISH] ♪ Tonight... ♪
♪ Life is complete ♪
[IN HINDI] ♪ By my lovers ♪
[IN SPANISH] ♪ Life is complete ♪
[WATER SPLASHES]
[JIM'S THEME PLAYS]
Cool, no?
Throw a few seeds on the ground
and the ants come crawling.
A bank account, a SIM card...
and Pathaan appears
in flesh and blood.
[IN ENGLISH] The hunter...
hunted!
[SCOFFS]
[IN HINDI] Meet my team, Pathaan.
Raafe, ex-GID.
Sergei, ex-SBU.
Begio, ex-AISE.
Dietrich, ex-BDD.
- And Rubai, ex-ISI.
- Hmm.
Nice.
[JIM] The world's top-secret agencies
are all represented here.
Only India is missing.
Will you oblige?
You offering me a job? [SNIGGERS]
Are you for real?
Actually, I came here
to offer you a position
in a six feet hole I've dug for you.
There's room to lie down too.
Will you come half naked like this?
Or must I drag you out?
I already have a grave
with my name on it, Pathaan.
You do too.
Since the day you became a soldier.
That's all that Mother India offers.
A never-ending supply of coffins.
Only the names of the corpses change.
[IN ENGLISH] See, Pathaan.
[IN HINDI] We're not answerable
to anyone. Family, foe or friend.
We choose the jobs we want.
And demand the price we want.
[IN ENGLISH] Join us, Pathaan.
Be rich.
Be powerful.
[IN HINDI] Or be a corpse.
[IN ENGLISH] Simple.
Shall I cuss you in English?
Or explain in Hindi?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[IN ENGLISH] Pay up, guys.
[IN HINDI] I wagered
you'd refuse my offer.
Even your death wins me a bet.
- Sorry, Pathaan.
- [HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
If you're not on my side, I can't
afford to let you be against me.
[JIM'S THEME PLAYS]
[IN ENGLISH] Sorry, Pathaan.
Nothing personal.
- [GUN COCKS]
- [IN ENGLISH] Really?
[GLASS SHATTERS]
Ow!
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
- [GRUNTS]
- Ooh!
- [THRILLING MUSIC]
Women!
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
Yours, ma'am.
[RUBAI GRUNTS]
[GRUNTS]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- [MULTIPLE GUNSHOTS]
- Let's go.
- Of course.
Oh!
- [GUNSHOT]
- [IN HINDI] Are you ex-ISI?
[IN HINDI] Not ex.
You thought you were the only ones
monitoring Outfit X?
I've been with them for a year,
undercover.
- Why all this?
- [GUNSHOT]
With you, we'll get what I want faster.
When did we become a "we"?
When I saved your life.
You endangered it!
[IN ENGLISH] You know that, right?
You...
- [RUBAI] Run!
- [PATHAAN] Where are you?
[IN HINDI] Where are you going?
- Wait!
- [RUBAI] Duck.
[IN ENGLISH] Good shot.
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- [PATHAAN GRUNTS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER CONTINUES]
[PATHAAN] Oh!
[IN HINDI] You aim well.
[IN HINDI] So do they.
- [DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- [GUN FIRING]
[WOEFUL MUSIC]
[DYNAMIC MUSIC]
[SIRENS WAILING]
[SOBS]
Father!
[GRUNTING]
[GASPING FOR BREATH]
[PATHAAN] Morning.
You were out for 18 hours.
- [SIGHS]
- [PATHAAN] Take it easy.
Fever's down.
No infection. And luckily the bullet
didn't touch any vital organ.
You were calling for your father
and crying.
You kept asking them
to let your father go.
Father...
He was a journalist in the Middle East.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC]
He asked too many questions.
Printed too many answers.
So he was brutally tortured...
and we were made to watch
from the front row.
Then you went to Pakistan with
your mother and joined medical college.
Dr. Rubina Mohsin.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
After that, to serve humanity...
you joined the ISI.
Hmm.
- [IN ENGLISH] Oh! Of course.
- [GRUNTS]
[GLASSES CLINK]
[IN ENGLISH] Cheers.
[BLITHE MUSIC]
[IN HINDI] Couldn't you
find a cheaper drink?
[IN HINDI] Thing is, we don't
have big budgets like the ISI.
But seriously...
why did you save my life?
Aren't your good looks
and personality enough?
Normally they are. I'm so sexy.
You said we'd get what
you wanted faster with me.
Hmm.
So I want to know,
what do "we" want?
Raktbeej.
[TENSE MUSIC]
Heard the name?
Hmm. He was a demon.
Wherever a drop of his blood fell,
another Raktbeej was born.
Basically, it was impossible
to destroy Raktbeej.
Whatever this Raktbeej is,
it's in Russia.
In seven days...
what?
Jim will take delivery
of Raktbeej in seven days.
[PATHAAN] Hmm.
Then all hell will break loose.
- So basically, we have...
- Seven days. Got it.
[IN ENGLISH] Cheers.
[IN ENGLISH] Bottoms up!
[CHUCKLES]
[IN HINDI] I think you skipped school
the day they spoke about ISI and India.
[SNIGGERS]
You see we don't get on so well.
Besides, the first day we met, you put
Jim's gun against my head. Remember?
So don't take it personally...
if I have a few trust issues.
[IN HINDI] Some things are
more important than trust issues.
Like these seven days and Raktbeej.
[IN ENGLISH] So are you in?
Or are you out?
Hmm...
[IN ENGLISH] So am I in?
Or am I out?
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[IN HINDI] Russia's a big place.
Do you know the address?
Any landmark?
[IN ENGLISH] You know? Something.
Vault 412, Moscow,
Woskwich Tower.
[IN HINDI] You must know the address.
You were posted in Russia
for three years.
[PATHAAN] Oh!
[IN HINDI] What else
do you know about me?
[RUBAI CHUCKLES]
Do you want me to tell you
everything now?
[PATHAAN IN ENGLISH] Scary.
An ISI agent tells us there's something
in Moscow that Jim's after.
[PATHAAN] Yes, ma'am.
[IN HINDI] I've heard
about Raktbeej on the darknet.
Do you know what it is?
[IN ENGLISH] No, ma'am.
So, let's hope wherever it is,
it stays unknown.
I know you're familiar
with every corner of Russia.
[IN ENGLISH] But Russia is still
a friendly country and a crucial ally.
[IN HINDI] A scandal will not be
tolerated in Moscow or in Delhi.
[IN HINDI] Ma'am, you know
Jim wants Raktbeej.
If he can't buy it, he'll steal it.
- And if you get caught?
- [SIGHS]
Don't try negotiating for me.
I'm not Jim.
[SIGHS]
[IN ENGLISH] Damn it!
[IN HINDI] Whatever Raktbeej is...
neither Jim nor ISI should
get their hands on it.
[IN ENGLISH] Go, get it!
[IN ENGLISH] Love you, ma'am.
MOSCOW, RUSSIA
[IN RUSSIAN] Welcome.
Sir, let me show you around.
Hmm. Same to you.
- For an English dictionary.
- [IN ENGLISH] Thank you, sir. Thank you.
You need anything, contact Andrei.
You have a great honeymoon.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
You didn't tell me
we were on our honeymoon.
If you had denied it, it would've
broken Andrei's heart.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
Look. What a stunning view!
Wow!
I never thought I'd see such a big
building on my wedding night!
If you stay with me,
there's more fun to come.
Many corporates have their offices
in that building.
WOSKWICH TOWER
This is the Woskwich Tower.
The 92nd floor is home to
the world's most secure vault.
92ND FLOOR -SECURED VAULT
The vault is a 30ft x 30ft room.
No key or explosive can open it.
No laser can cut through.
No acid burn through.
Can't cut it, can't break it.
Can't blow it up, can't burn it.
But we can open it!
But... there's only one problem.
The vault has a lock and key
but two different people have them.
So when you need to open it,
an uncle brings the lock from his home,
and an aunty brings the key.
The lock and key meet like the union
of the Ganges and Jamuna.
- Access granted.
- [VAULT WHIRRING]
[RUBAI] So, must we steal
both lock and key?
[PATHAAN IN ENGLISH] Yes, exactly.
[IN HINDI] But there's a complication.
The lock is 12 kms away
in Uncle Grigor's office.
GRIGOR UNCLE -12 KMS
And the key is 16 kms away
with Aunty Karen.
KAREN AUNTY -16 KMS
And of course, their offices
are in opposite directions.
[IN ENGLISH] And the best part?
[IN HINDI] We must get to the vault
in ten minutes once we've stolen them.
10 MIN
- [IN ENGLISH] Say what?
- [IN ENGLISH] What?
I love this sugar-free yogurt.
[IN HINDI] As soon as
the lock and key are removed,
a timer starts ticking.
[IMITATES TICKING OF A CLOCK]
Within ten minutes, at FSB headquarters,
someone must enter an "all-clear code".
This confirms all is well,
and it's not Rubai and Pathaan.
Or else...
Or else?
[VAULT WHIRRING]
[IN ENGLISH] Total lockdown. That's it.
[IN HINDI] Lock, key or prayers,
nothing makes a difference.
Unless the system
is reset in three places.
[IN ENGLISH] Game over.
[RUBAI] How can we reach the vault
in ten minutes in Moscow traffic?
[PATHAAN IN HINDI] Mm-hmm. Step one.
To get to the main lock,
we must first open another lock.
To open that, we need
Uncle Grigor's fingerprints.
- [RIVETING MUSIC]
- [SIRENS WAILING]
[CROWD CHEERING]
[DYNAMIC MUSIC]
[GASPS, SIGHS]
Any cops in sight?
Why?
Because you're looking like a bomb!
[CHUCKLES]
Oh!
Ooh!
[IN ENGLISH] Have a blast.
[IN ENGLISH] Oh, I will.
Boom!
[IN HINDI] Step two.
Our key-holding Aunty Karen.
- [RUBAI] You'll seduce her?
- [KAREN SNORING]
[PATHAAN] I wish!
I'm not her type.
She'll be knocked out
by some sleeping pills.
[PATHAAN IMITATES SNORING]
[PATHAAN CHUCKLES]
♪ You are my Karen ♪
Good night, K-K-K-Karen.
[GOOFY MUSIC]
[PATHAAN] Step three.
We need two planes. And two pilots.
Absolute professionals.
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- [INDISTINCT HARMONIZING]
You picked this place?
No. Our pilots did.
- [IN ENGLISH] Pilots? Right.
- Hmm.
They're late.
Very professional.
Uh, actually, flying is just their hobby.
Professionally, they're singers.
Singers?
Singers.
[HARMONIZING IN RUSSIAN]
[SNIGGERS]
[PATHAAN] Hey! What about the bill?
[IN ENGLISH] Rubai, listen.
You'll have some cheese?
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[IN HINDI] Now for step four.
- [CAR ENGINE REVS]
- [RUBAI] What step is this?
[PATHAAN] Never mind. It's fun.
Are you and the, uh, missus
looking for anything in particular?
[IN ENGLISH] Very particular.
How would you like
to earn 20,000 boobles?
Rubles!
[IN HINDI] What did I say?
[IN ENGLISH] I meant rubles.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER ON TV]
[PATHAAN SIGHS, SNIFFLES]
[IN HINDI] Let's sleep early.
Tomorrow's a big day.
We have a meeting with Raktbeej.
Our final step.
[SOFT JAZZ MUSIC]
[PATHAAN] Uh...
Uh, I think you're taking this
honeymoon suite too seriously.
Tomorrow we have
an appointment with Raktbeej.
[IN ENGLISH] So, you know, get some rest.
[MUTTERS INDISTINCTLY]
This may be our last night
outside a Russian jail. So...
Then we shouldn't waste it.
[IN ENGLISH] Yeah! Waste is not good.
[SCOFFS]
Maybe I...
Could you help with my bandages?
Yeah... Bandages? Of course.
[IN HINDI] Nothing better I'd like to do
than change your bandages.
[RUBAI MOANS]
Pathaan.
I mean, you're actually a Pathaan?
Are you a Muslim?
Rubai, I don't know what I am.
Who I am.
Or who my parents were.
Or why I was abandoned
in front of a cinema.
Landed up in an orphanage,
then a juvenile center,
then a remand home.
So, it was really my country
that raised me.
When I was older,
I wanted to be a good son
and serve my parents.
Pay them back.
So I joined the Indian army.
[IN ENGLISH] I'm sorry.
[IN ENGLISH] No, it's okay.
[IN HINDI] By the way...
what film was playing
at the cinema where they left you?
[CHUCKLES]
You don't take emotions seriously?
Do you?
[SMACKS LIPS]
Never.
So... how did you turn from
Lawaaris to Khuda Gawah?
[CHUCKLES]
It was in 2002.
I was in Afghanistan on a joint
mission with the US army.
My first mission.
U.S.A. MILITARY BASE, AFGHANISTAN
The US target that day
was a Salauddin Husseini,
a Taliban leader.
A missile was locked
on to the location of his phone.
[MACHINE BEEPS]
This Mr. Husseini was a teacher
in a madrasa.
People started to run.
The problem was there were
30 kids still in the madrasa,
and the missile was to strike
in one minute.
The missile was locked
on to the location of his phone.
The kids were still inside.
[MISSILE WHOOSHES]
[LOUD EXPLOSION]
I was in a coma for a month.
A day did not go by without someone
in that village praying for me.
Subhanallah.
How are you?
Hmm.
- Adaab.
- Salaam.
Everyone has been praying
for your good health.
I swear, no Pathaan mother
has ever given birth to someone
as brave as you.
From today, we are yours
and you are ours.
Our Pathaan.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC]
[PATHAAN] You know what?
Every year, without fail, I try...
and celebrate Eid with everyone
in that village.
With my Pathaan family.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh, man...
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[DYNAMIC MUSIC]
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
Once we have the bag, we have
ten minutes. Don't forget.
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
- [IN ENGLISH] Set.
- [IN ENGLISH] Rubai, start your timer now.
Three, two, one.
- [MACHINE BEEPS]
- Go!
[TIMER BEEPS]
[IN RUSSIAN] Karen, do you have a copy...
Who are you?
[DYNAMIC MUSIC]
[DEVICE BEEPING]
- [BUCKLE CLASPS]
- [PLANE ENGINE WHIRRING]
[DYNAMIC MUSIC]
MALFUNCTION
[IN ENGLISH] Rubai!
I have a release malfunction.
[IN HINDI] Rubai, when you're
above the building, cut your rope.
[GRUNTS]
[IN ENGLISH] Captain, listen to me.
Are you crazy?
Just do it!
What the...
[THRILLING MUSIC]
[THRILLING MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[RIVETING MUSIC]
[IN HINDI] We're 90 seconds late.
The alarm will go off
in a minute. Let's go!
- Vault number?
- 412.
[IN HINDI] How do these steps open?
No time for that.
Here.
Throw it to me.
Pathaan...
[IN ENGLISH] I'm sorry.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[IN HINDI] It's impossible
to open that vault.
It is possible.
For Pathaan.
Pathaan?
Why would he help you?
Mate-check.
[IN ENGLISH] You mean "checkmate"?
When the king thinks the queen
will sacrifice herself for him,
and all his concentration
is on saving the queen.
When the king realizes the queen
has switched sides, it'll be...
too late.
Checkmate.
[IN ENGLISH] The king is dead.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
PRESENT DAY
[CABIN BELL CHIMES]
[PILOT IN ENGLISH]
Please be seated for landing.
So, did the Russians arrest Pathaan?
Yes.
And they tortured him badly.
[PATHAAN SCREAMING IN PAIN]
BLACK PRISON
Not that one, not that one!
It will hurt like hell.
No, not this one... [SHUDDERS]
No! It will hurt... [SCREAMS]
Talk, Pathaan.
You know everyone talks in the end.
Your Hindi is damn good.
Was your mother in India?
Or a joint operation?
[GROANS]
I know you can take a lot of pain.
How much more?
Pathaan was put into
a high security prison.
That's where I last saw him.
[DOOR OPENS]
He's not with us.
[HUFFS] Oh, please, Ms. Grewal.
We know he's Marcos's agent.
He was.
[IN ENGLISH] He went rogue.
Do you think
we would sanction this stupidity?
[IN HINDI] Whatever he has done,
we have no stake in it.
So you don't care how we deal
with this situation?
[IN ENGLISH] Be my guest.
[IN HINDI] And if this
situation survives...
pump him with two bullets from me.
I'll reimburse you.
- [LOCOMOTIVE WHISTLING]
- [RIVETING MUSIC]
[DYNAMIC MUSIC]
[IN RUSSIAN] I'm going to
crush your bones to powder.
You're a dead man walking.
[GROANS]
[IN HINDI] What was he saying?
[IN RUSSIAN] I'm going to kill you.
[HUFFS]
[GROANS] Ow!
[IN ENGLISH] Guys. Timeout, guys!
Please.
Wait...
- [GROANS]
- [LOUD THUD]
[THUD]
[RIVETING MUSIC]
[IN HINDI] Stopped at a coffee shop?
And a pharmacy.
Here. Painkillers.
Men don't feel pain.
- Hmm.
- [YELPS]
Take them, brother.
They're coming.
[GRUNTS]
You've taken it easy too long.
Let's get to work.
Tiger, he's got a grenade!
So what!
I have the pin.
When will you stop pulling pins?
[IN ENGLISH] I'm sorry.
[LOUD EXPLOSION]
[IN ENGLISH] I'm having a blast.
Are you?
[IN HINDI] Oh, man!
[GRUNTS]
[IN HINDI] Behind you!
[DYNAMIC MUSIC]
- [IN ENGLISH] Mission accomplished!
- Hmm.
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
- [IN HINDI] Did they come for you?
- Mm-hmm.
For you.
You made big trouble, didn't you?
I'm a Pathaan.
- Shall we run?
- Me first.
[DYNAMIC MUSIC]
[BOTH SCREAM]
[THUNDEROUS EXPLOSION]
[LAUGHS]
You got scared, right?
- Yes.
- [IN ENGLISH] I know.
For you.
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMS]
- [GUN LOADS]
- [GUNSHOTS FIRING]
Look back!
[CRASH, THUNDEROUS EXPLOSION]
Run!
Run, Pathaan! Run!
- Listen.
- [PATHAAN] Hmm.
I'm going on a big mission.
Hmm.
Tiger may need Pathaan.
So stay alive.
[IN HINDI] I will. I'll be there.
[SMACKS LIPS] Oh, man. I promise.
- Don't need promises.
- Then what?
I need those painkillers.
Oh, painkillers. It's here.
[LIGHTHEARTED MUSIC]
This is yours, this is mine.
Bitter, isn't it?
It's a painkiller.
Not chewing gum.
PRESENT DAY
So, Tiger helped Pathaan in Russia?
How come Pathaan was missing
for so long?
That was the first time
anyone had defeated Pathaan.
He swore...
without Rubai, Jim and Raktbeej...
he would not return.
To maintain diplomatic relations
with Russia,
Pathaan's absence suited us.
And now?
The time of Pathaan's exile is over.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Pump him with two bullets from me.
What could I have said?
Pathaan is like a son to me,
Why did Luthra let you go to Russia?
[SCOFFS]
[IN ENGLISH] Don't ask.
[IN HINDI] He wanted to go himself.
He would've shot you point-blank
if he knew the reason
that I went there was to give you...
a message.
He's not with us.
WHY YOU HERE
TIGER ON WAY
Did Raafe tell you anything?
Hmm.
Jim bought two Saber missiles.
He doesn't know why,
or where Jim is.
Or...
where she is.
Hmm.
- Paris? When?
- [TENSE MUSIC]
A few hours ago.
[IN ENGLISH] Activity?
[IN ENGLISH] Walks, cafes.
[IN HINDI]
Perhaps she's waiting for someone.
- [IN HINDI] Then I have to go.
- [MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[IN ENGLISH] Can't keep a girl waiting.
Pathaan, I don't know what
you stole from the Russians,
but I've never seen them so tense.
[IN ENGLISH] Find it.
Find Jim.
Ma'am.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
PARIS, FRANCE
[TENSE MUSIC]
Salaam Alaikum.
[IN ARABIC] Wa 'alaikumu s-salaam.
May peace be upon on you too.
[IN ENGLISH] Thank you, Raza.
[IN HINDI] In romantic Paris,
two's company, three's a crowd.
I must talk to her about
the pleasures of love.
Alone.
Alone, Raza.
[IN ENGLISH] Thank you.
You want to talk to me?
Or kill me?
[IN HINDI] I figured
when I'd see you again,
I'd shoot you first,
then ask questions.
But you called me here
of your own accord, so...
Of course, Rubai...
we conveniently got your photo
at the Paris metro.
You knew I'd see that CCTV footage.
And I would...
come to you.
[IN ENGLISH] So, well, I'm here.
[IN HINDI] Tell me quickly
what you have to say.
- Raktbeej.
- [TENSE MUSIC]
You want to know what it is?
What is it?
Smallpox?
It was eradicated in 1980.
Yes...
but some research facilities
still have samples of the virus,
in case we need to fight smallpox again.
The virus samples were in Russia.
We stole them.
But why?
Every country in this world
has a vaccine against smallpox.
In case of an emergency outbreak.
The vaccine works against
the old smallpox virus.
Jim has mutated it.
The mutated virus is far more dangerous.
We have no vaccine against it.
No cure either.
That's why he planned the big operation
in Dubai to kidnap Dr. Sahani.
Who for? Who's paying him?
- Do you know General Qadir?
- [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
It's time to befriend the Devil.
- Your government?
- No.
The General joined forces
with ISI extremists...
when India abrogated Article 370.
[IN ENGLISH] Pathaan, I swear...
[IN HINDI] I had no idea at all...
that my own people would
do such a mad thing.
If this virus spreads...
how can Pakistan save itself?
He has changed the virus's DNA.
It does not follow the one-week
pattern like Covid-19.
This kills within a few hours.
Anyone infected by this virus
cannot go very far.
Once it spreads, it decimates
a whole city in a matter of days.
But it can also be contained
within a city's borders.
It attacks one city at a time.
Not the whole world.
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
But how, Rubai?
So why do you think
I can trust you again?
I'm a soldier, Pathaan.
Just like you...
I will do anything for my country.
But this?
Killing thousands of innocents?
This is not my idea of war.
[SOFT MELODY]
[IN ENGLISH] Trust me, Pathaan.
[IN HINDI] Just once more.
I'll always have my eye on you.
One wrong move...
I've made all the wrong moves I had to.
Now I want them erased.
Where's Jim?
He's meeting Dr. Sahani
in his lab in two days.
[IN ENGLISH] Tell me about this lab.
[IN HINDI] Everything.
[RIVETING RAP MUSIC PLAYS]
So good to see you, sir!
Mm-hmm... if we survive,
we'll hug then.
Everybody, back to work.
- I'll never hug you.
- [CHUCKLES]
[PATHAAN SMACKS LIPS]
There's only one way.
Parachutes.
[IN ENGLISH] Land here, above the lab,
and work your way down there.
[NANDINI] Rubai?
Pathaan...
how can you trust her
after what happened in Russia?
[IN HINDI] Okay.
We won't trust her.
Next plan?
Use a missile.
Blow up the lab.
And Jim, the virus, the lot.
What if the virus isn't destroyed
and it gets into the air?
The virus could come down as rain...
over three continents.
[IN ENGLISH] Alright, Pathaan.
Make it happen.
- Ma'am.
- And...
get a trim.
[IN ENGLISH] Really?
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
[JIM'S THEME PLAYS]
Rubai!
Jim.
[IN ENGLISH] Looking good.
[IN ENGLISH] Always.
[IN HINDI] But you
haven't noticed me before.
[IN HINDI] Who says
love is only at first sight?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Want to drown in them?
I know the difference
between the sea and lava.
Did you design the virus as instructed?
[RIVETING MUSIC]
Are you really going to do this?
For money?
You think this is about money?
I could've easily robbed a bank
blindfolded, Doctor.
I was asked a question once.
What's your price?
Today you have my answer.
And I will decide the price of your life.
Do you have the power to buy me?
So buy me.
This is crazy.
These are your own people.
Your own country.
[SCOFFS] Oh, Doc!
Country, borders, etcetera.
They exist to remind the weak
to stay in their place.
While the real machines keep turning.
[IN ENGLISH] Power and control.
[IN HINDI] I don't care
for any country now.
My country is wherever I happen to be.
That's my world.
[THRILLING MUSIC]
[MACHINE BEEPS]
SATELLITE PREF LOCATION
[SIREN BUZZING]
Let me check.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [GROANS]
CENTER D'INNOVATION
ET DE RECHFRCHE
[SIREN CONTINUES BUZZING]
[IN ENGLISH] Stay out.
[IN HINDI] If anything happens to these
orbs, then cut your own throat.
[ENTHRALLING MUSIC]
Dr. Sahani!
Give me the orbs.
[MULTIPLE GUNSHOTS]
- [LOUD EXPLOSION]
- [GRUNTS]
The orbs are safe.
Let's go.
Jim, I was trying to keep
Raktbeej safe...
Normally when you lie,
it's so smoothly done.
I'm touched you're scared of me.
- Jim, trust me, I...
- Explain to your people...
how you betrayed them.
General Qadir is not "my people".
When my people hear what he has done,
they'll bloody hang him.
I... I have a daughter.
I wanted you to stay alive for her sake.
[RUBAI GRUNTS]
Bag?
[MOTORCYCLE REVVING]
[DYNAMIC MUSIC]
[LOUD EXPLOSION]
- [MOTORCYCLE SCREECHES]
- [GUNFIRE]
[IN ENGLISH] He must be close.
[LOUD EXPLOSION]
[EXHILARATING MUSIC]
[MOTORCYCLE REVVING]
[JIM'S THEME PLAYS]
[BOMB EXPLODES]
[SOFT MELODY]
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
Give it to me, Pathaan.
No, sir. We have to destroy it.
Right now.
[IN ENGLISH] Absolutely not.
[IN HINDI] Jim has mutated
the smallpox virus,
- so we need to make a vaccine.
- [IN ENGLISH] I don't think so, sir.
[IN ENGLISH] Give it to me.
Sir.
Sir...
- [TENSE MUSIC]
- Pathaan!
- [IN ENGLISH] What the hell, sir?
- [RUBAI GRUNTS]
[IN HINDI] What's going on?
[IN ENGLISH] She's ISI, Pathaan.
We have the virus orb, thanks to her.
[IN HINDI] And thanks to her,
the virus landed in Jim's hands.
She knows Jim's plans.
[IN ENGLISH] We have
to question her, Pathaan.
Ma'am...
Besides, where can she go now?
Jim and the ISI are looking for her.
If we let her go,
she won't survive for two days.
[IN ENGLISH] Take her.
- [IN ENGLISH] Wait!
- [RUBAI GRUNTS]
[WHISPERS] Pathaan...
[IN HINDI] You'll be okay.
Pathaan's promise.
[REASSURING MUSIC]
- Where's Jim?
- [THUD]
[WOMAN 1] Where is the antivirus?
[WOMAN 2] What is the missile's target?
[WOMAN 1] You know his plans.
[MAN 1] You think we believe
you know nothing!
No one knows anything.
What Jim thinks or plans,
only Jim knows.
If anything goes wrong,
he has a backup plan.
Things may be going wrong
for him right now,
but soon his backup plan will kick in.
This screw-up must have been...
planned by Jim.
INDIAN INSTITUTE OF
CONTAGIOUS DISEASES
Ma'am, you'll have to wear this suit.
[IN ENGLISH] Yes, Doctor?
[IN HINDI] I got your message.
Come, Nandini.
I must show you something.
[IN ENGLISH] Show me.
There are three layers
to get to the orb's core.
- [IN HINDI] Did you cut through?
- We got to the central core.
Where the virus is.
It was empty.
[IN ENGLISH] What?
We analyzed the liquid carefully.
It's water. Only water.
- [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
- [MACHINES BEEP]
[IN HINDI] What happened to the lights?
Ma'am, our system has been hacked.
[IN ENGLISH] There's an incoming
video call.
It's Jim.
[IN ENGLISH] Connect him.
Hello, hello! How's everyone?
Was it fun?
Finding only pure distilled
mineral water in the orb?
What the hell are you playing at, Jim?
Just following my plan in case
anyone tried to force the orbs open.
The orb has three layers.
The first layer was empty.
Only a vacuum.
The second layer wasn't empty.
It contained an invisible corrosive gas.
It's an acid that
melts plastic on contact.
Your plastic suits, for example.
The third layer contained my superstar.
Raktbeej.
The virus is now all over the lab.
In the orb's center, you'll find
clean safe mineral water.
You won't feel thirsty
when you're dying.
[IN ENGLISH] You think I'm bluffing?
[IN HINDI] Look at your
pretty white suits.
Are they turning black?
[SUITS CRACKLING]
Your suits are of no use now.
The virus you were
looking for in the water
is invading your whole body.
If pain is measured on a scale of ten...
you'll experience it at 13 or 14.
Exciting, right?
A demo of Raktbeej.
So please, share your dying moments
on Instagram and Twitter.
Things that are seen... they sell.
[IN ENGLISH] Cheers!
No!
Lock down the lab!
Lock the lab!
- [IN HINDI] Others, get out of here!
- [INAUDIBLE CHATTER]
We're sealing the lab.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING IN FEAR]
[IN ENGLISH] Get out! Get out now!
Get out all of you!
We can decontaminate the atmosphere.
UV radiation, gamma rays.
[IN HINDI] But how can you
decontaminate us, Luthra?
The virus is inside us.
[PANICKY CHATTER]
There's only one way.
[DYNAMIC MUSIC]
Very few people get the chance
to decide how they'll face their death.
With fear? Hesitation?
Or will they panic?
I will not give a bloody terrorist
that satisfaction.
I'm a soldier.
And now...
all of you are too.
Everyone dies someday...
today it's our turn.
[IN ENGLISH] I accept it.
[VICTORIOUS MUSIC]
Colonel, you know what to do.
[IN HINDI] Don't save RDX.
We'll be dead anyway.
Just make sure the virus does not spread.
[IN ENGLISH] Thank you.
Thank you, everyone.
It was a great honor serving with you.
[IN HINDI] You're the molten gold
that kept my life together.
Ma'am...
You are that gold now, Pathaan.
You'll keep everyone together,
and make them strong.
You were always...
the one who kept us together.
Don't stop.
[IN ENGLISH] Get Jim.
[IN ENGLISH] I promise, ma'am.
[IN HINDI] Make him die a death...
far worse than ours.
Ma'am.
[DYNAMIC MUSIC]
[IN ENGLISH] I hated guns.
[IN HINDI] In the name of Lord Shiva!
[GUNSHOT]
[JIM IN ENGLISH] Hello, everyone.
[IN HINDI] I know
this is a bad time for all of you.
I respect your pain.
So, I'll do my best
not to appear too cheerful.
[IN ENGLISH] But come on!
[IN HINDI] It was some plan!
You should be impressed.
You were an Indian soldier. Dammit!
And thanks to you,
I'm an Indian businessman now.
If you survive, you might
become a client of mine.
Then I'll get you anything you want.
Right now, I serve another client.
I'm doing what he wants.
Do you even realize what you're doing?
You're unleashing your wrath on humanity!
[IN ENGLISH] History will
remember you as a monster!
Oh! That never occurred to me.
What can I do?
Everything is ready.
My Saber missile.
[IN ENGLISH] Armed and ready.
[IN HINDI] It's in a location
that only I know.
The target?
An Indian city, that only I know.
Such a pity!
You blew up your lab before you could
see what Raktbeej was capable of.
But when it spreads in Delhi,
Mumbai, Hyderabad or Amritsar...
what will you do?
Blow up those cities?
[IN HINDI] What do you want?
I want you to negotiate with
a terrorist, Colonel Luthra.
You didn't do it for me.
Now you'll negotiate with me.
[IN ENGLISH] What do you want?
[IN ENGLISH] What do you think?
Kashmir.
Obviously, Kashmir.
You have 24 hours.
[IN HINDI] After 24 hours,
if a single soldier,
a single tank, a single gun...
or the Indian flag
is seen in Kashmir, then...
[IN ENGLISH] That's impossible!
[IN HINDI] How can I
make that happen in 24 hours?
We need time to think.
Perhaps I used the wrong word,
that's why you're confused.
This is not a negotiation, Colonel Luthra,
it's an ultimatum.
[IN ENGLISH] Your time starts...
[WATCH BEEPS]
...now.
The situation you're in,
the fear that's overcoming you,
I've been there.
No one took responsibility for
the death of my wife and unborn child.
And now no one is
responsible for your death.
[LAUGHS]
[IN ENGLISH] How does it feel, guys?
[IN HINDI] It's not appropriate
to say "Jai Hind".
[IN ENGLISH] So, take care.
[IN HINDI] Time is running out.
[MAN 1] Pathaan, you have to
stop this madman.
- [WHACKING]
- [CHAIN RATTLING]
Mm-hmm. Look! Your innocent family.
You know what we'll do to them?
Whichever city the missile strikes,
that's where your family will be.
Where is that missile?
My job...
was only to make payment.
Mm-hmm.
I said Jim would tell them
where to deliver it.
[THUD]
If you don't know the city,
you must know the country.
Where?
Afghanistan.
Father!
[WHIMPERS]
[GRUNTS]
[SOFT MELODY]
[IN ENGLISH] I'm sorry, Rubai.
[IN HINDI] Fear blinds people.
But you can see...
I'm not your enemy.
I know.
I shouldn't do this.
It's wrong.
[IN ENGLISH] I'm sorry.
Pathaan?
[IN HINDI] Not to you.
To you!
I said sorry.
[SIRENS BLARING]
AFGHANISTAN
[RHYTHMIC MUSIC]
All calm, General?
I don't want calm, I want havoc.
India will not give Kashmir, General.
So...
do we teach them a lesson?
[DYNAMIC MUSIC]
[JIM] The missile is ready.
You just have to press the button
and I have to get paid.
Then...
boom!
ENTER AMOUNT
General!
Sir.
[IN PASHTO] Everyone in my village
was struck by a strange disease.
They're all dead now.
A metal ball fell here and no one
survived after that.
What are they saying?
The video is from an Afghan village,
some 200 kms away.
The local TV is saying...
a strange virus is spreading
through the village.
It has the same symptoms as...
smallpox.
[IN ENGLISH] That's...
that's impossible.
Raktbeej.
[IN HINDI] How can it be Raktbeej?
One orb is on the missile...
and the other was destroyed in India.
Either you're a fool...
or you think I am.
If you want all your money,
find out how this other Raktbeej
landed there.
[GUNS COCKING]
You're mistaken
if you think I'm your friend...
or that I have sympathy towards Pakistan.
Or that I need money.
You haven't understood me, General.
I am the demon Raktbeej.
[GAGS] Leave me!
If you want to see a free show,
why pick on Delhi?
Change the co-ordinates.
Let's party in Islamabad.
No, sorry. I'm sorry. Don't do that.
[GROANS]
[IN ENGLISH] You handle it
yourself, right?
Exactly as you told me.
I don't know where it came from.
[IN HINDI] Find out what's going on.
Who's behind this?
I want the answer...
and his head.
I want both.
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
How?
Welcome!
[DYNAMIC MUSIC]
To my home!
This is my Afghan family.
My people.
Our Pathaan.
What did you find there?
The man who stands before you.
Pathaan.
You have this nasty habit.
You smell a party and arrive uninvited.
Never ever invited to a bash,
Pathaan just loves to gatecrash.
If you have a party in Pathaan's home,
he has to be there to welcome you...
with some fireworks.
Some joke, General!
Another of your agents
has fallen in love with the enemy.
First there was Zoya and Tiger.
And now...
Has ISI turned into some
dating website for Indian agents?
MISSILE STATE
UNARMED
[THRILLING MUSIC]
MISSILE STATE
ARMED 02:44
Pathaan!
Raza... Raza!
Pathaan...
Pathaan, Jim isn't a man to give up.
There must be...
Huh?
- Amol!
- Sir!
Amol, see if the orb
can be detached from the missile.
- [IN ENGLISH] Yes, sir!
- [IN ENGLISH] Duck!
Let's do this, man.
MISSILE STATE
ARMED 01:49
I'll deactivate the missile.
[GRUNTS]
[DYNAMIC MUSIC]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[RIVETING MUSIC]
[JIM'S THEME PLAYS]
[MULTIPLE SHOTS FIRING]
Where's the orb?
Pathaan, the missile
was only a diversion.
The real Raktbeej isn't here.
Jim had another plan all along.
[LOUD EXPLOSION]
Where is Raktbeej?
What is Jim's real plan?
- You traitor, I will...
- [GUNSHOT FIRED]
[IN ENGLISH] Wait! Wait!
Only Sergei knows.
Sergei.
Flight LT-72.
[GROANS]
[THUD]
[RUBAI] Pathaan and
Colonel Luthra, listen to me.
Raktbeej is on a plane.
Flight LT-72.
It's circling Delhi right now.
There's a way to deactivate the orb...
and only Jim knows how.
Connect me to air traffic control. Now!
- Pathaan, find Jim.
- [IN ENGLISH] Yeah...
Yes.
[JIM'S THEME PLAYS]
[IN ENGLISH] Flight LT-72, do you hear me?
[IN ENGLISH] Ground Air Control,
this is Captain Mehra from Flight LT-72.
Landing permission denied.
I repeat, landing permission denied.
What?
Raktbeej is sitting happily
in a plane over Delhi now.
The orb has six minutes left.
And so does Delhi.
In six minutes, the virus...
will spread through the plane's AC ducts.
Unless...
you can grab this
detonator switch from me.
What a pity!
It's unlikely.
[BOTH SCREAM]
[IN ENGLISH] Captain Mehra,
this is Colonel Luthra from RAW.
[IN HINDI] There's a biological weapon
on board.
The device is in your AC ducts.
What?
What am I supposed to do, Colonel?
We're running low on fuel.
Captain, you're carrying
a very dangerous weapon.
Fly as far as you can
from Delhi, please.
[TIMER BEEPS]
CONNECTING TO Wi-Fi.
CONNECTED
I found it, Colonel.
[IN HINDI] Only four minutes to go.
[IN ENGLISH] Get me the minister.
[TIMER BEEPS]
[IN ENGLISH] Yes, sir.
[IN HINDI] There is no other option.
Jai Hind.
[IN ENGLISH] Connect me
to missile command.
[IN ENGLISH] Yes, sir.
[LUTHRA IN HINDI] Captain, we will
have to destroy the plane.
[IN HINDI] There must be
another way, Colonel.
I have 300 passengers
and many children on board.
Right now, your plane is more
dangerous than a nuclear bomb.
[IN ENGLISH] I'm sorry.
We... can't save you.
Missile Control,
initiate strike protocol.
[IN ENGLISH] Come on, Pathaan.
There's only one option.
Remember how you
sacrificed your scientists?
Play "Vande Mataram" on the plane
and blow up the passengers.
Fire.
My family's lives were sacrificed.
Now it's your turn to make a sacrifice.
[THRILLING MUSIC]
[TIMER BEEPS]
- [KNIFE SQUELCHES]
- [GROANS]
Farewell, Pathaan.
[TRIUMPHANT MUSIC]
[IN ENGLISH] The timer has stopped, sir.
Please stop the missile.
[IN ENGLISH] Abort, abort, abort!
[LOUD EXPLOSION]
[EVERYONE] Yeah!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
[EVERYONE APPLAUDS]
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is your Captain here.
Please buckle up because
we're about to land in Delhi.
[HUFFS]
You couldn't understand
something very simple, Jim.
A soldier does not ask...
what his country can do for him.
He asks...
what he can do for his country.
[TRIUMPHANT MUSIC]
You don't deserve this, Jim.
Give your Mother India my last goodbye.
Jai Hind.
[TRIUMPHANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MELLOW MUSIC]
DIRECTOR
SIDDHARTH ANAND
PRODUCER
ADITYA CHOPRA
If anyone merits this medal,
it's you.
I've never met a braver soldier than you.
Ma'am.
Pathaan.
Colonel, good news.
I'm leaving.
So you won't suffer from acidity
and blood pressure anymore. [CHUCKLES]
Our paths are separate now.
- Thank you, sir.
- The war is not over, Pathaan.
[TENSE MUSIC]
[IN ENGLISH] We need you.
[IN ENGLISH] Me?
[IN HINDI] But we are...
What did you call us? Broken eggshells?
[IN HINDI] I admit
mistakes were made, Pathaan.
But this country cannot be saved
by Colonel Luthra alone.
Or by Tiger or Kabir.
Or even by Pathaan.
Everyone is needed.
There are many soldiers like them,
Pathaan.
Some with wounded bodies,
others with damaged souls.
But they are ready to sacrifice
their lives for this country.
These broken folks can
only be put together with the gold...
that has lived through fire.
And that person is you.
Make the sharpest sword, Pathaan,
so the souls of the enemy tremble.
But who will wield that sword?
Who will it strike?
How will it strike?
Who decides that?
The sword is yours.
So it is your call.
[DYNAMIC MUSIC]
[IN ENGLISH] Thank you.
Thank you very much, sir.
- [IN ENGLISH] Let's start.
- Yes, sir.
Uh... sorry, sir.
[IN HINDI] I have an urgent appointment.
[IN HINDI] With whom?
With... my hairdresser.
Getting a haircut?
No, sir.
- Just shampoo.
- [JUBILANT MUSIC]
[LAUGHS]
[MOTORCYCLES REVVING]
♪ If you want to fall in love ♪
♪ I know what love is ♪
♪ I ask only ♪
♪ My heart for permission ♪
♪ The ways of love ♪
♪ Only the fortunate know ♪
♪ Risking my own life ♪
♪ I saved the enemy ♪
♪ Many people love to talk ♪
♪ Many people ♪
♪ I know what's real, my friends ♪
♪ My friends ♪
♪ Many people love to talk ♪
♪ But I know what's real ♪
♪ I can even stop the wind ♪
♪ The Lord showers you with prayers ♪
♪ When Pathaan
Gets into the groove, my love ♪
♪ He steals all hearts ♪
♪ The promises he makes, my love ♪
♪ He'll stand by forever ♪
♪ When Pathaan
Gets into the groove, my love ♪
♪ He steals all hearts ♪
♪ The promises he makes, my love ♪
♪ He'll stand by forever ♪
♪ I'll tell you how to win hearts ♪
♪ My friends! ♪
♪ I will tell you how ♪
♪ I'll tell you how to love ♪
♪ the enemy ♪
♪ I will tell you how ♪
♪ Just give me a sign ♪
♪ A sign ♪
♪ I'll give my heart to you twice over ♪
♪ Twice ♪
♪ Just give me a sign ♪
♪ I'll give my heart to you twice over ♪
♪ Feelings of friendship ♪
♪ have cast their spell ♪
♪ Even enemies turn to me for an embrace ♪
♪ When Pathaan gets into the groove, ♪
♪ my love ♪
♪ He steals all hearts ♪
♪ The promises he makes, my love ♪
♪ He'll stand by forever ♪
♪ When Pathaan gets into the groove, ♪
♪ my love ♪
♪ He steals all hearts ♪
♪ The promises he makes, ♪
♪ my love ♪
♪ He'll stand by forever ♪
[BOTH GRUNT, GROAN]
Can't do it anymore.
Yeah.
I've been thinking, it's been 30 years,
we should stop.
But who'll replace us?
Hmm...
Hey... [CLEARS THROAT]
There's that guy.
Hmm?
That guy.
[SCOFFS]
No?
[SNIFFLES]
What about that other guy?
He has something.
No, not him.
He's got no style. Nah!
No.
Never mind.
- And him?
- Nah!
- No.
No.
- It's up to us, Bhai.
- Hmm.
Our country is at stake.
We can't leave it to kids.
Come on. Let's go.
Help me up. Lift me up.
Lower back.
♪ When all the world is burning ♪
♪ And fearing all the time ♪
♪ Crying every breath out loud for help ♪
♪ But there's no one around ♪
♪ Looking in the gloomy face of bleak ♪
♪ And darkness everywhere ♪
♪ Losing all hope and faith ♪
♪ But there's no one to dare ♪
♪ Rises an arrow to burn the evil ♪
♪ And set the order right ♪
♪ He strikes a blow, he fights alone ♪
♪ Shining so bright he's the knight ♪